Chapter 1033: Flood Dragon

This pressure belonged to a type of spiritual attack, mostly from high-ranked Experts. It can also be used by low-ranking beings, but this was only possible if they had an innate talent. These include the Dragons from the Ark Continent. However, this kind of pressure was almost useless in front of Zhao Hai.

However, the pressure this time was different. This time, Zhao Hai can actually feel it. One should know that Zhao Hai had long surpassed the strength he had back in the Ark Continent. In this case, feeling this pressure meant that the Snake King wasn’t an ordinary foe.

Zhao Hai stopped and focused on what was in front of him. Although his spiritual force can sweep towards the enemy, the other party had wrapped themselves up with their own spiritual force. Because of this, Zhao Hai couldn’t see what he wanted to see.

The Snake King got closer and closer to Zhao Hai. 500 meters, 100 meters, and before long the two parties met eye to eye.

The Soul Snake King was forced to stop. He didn’t expect to see a human being here. He expected another high-ranked magic beast causing trouble, not a human.

At the same time, Zhao Hai was also shocked. The Soul Snake King in front of him was about a hundred meters long. The thickness of its grey scales was very evident. What surprised Zhao Hai the most was the fact that there was a pair of horns growing on top of the snake’s head. It was clearly a Flood Dragon!

A Flood Dragon wasn’t a Dragon, it was something that has yet to become one. But meeting a Flood Dragon here truly surprised Zhao Hai!

At this moment, Zhao Hai calmed himself down. The Flood Dragon also stopped. Zhao Hai inspected the creature in front of him. It was truly a huge flood dragon.

While Zhao Hai was inspecting the flood dragon, the flood dragon was also sizing Zhao Hai up. After scanning Zhao Hai with his spiritual force for some time, a voice was suddenly transmitted to Zhao Hai’s mind, “Who are you? Why did you come here?”

Zhao Hai stared, then he quickly understood that the snake king was talking to him. However, this was a spiritual force communication. To people with their level of strength, communicating using this method was quite normal.

Zhao Hai replied, “I have seen the Snake King, this one is Zhao Hai.”

The huge snake slowly approached Zhao Hai, then it said, “You still haven’t told me why you came here.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “The Underworld will be my domain in the future. And this place will be mine as well. I don’t need a reason to come here.”

Rampant, too rampant. Zhao Hai’s words were too overbearing, to the point where the Snake King was given a shock. The Snake King went closer towards Zhao Hai before its mouth opened, releasing a bellow of spiritual force. It seems like Zhao Hai’s words had angered him.

Zhao Hai didn’t move and just countered the spiritual force, steadily defending.

The Snake King discovered that his spiritual force wasn’t able to affect the man in front of him. But since he was close enough to Zhao Hai, he began to spit out a blood red poisonous mist.

Zhao Hai finally made a move. He waved his hand, making a spatial rift appear that sucked the poisonous mist in. Then Zhao Hai waved his hand once more as he took a huge red hammer out and attacked the Snake King.

The Snake King was truly worthy of its title. Although Zhao Hai’s spatial rift gave it a shock, it quickly recovered. Its body curved as its tail met with Zhao Hai’s hammer.

Boom! The hammer was repelled by the Snake King’s tail. However, the Snake King also let out a painful roar. He didn’t expect Zhao Hai’s attack to be so strong, a few of its scales had actually been peeled off.

But at the same time, Zhao Hai didn’t expect the Snake King’s scale to be so hard. He used his blood ghost staff and turned it into a hammer, but it only crushed a few of the Snake King’s scales. It failed to cause huge damage to the snake’s body.

Zhao Hai quickly changed his weapon into a giant sickle before swinging it towards the Snake King. The Snake King wouldn’t dare underestimate Zhao Hai’s weapon again. He just ate some damage thanks to his negligence.

The Snake King curled up before rolling out. But this time, a spatial rift suddenly appeared in front of it. This curled up ball happen to be heading towards the spatial rift.

But the Snake King was able to react fast. When its head entered the spatial rift, it immediately sensed that something was wrong. Therefore, it smashed its tail down, intending to drag itself out of the rift.

However, Zhao Hai used this opportunity to make a move. His sickle forked the Snake King’s body and pushed it towards the Space. On the other hand, the Snake King didn’t admit defeat, its tail was still firmly anchored outside, refusing to enter the Space.

But it was already too late. Zhao Hai’s figure moved and entered the Space. After that, the handle of the sickle turned into chains. With the sickle firmly stuck in place, Zhao Hai wound the chain around the Snake King before giving a strong tug, bringing the soul snake into the Space.

The entire process might seem to take a long time, but the entire process was actually very quick. Zhao Hai and the Flood Dragon only fought for a few rounds before Zhao Hai set up a trap to capture the snake into the Space.

As the Snake King entered the Space, a prompt was immediately heard, “Flood Dragon-type being detected. Subduing. Subjugation completed. Flood dragons are improved version of snake-type beings. Host may now purchase flood dragons from the Space’s shop.”

Zhao Hai paused, he didn’t expect the Space to reach the same identification as him. It seems like the Snake King was truly on its way to becoming a Dragon.

Zhao Hai let out a long breath. He had the Space heal the Snake King before he called it over. It didn’t take long before the enormous Snake King appeared in front of Zhao hai.

When the Snake King arrived, it immediately sent a spiritual wave, “I have seen the Young Master. Does the Young Master have any commands?”

Zhao Hai replied, “How did you turn into your current appearance? Is it only by cultivation?”

The Snake King nodded and said, “Yes, Young Master. But I also ate some plants. These plants increase my life force and also my internal energy.”

Zhao Hai stared, then his figure teleported to the bone fields, bringing the Snake King along with him. Zhao Hai gestured towards the plants in the field and said, “Which of these plants did you consume?”

The Snake King pointed to a few plants using its tail. However, the Snake King didn’t point to any of the bone plants. Zhao Hai looked at the plants and nodded. Then he had Cai’er take note of those plants, they should be good in evolving snakes.

Even so, Zhao Hai was disappointed that the Snake King didn’t point at the bone plants. He pointed to the bone plants and said, “How about this plant? Do you eat these things?”

The Snake King nodded and said, “Replying to the Young Master. Some ate it, but not me. This plant has no use for us. After eating this plant, it wouldn’t increase our life force nor did it increase our energy. When a soul snake that ate this plant dies, they completely lose their fiery souls. Their body would also disappear, only leaving a piece of bone or two. Because of this, we always regarded these plants as ominous.”

The Snake King’s words made Zhao Hai’s eyes shine. The scenario that the Snake King described was the same description that the Gibbon Brothers said. The only surviving evidence of the soul snake that the brothers killed were two fangs. If this was really the case, then Zhao Hai finally had an idea on how to use the bone plants.

Zhao Hai immediately replied, “Did you collect the bones left behind by those snakes?”

Although the Snake Kind didn’t know why Zhao Hai was asking this question, he could feel that it was important for Zhao Hai. Therefore, it quickly answered, “We’ve kept their bones. But since we see them as dangerous, we kept them inside a mountain, far away from the place we live in.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Lead me to take a look.” After he said that, Zhao Hai waved his hand as they returned to the Snake King’s domain. Then the Snake King brought Zhao Hai to a bone mountain. There was a cavern on the side of this mountain. The cavern wasn’t very big nor was it deep into the mountain. However, there were bones stored inside. Each one of these bones looked like crystals, they shone despite the relative darkness of the place.

These bones didn’t only include soul snake fangs, there were also bones from other parts of their body. Zhao Hai also saw a well-preserved snakehead. Naturally, the head was small. There were also scales present, one of them looked very special since it was the size of a palm.

The Snake King turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Young Master, the bones are in here.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he released his spiritual force to scan through this pile of bones. After a short inspection, Zhao Hai can affirm that all of these bones were soul weapons!

Zhao Hai rejoiced. He finally discovered the use of bone plants. This made it possible for him to make beasts that produce soul weapons. Although Zhao Hai didn’t know the purpose of these bones once they become soul weapons, he was certain that they would have great uses.

Zhao Hai thought about it and decided to call them soul bones. He waved his hand to take all of the soul bones before he turned to the Snake King and said, “You stay here. But remember, if you discover more of these bones in the future, make sure to collect them for me. It doesn’t matter if it came from soul snakes or other beasts.”

The Snake King nodded. Then Zhao Hai’s figure flashed back into the Space.

…………………………………….

Author’s Note:

I know that the readers reading this chapter would think that Flood Dragons are too weak. But don’t worry, this is a flood dragon that grew in the Underworld, not in the Cultivation Realm. Therefore, it wasn’t very strong. After Zhao Hai goes to the Cultivation Realm, these things would be further explained. Please don’t worry about it!

Chapter 1034: Strange Central Region

After Zhao Hai returned to the Space, he immediately went to Wild Dragon Island to look for Gimreden. Gimreden was currently doing an experiment with the Gibbon Brothers. By this point, the target for Gimreden’s research was already shifted to the Gibbon Brothers’ soul weapons.

Gimreden’s research had something to do with joining one’s soul with a weapon. And now, the Gibbon Brothers could actually use their souls to make their weapons take action. Moreover, their weapons had integrated into their souls. For Gimreden, this was a very precious discovery. Gimreden wanted to study how the weapons fused with the soul. As long as he figured this out, then his research would certainly gain considerable progress.

However, Gimreden’s path to this progress had just begun, and the Gibbon Brothers only had two weapons in hand. The size of these weapons wasn’t large either. Because of this, Gimreden was afraid of carrying tests on them. He was afraid that he would end up destroying these weapons. At this point, Gimreden can only make careful observations regarding the items. Because of this, his progress was very slow.

The key to this research were the materials. Although Gimreden really liked to dismantle the Gibbon Brothers’ weapons, he didn’t have the guts to do it right now.

The pair of weapons were very small, ruining one would be a huge loss. After they were dismantled, they would certainly lose their function. This would put the research at a screeching halt. It was because of this that the Gibbon Brothers were always with Gimreden.

The Gibbon Brothers weren’t too reluctant to part with their weapons. Although they really needed the weapons, they were completely immersed in research at this point. For them, they would do anything for the sake of results, even if it ends up with the destruction of their weapons. Additionally, they were now inside the Space, so they weren’t in immediate danger. There was no point in keeping the soul weapons for themselves.

At this time, upon arriving at Wild Dragon Island, Zhao Hai immediately went to Gimreden’s laboratory. Although Gimreden needed to teach in the Undead Academy, he only had 5 teaching hours per week. Because of this, Gimreden was still able to conduct experiments in his laboratory.

In order to facilitate the exchanges in the various Academies, Zhao Hai equipped each one with a teleportation magic formation. This magic formation allowed people to go to each Academy, making the exchange more convenient. Naturally, Zhao Hai also placed a magic formation in Wild Dragon Island. However, those who can use this formation were only limited to a few chosen people such as Gimreden and the others.

Because of the Academy Alliance, Zhao Hai didn’t only send Gimreden and Kampala’s group. Those in Wild Dragon Island were also employed to teach at the other Academies. These people normally lived in Wild Dragon Island and would only go to the Academies when they do their lectures. When they were done, they would return to Wild Dragon Island in order to resume their work. To make it easier for them, Zhao Hai decided to install a magic formation in Wild Dragon Island for them to use.

Gimreden’s laboratory wasn’t too far away from Karen’s. Both sides also carried exchanges of information. At this moment, Karen’t laboratory was the largest one in the island, the others were still trailing behind.

Gimreden and the two brothers were currently conducting a microscopic examination on the soul weapons. Since they wouldn’t dare to destroy the weapons at this time, they could only use this method. These microscopes were things that Zhao Hai provided to the various laboratories in the island. Naturally, these were acquired from the science and technology backgrounds.

After seeing Zhao Hai arrive, the three couldn’t help but stare. However, they quickly responded and gave Zhao Hai a salute. Zhao Hai waved his hand and said, “As you were. How is your research going?”

Gimreden sighed and said, “Not very well. The materials are too few. We wouldn’t dare use them up. Because of this, we cannot do deeper experimentations.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he inspected Firemen’s laboratory. The place was extremely neat, reflecting Gimreden’s care. Then Zhao Hai waved his hand as he took some soul bones out, then he said, “Take a look at these bones. They’re the same as the Gibbon Brothers’ weapons. You can conduct experiments on these things. We would have more of these things in the future. You don’t need to be careful anymore. Use them all up if you need to.”

When Gimreden saw these bones, it was as if he had forgotten everything else. He rushed over and used his spiritual force to scan the bones. Gimreden’s eyes lit up as he took one bone, then he went to a pulverizer and placed it inside.

The Gibbon Brothers also seemed to forget Zhao Hai’s presence as they immediately tidied the laboratory up. The test equipments were prepared, the three Lich forgot to talk to Zhao Hai.

After seeing their reaction, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile bitterly as he shook his head. Then he turned around to leave the laboratory and return to the villa.

Laura and the others were currently in the living room.. The monitor wasn’t displaying the Underworld, instead it showed the events in the Divine Realm’s Taurus Continent. The Foreign Races and the O’Neal family still carried on fighting small conflicts here and there. Both sides had wins and they also suffered losses. But generally speaking, the Foreign Races were losing more.

However, although the Taurus Continent was shown on the monitor, Laura and the others weren’t looking. Instead, they just relaxed and had a chat.

After seeing Zhao Hai return, Laura and the others immediately stood up. They saw Zhao Hai’s fight with the Snake King. However, they didn’t expect Zhao Hai to return to the villa right after.

Zhao Hai looked at the women and smiled, “I just went to Wild Dragon Island to send materials to Gimreden. Cai’er, come here quick, I’ve managed to find out a use for those bone plants.”

Cai’er immediately flew over, she looked pleasantly surprised at Zhao Hai as she said, “Young Master, are you telling the truth?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Soul snakes who have eaten those bone plants don’t leave behind fiery souls when they die. Instead, they leave pieces of bones much like the weapons used by the Gibbon Brothers. This means that the bone plants might be thing that aids magic beasts in forming soul bones. Cai’er, try it out, see if you can gather soul bones from the beasts in the Space. I will leave this matter to you.”

Cai’er nodded before she turned around and disappeared. Naturally, she went to do the experiment on the magic beasts. Zhao Hai didn’t think about it anymore as he sat down and changed the image on the monitor to the Underworld. He stared at the regions that Addison drew.

Laura frowned when she saw Zhao Hai looking at the map. She asked, “Brother Hai, do you still plan to return to the Dark Creature’s domain? Didn’t you already discover the secret to soul weapons?”

Zhao Hai turned his head to Laura and said, “I’ll be fine. Haven’t you seen? Those Dark Creatures are not a threat to me. I want to conquer the Dark Creature Domain, isn’t that part of unifying the Underworld?”

Laura nodded and didn’t say anything else, the same was true with Lizzy and the others. The group just proceeded to look at the map and the regions that were sectioned out. Even if the marks were clearly seen, this only involved the outskirts of the territory. The central area was still blank.

Zhao Hai rubbed his forehead for a moment before he called the Snake King over. Since the Snake King was huge, he can only wait for Zhao Hai outside the villa.

When Zhao Hai came out of the villa, the Snake King immediately gave him a salute. Zhao Hai nodded as he waved his hand. After that, an image of the Dark Creature Domain appeared. Zhao Hai pointed at the projection and said, “Snake King, take a look. Is the information about the magic beasts correct?” At the same time, Zhao Hai also said the name of the magic beasts as well as their reported power level.

Although the Snake King had intellect no less than a human, it still doesn’t know how to read. Because of this, Zhao Hai can only orally relay everything to it. After listening to Zhao Hai’s words, the Snake King nodded and said, “Answering to the Young Master. This map is basically correct. However, we magic beasts live very long lives and we also cultivate slowly. Even if there is nothing wrong with this map, I also haven’t got into contact with these fellows in about 100 years. If there were changes then I wouldn’t know.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Alright, it doesn’t matter. Just being fairly correct is already good. Right, how about the inner areas? Do you know any other dark creature?”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, the Snake King couldn’t help but shake its head as it answered, “I’ll be unfair to the Young Master, but I don’t know much about the central area. It is covered with a white protective cover all the time. That white light is very lethal to us, so we simply don’t go there.”

Zhao Hai gently knit his brows. He didn’t think that the Underworld would have such a place. But he still nodded and said, “Alright, you can go back. Cultivate well. If you need anything just tell me.” The Snake King nodded before Zhao Hai sent it out.

After sending the Snake King back, Zhao Hai returned to the villa and looked at the map once more. In the end, he decided to deal with the territory beside the soul snakes. This territory was ruled by pig-shaped magic beasts named steel pigs. Their strongest member had strength fairly similar to the Snake King. Not only was the Pig King powerful, it was also defensively better compared to the Snake King. It was a fellow that was difficult to deal with.

It can be said that Zhao Hai spent too long inside the soul snake area. This was because he was looking for traces of variant snakes. Now that he knew about the function of the bone plants, Zhao Hai prepared to go straight to the strongest beings this time!

Chapter 1035: Terrifying Five-Colored Light Wall

Zhao Hai’s operation went very smoothly. He used the Space’s map to find those magic beasts and then went and took them to the Space. It didn’t take a long time before he was done capturing them all.

Ten King-level magic beasts. Although they added strength to Zhao Hai, he didn’t plan to make use of them. He returned them to their territories in order to make them rule the Dark Creatures. This way, the Dark Creatures wouldn’t disturb him.

Zhao Hai subdued these beasts for two things; first, he wanted to collect soul bones, and second, he wanted the Dark Creatures to behave. If the Dark Creatures suddenly act up when Zhao Hai goes to war with the Dark Temple, then that would be very annoying. Because of this, Zhao Hai chose to subdue those magic beasts now.

Now that these magic beasts had been subdued, Zhao Hai moved on to his next plan, exploring the central area of the Dark Beast Domain. He wanted to see the white protective layer that the Snake King talked about.

However, Zhao Hai didn’t immediately go to the central region after subduing the ten king-level beasts. He had plenty of time, there was no need to be anxious.

Zhao Hai returned to the Space and rested for a few days. Zhao Hai was clear, if those with the Snake King’s strength weren’t able to enter the central region, then that was enough to explain its danger. Because of this, Zhao Hai planned to rest well in order to reach an optimum condition before he makes his move.

Zhao Hai rested for five days. In the past few days, Zhao Hai didn’t have little harvest. He gained a lot, and this was in terms of soul bones.

After being informed about the formation of soul bones, Cai’er immediately performed experiments on magic beasts. She tried magic beasts from every Space. In any case, there were a lot of bone plants. Therefore, there was no need to save up on materials.

The result left Cai’er satisfied. This bone plant’s main function seems to be forming soul bones. No matter what magic beasts ate it, they would drop soul bones whenever they died. However, which kind of bone was left behind was still random.

In addition to this result, determining the size of the soul bone produced had also been discovered. The size of the soul bones had something to do with the amount of bone plants a certain magic beast ate. If a magic beast only ate one leaf, then its soul bone would just be as large as a person’s tooth. If it ate a whole plant, then their bones would be as large as the weapons used by the Gibbon Brothers. The more bone plants they ate, the bigger the soul bone would be.

Cai’er first performed this experiment with Argali. After eating 20 bone plants, an Argali would die. Then after perishing, the Argali would leave behind soul bones. Moreover, after eating a bone plant, as long as they don’t reach the maximum amount, the Argali would be able to live normally. They didn’t have any difference compared to the other Argali.

Since time was short, Cai’er’s experiments could only have these results. However, this information was still very useful for Zhao Hai.

They were now aware that bone plants allowed the production of soul bones. But aside from this, they weren’t able to find out about anything else. It looks like, for now, the bone plant’s function was just to make soul bones.

But Zhao Hai had a certain premonition, both bone plants and soul bones would be very important in the future. Because of this, Zhao Hai placed great attention to these two things.

After resting inside the Space for five days, Zhao Hai finally decided to head towards the central area to take a look. Although the Snake King said that the central area was dangerous, Zhao Hai still wanted to take a look no matter what. The Underworld would be his territory in the future, leaving behind such an unknown place unexplored would not be great.

This time, Zhao Hai didn’t dare to lower his guard. After he passed through the Snake King’s domain, he went straight towards the central region. Naturally, the Snake King was right beside Zhao Hai.

From the Snake King’s domain, the two flew for another three hours before Zhao Hai felt that his spiritual force could no longer go forward. Zhao Hai couldn’t help but be alert, he knew that he must be close.

The Snake King stopped, then it turned its head to Zhao Hai and said, “Young Master, I can only accompany you up to here. I would be attacked if I proceed.”

Zhao Hai nodded. He also knew that he wouldn’t be able to ask the Snake King for help. The Snake King gave Zhao Hai a salute before it turned around and left.

Zhao Hai slowly flew forward, his heart was somewhat anxious. After flying for about ten minutes, Zhao Hai suddenly discovered the dark mist slowly turning faint!

Zhao Hai gawked. He spent a lot of days inside the Underworld, and all through that time he had been inside the Dark Mist, so he was very familiar with it. Now, the dark mist suddenly started to thin out, he began to feel strange.

Zhao Hai stopped and paid attention to the surroundings. The dark mist had turned faint, moreover, a white light began to shine out. It seems like the white light scattered the dark mist.

Zhao Hai examined himself and found that the white light seems to not affect him. He tried to fly forward, only to see that the white light was becoming brighter and brighter while the dark mist turned more and more faint. Zhao Hai flew for over 20 minutes before the Dark Mist completely vanished. What was in front of Zhao Hai was a wall of gentle white light.

Zhao Hai was somewhat puzzled. He was made aware of this white light by the Snake King. According to the Snake King, this white light should be dangerous. However, Zhao Hai couldn’t feel any danger coming from it. Conversely, the white light gave Zhao Hai an unending supply of energy. It was actually very comfortable.

At this time, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but rub his temples. He can feel that dark energy was absent from the light wall. Instead of dark energy, Zhao Hai can feel the presence of the five elements. It can be said that the light wall was made out of the five elements.

This stoked Zhao Hai’s curiosity. Almost all of the energy in the Underworld was dark energy. But on this light wall, Zhao Hai could actually feel the five elements. What was going on?

Although he didn’t understand, Zhao Hai decided to fly forward. In any case, he couldn’t feel a threat coming from the light wall.

As Zhao Hai flew forward, he discovered that although the light wall wasn’t far, it wasn’t close either. It took Zhao Hai a bit more than a half an hour before reaching the light wall.

Upon reaching the wall, Zhao Hai found out that the wall wasn’t all white. Five colors constantly flashed from time to time, they were very bright.

Zhao Hai crystallized his hand before he plunged his fingertips towards the wall. Just as his fingers touched the wall, a huge twisting force suddenly came out from the wall. It was as though a large hand had come out to pull Zhao Hai in.

Zhao Hai immediately took his hand back. His hand was still crystallized, but Zhao Hai knew that if it wasn’t, then his fingers would’ve already been sucked in.

Zhao Hai was clear about the strength of his crystal body. But even so, Zhao Hai could still feel the twisting from the light wall. This was an evidence of how dangerous the wall was.

Upon the thought of this, Zhao Hai took out a high-grade steel blade from the Space. This blade was a superior weapon produced by the Dwarves.

Zhao Hai proceeded to stab the steel blade towards the wall of light. As soon as the blade came in contact with the wall, Zhao Hai felt the twisting force once more, but the force quickly disappeared.

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but stare, was this twisting force just a fluke? At this thought, Zhao Hai took the steel blade back before preparing to insert it back into the light wall.

However, just as Zhao Hai pulled the steel blade out, he discovered that something was wrong. The part of the blade that was inserted into the wall had disappeared. Moreover, the cross-section was very smooth, as though it has been cut by an extremely sharp instrument.

When he saw the blade’s state, Zhao Hai’s expression changed before he forced a smile, “Interesting, even this steel blade has been cut. This wall isn’t normal.”

Zhao Hai threw the blade into the light wall. The blade just vanished into the wall, it was like when a water drop disappears into the big sea. There wasn’t even a hint of disturbance on the wall’s surface.

Although the light wall didn’t transmit any sound, Zhao Hai knew that the blade had been twisted into nothingness by the light wall. Zhao Hai stopped in front of the wall and looked at the flashing multicolored light. After a while, he couldn’t help but smile bitterly.

This light wall was sending out a gentle light, giving people a sacred feeling. Moreover, the attractiveness of the five colors was extraordinary. However, who knew that beyond this wall was a twisting force that would strangle everything. If an ordinary human goes through this wall, then even bones wouldn’t be left behind.

However, this made Zha Hai even more curious. He felt that this light wall didn’t appear naturally. It was surely made as a defensive measure by someone. Moreover, this defensive formation seems to be much stronger compared to what Zhao Hai had seen before.

Zhao Hai felt even more curious about what was inside this wall. It was impossible for it to appear for no reason. This was guarding something, or sealing something inside.

The more Zhao Hai thought about, the more curious he was. He waved his hand and took his blood ghost staff out. Then he turned the staff into a protective sphere. After also crystallizing his entire body, Zhao Hai flew towards the wall.

As the blood ghost staff entered the light wall, Zhao Hai immediately felt the twisting force. Its strength was very huge, making the blood sphere shiver. It might even break at any time.

Zhao Hai stood firmly inside the blood sphere as he continued to fly forward. The blood sphere’s shaking got more and more violent, however, it still held on without no sign of bursting.

Zhao Hai didn’t dare to be careless, as he controlled the blood sphere, he made a mental message, “Cai’er, pay attention to the monitor. See whether I am progressing or just moving in circles.”

Cai’er’s voice was quickly heard, “Young Master, rest assured, you aren’t going in a circle. You’ve been going in a straight line.”

Zhao Hai nodded before he stimulated the blood sphere to speed up. He wanted to go through the light wall as soon as possible, but he couldn’t do anything to the twisting force.

Even so, Zhao Hai didn’t stop. He advanced bit by bit, Zhao Hai didn’t care that he was going slowly, it was good as long as he was moving.

One hour passed, two hours, three hours,…. Ten hours passed by. Zhao Hai’s head began to perspire. He didn’t think that it would take this long to cross the light wall. He felt that his mental strength wouldn’t be able to keep up. Zhao Hai knew that if his spiritual strength was exhausted, then the blood sphere would stop moving. Even if the blood sphere didn’t collapse, without the support of his spiritual force, Zhao Hai wouldn’t be able to proceed. When that time comes, who knows what would happen.

Because of this, Zhao Hai insisted on going through this light wall. He wanted to take a look at what’s inside the wall. He wanted to know the reason why there was a strong magic formation here.

After another hour, just as Zhao Hai felt that he wouldn’t be able to go on, he suddenly felt that a portion of the blood sphere had a reduced pressure from the twisting force. Zhao Hai stared, his gaze shook, he knew that he was about to come out of the light wall. As soon as he thought about this, Zhao Hai immediately pushed the blood sphere further. The force of the wall became weaker and weaker. Then after five minutes, Zhao Hai finally went through the light wall. He couldn’t feel the twisting force anymore.

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but let out a long breath as he wiped the sweat off of his face. Then he looked at the place through the blood sphere. Inside the light wall wasn’t a huge place. On top of the area was a light source giving off gentle light. The space was only about 100 square meters, surrounding it was the light wall. In the middle of this place was a small tree. The tree was a little more than a meter high. There were several long roots branching out from this tree. Its leaves were scattered, it seems like the tree didn’t have any proper nourishment.

Zhao Hai discovered people gathering around this tree. However, the existence of these people was strange. Some looked like Beastmen, some looked like Dwarves, some were like Elves, there were some golems, and those who looked like the Thunder Clan, Winged Pegasus, Barbarians. At the same time, there were people who were pitch black, blacker than a black person. Purple people were present as well. In any case, there were races that Zhao Hai could identify and some that he couldn’t. What made Zhao Hai even more curious was the fact that there was a giant among these people. This giant was very tall, its head as high as Zhao Hai’s entire body. Zhao Hai suddenly felt that this giant looked very familiar. Then his eyes quickly lit up, he knew that this giant was the same giant as the huge skeletons that he was collecting before. They looked fairly the same.

Zhao Hai counted and there seems to be about a hundred individuals inside this place. These people were cross legged and had their eyes closed. However, Zhao Hai knew that these people were already dead, judging by the fact that they had no life force.

Chapter 1036: Do You Desire Immortality?

A place of about 100 square meters being illuminated by colorful lights would look attractive to any person. However, such a place had a hundred dead people surrounding a half dead tree. This made it look strange instead.

Zhao Hai stayed in place while in mid-air. He slowly received his blood ghost staff. However, he kept his crystallization, afraid of any potential danger. Only after finding that there weren’t any threats would he begin to withdraw his crystal form.

After seeing that there was still no danger, Zhao Hai felt relieved. Then he turned his crystallization off. He began to closely inspect this small space. In this place, besides the small tree, the other places were occupied by those 100 people. Other than these things, nothing else was found.

Zhao Hai began to descend to the ground to look at the 100 individuals. These people were from all kinds of races. The biggest one was the giant that Zhao Hai had seen before while the smallest one was at a size of a fairy. This fairy had fairly transparent skin, showing the blood vessels and the muscles within. The other parts were as black as the darkest coal.

These people were dead, their bodies lacked the presence of life, their souls had long been dissipated. Even if Zhao Hai used his dark magic, it would be impossible for him to turn them into Undead.

However, Zhao Hai didn’t want to underestimate them. This was because Zhao Hai saw that their bodies didn’t rot. And this wasn’t because of the environment. In fact, the environment here was the same as the Ark Continent, aside from the air being a bit dry, nothing else was different.

The reason why these corpses were still in perfect condition was because these people were all peak Experts. At the very least, they were stronger than the current Zhao Hai. Since they were too strong, their bodies were preserved despite dying. It can be said that they were on the boundary of being immortal.

Immortal doesn’t mean everlasting, it meant that the body of a person had reached a very high degree of cultivation to the point where it wouldn’t be corrupted upon death.

It was clearly obvious that these 100 individuals had reached a point of immortality. But Zhao Hai knew that the Underworld, or even the Divine Realm’s experts wouldn’t achieve such a degree. Only the Cultivation Realm might have these kinds of experts. In other words, these 100 people could very well be from the Cultivation Realm.

The clothing style of these people were very unusual as well, and each of them were different. It can be seen that their clothing represented their race’s identity. At the same time, Zhao Hai can see that their clothes were made out of high-quality materials. Who knows how long it has been since these people had died, but their clothes were still as good as new. This was evidence enough of how advanced the fabric was.

Gently touching the clothes would make it clear that the material used were tenacious and strong. In addition to the incomparably powerful multicolored light wall, it confirmed Zhao Hai’s guess. These people were most likely from the Cultivation Realm. Whether they were trapped here or had sealed themselves in was still hard to say.

Zhao Hai looked all around and saw that there wasn’t anything else. Zhao Hai hesitated for a moment before he carefully flew towards the small tree.

It was a type of tree that Zhao Hai had never seen before. Its leaves were quite fat, its bark was very smooth. It looked like any other small tree, but Zhao Hai can affirm that this was not an ordinary tree.

Looks couldn’t give enough information, so Zhao Hai couldn’t stop himself from touching the tree with his hand. Just as his hand came in contact with the tree, the tree suddenly emitted a five colored light towards Zhao Hai’s face. Zhao Hai’s eyes shook before he stood straight and didn’t move. At the same time, his eyes seem to lose their sheen. It was as though Zhao Hai had lost his soul.

In the next instant, Zhao Hai discovered that he was inside a strange place. Mist fluttered everywhere. However, this wasn’t the same dark mist of the Underworld. This mist gave one a comfortable natural feeling.

Zhao Hai looked around in confusion. At this time, the mist retreated as a person appeared in front of him. The man wore a long gown and was quite handsome. On his face was a devilish smile while under his feet was a double-edged sword. His hair was tied up in a ponytail, making him look carefree.

This person looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Do you desire Immortality?”

Zhao Hai stared as he digested the words of this person. From this person’s appearance, he’s most likely to be a cultivator, moreover his level doesn’t seem to be low. Why did he appear here? And why did he suddenly utter such words?

However, Zhao Hai took a deep breath before he answered, “Yes!”

The person looked at Zhao Hai and laughed, “In this universe, almost all people desire immortality. However, one should know that immortality goes against the will of the heavens. It is stealing life from the heavens. Everyone who desires immortality would have to do this alone. Will you?”

Zhao Hai knit his brows. Although he was an indifferent person, he wasn’t completely ruthless. It was impossible for him to sacrifice Laura and the others just for the sake of immortality. Because of this, Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “I’m unable to do this.”

The person seemed to be stunned at Zhao Hai’s reply. Then he disappeared into thin air. Along with the disappearance of the man was the appearance of a kindly dressed monk. When the monk appeared, he put his hands together before smiling at Zhao Hai, “Greetings, young benefactor.”

Zhao Hai stared, he didn’t understand why this monk appeared. However, he also put his hands together and said, “Greetings, Master.”

When the monk saw Zhao Hai’s conduct, his smile couldn’t help but deepen. He immediately replied, “Benefactor has answered well. In this world, there are many paths in order to achieve immortality. With Buddhism, you will receive the grand dao.”

Zhao Hai replied, “These paths, Master, please enlighten me.”

The Monk said, “All living things aim for immortality, but this is a selfish aim. Why not follow the teachings of Buddha. Receive happiness, and enter the everlasting!”

Zhao Hai gave a faint smile as he said, “Those who are not fish would never know the happiness of one. The Buddha has transcended humanity, so how could he know our pains? I do good deeds, but I’m not a monk nor do I worship to Buddha. In such case, won’t I be a living Buddha? If I am wicked, dress myself in gold, burn books, and break wooden fish, then wouldn’t I be a great Demon?”[1]

When the Monk heard this, he began to vanish, replacing him was a person with a scholarly appearance. In this person’s hand was a book, he looked at Zhao Hai and smiled, “Those who are not fish will never know a fish’s happiness. Good, good. Those who can save the world are only saints and sages. Are you willing to follow the saint’s path with me in order to achieve immortality?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Only commoners can save the people of the world. Where do saints and sages come from? They are also ordinary people!”

The Scholar vanished, in his place was an Old Daoist. The Old Daoist had snow white hair, beard and eyebrows. In his hand was a bone dust pouch. He Old Daoist looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Little friend is persevering and wise. You are a good candidate for spiritual cultivation. Little friend, are you willing to explore nature with me? We will take the mountains and the rivers as our teachers, treat the heavens as our friend. To pursue the path to immortality together!”

Zhao Hai actually chuckled as he replied, “What is the grand dao? The grand dao is the dao of the heavens, a path of humanity, and a bitter life to some people. But if I become immortal alone, then what is the point? People can be happy without being immortal, is that part of the dao? The Dao is life, the heavens are the dao. The dao is my heart and my heart is the dao!”

The Old Daoist vanished. At this time a giant appeared in front of Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai had seen this giant before. It was the dead giant back in that small place. When the giant appeared, he gave Zhao Hai a salute before he said, “This one has met Little Friend. This one is Scattered Spirit of the Spirit Giant race.”

Zhao Hai stared, then he returned the greeting, “This one is Zhao Hai.”

Scattered Spirit looked at Zhao Hai and said, “I have seen Little Friend Zhao Hai. My Spirit Giant race is one of the races that coexisted along with the other 99 from the Spirit Realm. Our clan, along with the others, don’t vie for supremacy nor do we indulge in conquest. The 100 races lived harmoniously. But one day, a severely wounded Human arrived at our Spirit Realm. The 100 clans did our best in order to rescue and befriend him. However, nobody expected that Human to call other Humans in order to attack our realm. They destroyed our civilization. In the end, we could only call for 100 brave warriors for one last struggle. We created a space to save and protect our sacred relic, the Hundred Spirit Tree, up until a destined friend arrives. Little Friend Zhao Hai, you are that destined friend. Little Friend, please take the Hundred Spirit Tree away from this place. Let it recover. If you do, then we will be deeply grateful to you.”

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but stare. He looked at Scattered Spirit and said, “You made this space? Didn’t you die, how are you able to speak to me?”

Scattered Spirit replied, “Little Friend doesn’t need to be confused. Me and the other 99 sent our spiritual force to the Hundred Spirit Tree before we died. Upon meeting you, our spirits would start to dissipate. My current appearance is the amalgamation of all our spiritual forces.”

Zhao Hai nodded, he looked at Scattered Spirit and said, “Did you also arrange the magic formation? How can I remove it?”

Scattered Spirit replied, “This formation was arranged by the hundred clans. It is named Divine Soul Five Element Killing Formation. It cuts both yin and yang energy of the five elements. Breaking this formation is easy, as long as you throw our corpses towards the formation, then the formation would dissipate. You can also obtain the formation itself.”

Zhao Hai stared as he listened to Scattered Spirit. At this time, Scattered Spirit gave Zhao Hai a last salute before saying, “Little Friend, my divine soul is starting to vanish. I ask Little Friend to take good care of the Hundred Spirit Tree, our 100 clans would forever be grateful to you.” After he said that Scattered Spirit became more and more pale before he completely vanished.

* * *

I’m not sure about this. I didn’t manage to find any relevant resources to translate this segment.

Chapter 1037: Insane Level Ups

After Scattered Spirit vanished, Zhao Hai discovered that he had returned to the small tree. HIs hand was on the tree, the same action that he had earlier.

Zhao Hai stared, he can affirm that he wasn’t dreaming. He was just sent to another place and this place was actually his own sea of knowledge.[1]

Zhao Hai frowned. He was sure that he had just talked with Scattered Spirit. But that happened not in another place, but instead inside his own mind.

But what made Zhao Hai confused were the people who appeared before Scattered Spirit. What’s the purpose of the Immortal, Monk, Scholar, and Old Daoist?

Although he was left with questions, Zhao Hai recalled Scattered Spirit’s wish. Inside this formation called the Divine Soul Five Element Killing Formation was a tree he was meant to protect.

Zhao Hai had no problems agreeing to Scattered Spirit’s request. This was a tree species that Zhao Hai had not seen before, and the Space would definitely take it in. Moving the tree to the Space would be beneficial to it, and it would also give the Space some experience.

Zhao Hai turned his head to look at the corpses of the 100 individuals. Scattered Spirit said that throwing these corpses towards the Divine Soul Five Element Killing Formation would turn it off. Moreover, Zhao Hai could also obtain the formation itself. However, Zhao Hai didn’t want to do this.

Zhao Hai heard Scattered Spirit say that all of them used their final strength to establish the formation in order to protect the Hundred Spirit Tree. So even if Zhao Hai broke the formation and obtained its method of activation, it was still impossible for Zhao Hai to use it. He alone wasn’t enough to establish the formation.

Throwing these corpses to disintegrate inside the formation wasn’t something that Zhao Hai could bear to do. He was a Dark Mage, but he would only be impolite to the corpses of his enemies and turn them into Undead. As for people on his own side, he would only turn them into Undead if necessary, otherwise he would give them the greatest respect.

Scattered Spirit and the others weren’t people on his own side, but they were surely not his enemy. For Zhao Hai to throw their corpses towards the killing formation was something that Zhao Hai cannot do.

Although he doesn’t know another way to break the formation, Zhao Hai can still leave using the Space. Zhao Hai plans to leave using the Space along with the 100 corpses. Then he would find a good place to bury them in.

There was another reason why Zhao Hai chose to bury the bodies of the 100 people from the Spirit World. This was because these people were all experts. All of them deserved to rest with dignity. And from Scattered Spirit’s words, what happened to them was caused by the Human Race. When he thought about this, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but feel guilty.

Zhao Hai sighed, then he waved his hand to take all of the corpses. After that, Zhao Hai inspected the small tree. His spiritual force searched underground in order to find the tip of the tree’s roots. This way, it would be easier for it to be moved to the Space.

Scattered Spirit said that this tree was their most sacred artifact, the Hundred Spirit tree. Upon facing such a treasure, Zhao Hai didn’t dare to be negligent. Because of this, he was very careful in searching for the tree’s roots.

However, Zhao Hai didn’t expect the tree to have such strong roots. Moreover, the roots of the tree spanned the entire 100 square meter area. At the same time, the main root of the tree stretched up to 1 kilometer into the ground.

A meter high tree actually had a kilometer long root? This caused Zhao Hai to be startled.

Zhao Hai opened a spatial rift using all of his strength. The huge spatial rift appeared on top of Zhao Hai’s head.

Zhao Hai used his finger to lead the spatial rift’s dimensions towards the light wall. It must be said that Zhao Hai was thankful for the existence of the Divine Five Element Killing Formation. The formation kept the roots of the tree contained. Without the formation, who knows how large the tree root’s span would be. If that happened, Zhao Hai would have to spend more effort in moving the tree.

Zhao Hai also discovered that the Five Elements inside this small space was completely isolated from the Underworld. And unlike the Underworld, the soil in this place was common dirt. Any presence of blood also couldn’t be found. It looked like this place wasn’t in the Underworld at all.

Zhao Hai didn’t dwell too much on this as he directed the spatial rift to push downwards. And since the tree didn’t expand too much aboveground, the spatial rift had a smooth path downward. It proceeded downwards until it had fully swallowed the Hundred Spirit Tree.

When the Hundred Spirit Tree was finally absorbed, Zhao Hai decided to place it by the Space’s villa. As the Hundred Spirit Tree was sent in, the Space immediately issued a prompt, “High-grade plant discovered. Level required to scan is too high, Host currently has no permission to view data. Since host has acquired a high-grade plant, the Space has been upgraded to level 110. Host can now purchase 10 low-ranked cultivation backgrounds as well as 20 common backgrounds. Hoping for the Host to continue your hard work.”

This caused Zhao Hai to stare, the Hundred Spirit Tree was truly astonishing. Not only could Zhao Hai not view its properties, it even made the Space level up 8 times, making it level 110. This was truly a great harvest.

However, this wasn’t the end. After Zhao Hai planted the Hundred Spirit Tree and watered it with the space’s water, the tree began to grow at a rate visible to the naked eye. It didn’t take long before the tree’s root grew to a kilometer deep. Then Zhao Hai began to feel the energy inside the Space quickly flowing towards the tree’s trunk, making the Hundred Spirit Tree the center of an energy whirlpool. As the energy of the Space was vigorously absorbed, the tree began to grow bigger and bigger. In the end, the Hundred Spirit Tree reached an astonishing height of a kilometer, surpassing the Tree of Life’s record height by about 100 meters. The tree gave shade to the villa, giving it a quaint atmosphere.

At this time, the tree stopped its growth and cut off its absorption of the Space’s energy. And then it began to release some energy to the Space for some time before it stopped.

Zhao Hai discovered that the energy released by the Hundred Spirit Tree gave the Space more vitality. Zhao Hai was able to faintly feel the plants in the Space cheering.

At this time, Laura and the others went outside of the vila. All of them were shocked upon seeing the huge Hundred Spirit Tree.

Zhao Hai also began to discover that 100 flowers had appeared on the Hundred Spirit Tree. These 100 flowers looked different from each other. Some were single flowers, while some came in clumps. However, each flower had a size of about a meter, they were very beautiful.

Zhao Hai stood below the tree, feeling the delicate fragrance that it gave out from time to time. This fragrance was quite special. Initially, it wasn’t very thick, feeling quite pale. But after some time, it gave people a plain and sincere feeling, it seems as though it refreshed one’s soul.

Laura and the others couldn’t help but lift their noses up. Then Megan said, “It’s fragrant, it smells very good. Big Brother Hai, was this that half-dead tree? Did you use magic? Or accelerated time?”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “I didn’t use magic or anything else. It’s a mystery why it grew to this height.”

Laura smiled and said, “I’ve always wanted to plant a huge tree next to the villa. With this tree, everything looks perfect.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “This is the Hundred Spirit Tree. Those people surrounding the tree are from the Hundred Spirit Clan. It’s possible that they are from the Cultivation Realm. They were attacked by the Humans. Because of this, they escaped with the tree to the Underworld. With the tree being their sacred relic, they surrounded it with the killing formation. After I rushed through the light wall, the people from the Hundred Spirit Clan asked me to take care of their tree. Because of this, I decided to plant the tree inside the Space.”

Laura looked confused at what Zhao Hai said, so she asked, “Brother Hai, how did you know about all of these?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Those 100 people sent their final spiritual force into the Hundred Spirit Tree. They directly sent a message to me when I touched the tree.”

Laura replied, “Didn’t you just rub the tree? How can you obtain this information?”

Zhao Hai stared, “Rub that tree? Haven’t I been out for some time?”

Laura shook her head and said, “No, we just saw you rub the tree. It wasn’t that long.”

Zhao Hai began to understand the problem. He felt that it he took a long time inside that dream-like world. But in fact, it only took a very short time.

After he thought about this, Zhao Hai nodded and said, “I just felt like time passed longer than what it should have taken. Alright, we’re done here. Let’s continue exploring the Underworld. Make sure to tell the Snake King and the others to refrain from getting close to the killing formation, or else they would be smashed to pieces.”

Laura nodded and said, “Alright, we’ll relay this matter to the Snake King and the others. Brother Hai, that Divine Five Element Killing Formation is too dangerous. Don’t go into such danger in the future, you’ll worry us to death.’

Zhao Hai looked at Laura and then smiled, “Alright, you can rest assured. After all, it was a risk worth taking. Also, don’t forget that I have my staff and my crystal form. I’m not that easy to damage.”

Laura knew that urging Zhao Hai further would prove useless. Moreover, this risk was truly worth it. If Zhao Hai didn’t do this from time to time, then the Space wouldn’t’ develop. Therefore, she decided to just nod and say nothing else.

* * *

It’s 识海(Shì hǎi) or sea of knowledge. This is the first time this appeared.

Chapter 1038: Heaven Defying Hundred Spirit Tree

Zhao Hai’s figure flashsed out of the Space as he returned to the Underworld. He was planning to head towards the Snake King’s territory.

However, Zhao Hai suddenly discovered that he had arrived in his sea of knowledge once more. Last time, he was made aware of this because of the dreamy mist surrounding it, and by the fact that it didn’t look like any other place.

While Zhao Hai was puzzled, Scattered Spirit suddenly appeared in front of him. In their previous meeting, Scattered Spirit was unemotional. But this time, Scattered Spirit had a smile on his face. He looked at Zhao Hai before he bowed and greeted, “Little Friend Zhao Hai.”

Zhao Hai stared, he looked at Scattered Spirit and said, “Scattered Spirit? Is that you? You didn’t dissipate?”

Scattered Spirit smiled faintly and said, “Correct. Little Friend Zhao Hai is truly a good man.”

Zhao Hai knit his brows, “Scattered Soul, what do you mean? Are you saying that you don’t dissipate? Are you going to stay here?”

Scattered Spirit felt that Zhao Hai was starting to get annoyed, so he immediately said, “My friend, you misunderstand. The reason why I appeared is because you have fulfilled the requirements of the Hundred Spirits Clan.”

Zhao Hai still couldn’t understand, “What do you mean? Scattered Spirit, explain it to me clearly.”

Scattered Spirit smiled faintly and replied, “My friend, don’t worry. What you saw last time is truly my remnant soul. However, my task is still not complete. Before seeing me, you saw a Demon Path Practitioner, a Buddhist Monk, a Confusian Scholar, and a Dao Sect Practitioner. Those are tests. I told you last time that we rescued a Human who brought other Humans to slaughter our clan. In order for us to establish trust, we needed to make a test.”

After hearing this, Zhao Hai’s expression changed, “So in other words, if I agreed to any of those Cultivators, I would have died?”

Scattered Spirit replied, “Cultivator? What are those? I don’t understand. Those people are all Immortal Practitioners. But you don’t have to worry. Even if you agreed to any of them, you would not die. You would just be expelled from the formation since it would be impossible for you to handle our request.”

Zhao Hai looked at Scattered Soul and said, “Is it really that simple?”

Scattered Spirit smiled, “Naturally, it’s impossible for it to be that easy. If you followed what I said and threw our bodies into the Divine Five Element Killing Formation, then not only could you dissipate the formation, you would also fail to obtain it. Instead, you would detonate the formation, burning everything inside.”

Zhao Hai knit his brows, “So is there another way to break it?”

Scattered Spirit smiled and said, “There’s another way to break the formation. The formation would only dissipate when our requests have been accomplished. Little friend, you should know that since you met us, then there’s no need for you to break the formation in order to escape that place. If you threw our corpses into the formation, then this meant that you are a person with no compassion. So how could we possibly hand over our Hundred Spirit Tree to a person like that?”

Zhao Hai began to understand. The Hundred Spirit Clan died in order to protect the Hundred Spirit Tree. This showed how important the tree was for them. So how could they have a piece of mind if they just hand it over to anyone.

Scattered Spirit looked at Zhao Hai’s expression as he smiled faintly and said, “It seems like you understand why we did all of that. My Hundred Spirit Clan surely won’t make Little Friend lose out on this matter. Now that the Divine Five Element formation is about to be broken, by remnant soul would no longer be able to hold out for long. However, Little Friend can rest assured, you don’t need to destroy our corpses nor the Hundred Spirit Tree in order to obtain the formation. The formation will be absorbed inside your body and reside outside your sea of knowledge. No matter what kind of spiritual attack, the formation would block them all. Moreover, from now on, the formation would be under your control. Even if you destroy the Hundred Spirit Tree, the formation wouldn’t retaliate against you. This is my Hundred Spirit Clan’s gift to you. I ask you to accept it.”

Zhao Hai gawked. He didn’t expect to gain another good thing. It was actually a defensive measure. Moreover, it protected his sea of knowledge.

Scattered Spirit continued, “My friend, there’s no need to take revenge for the Hundred Spirit Clan. The Universe is a complex being, and being extinguished is part of nature’s laws. The Humans eliminating our Hundred Spirit Clan goes according to nature’s laws. Actually, this Hundred Spirit Tree is actually not the one from our Hundred Spirit Clan. When the Humans destroyed the Hundred Spirit Tree, they only destroyed the main tree. They were unaware of the seedling growing under the tree. This is enough to prove that the Universe wanted the tree to survive. Therefore, Little Friend, please take good care of the tree. These trees existed in the Spirit World long before the Hundred Spirit Clan existed. And even after 1 million years of research, we still had yet to unlock the full capabilities of the tree. Now, I will relay the abilities of the Hundred Spirit Tree to Little Friend.”

After he said that, Scattered Spirit emitted a five colored light as he drilled into Zhao Hai’s body. Before long, Zhao Hai was bombarded with information. However, even before Zhao Hai managed to digest it all, he noticed that Scattered Spirit had appeared once more, but now his body was fainter than before. While Zhao Hai was stunned, Scattered Spirit said, “Little Friend, we have waited for a long time. Now that the Hundred Spirit Clan has been eliminated from this universe, we hope that you can take care of the Hundred Spirit Tree. Little Friend, this will be my last farewell.”

After he said that, Scattered Spirit faded for the last time. Then another Hundred Spirit Clan member appeared in his place. This person gave Zhao Hai a bow before he disappeared and was replaced by another person. In the end all 100 members of the Hundred Spirit Clan had given Zhao Hai their respects. Then after that, Zhao Hai saw nothing else.

Zhao Hai knew that this was the Hundred Spirit Clan expressing their gratefulness towards him. Zhao Hai wasn’t impolite and returned each salute given to him. After that, Zhao Hai felt his sea of knowledge being surrounded by a five-colored light, forming four light walls that firmly protected what was inside.

Zhao Hai used his spiritual force to search, and as he did that, he heard the Space’s prompt, “Five element protective light wall detected. Extracting function and integrating it to the Space. The Space’s defenses have increased. Without the host’s permission, anybody who dared to enter a spatial rift to the Space would be strangled to death by the five element light wall. Any spiritual force with evil intention who attacks the host would also be strangled by the five element wall.”

At the same time, Zhao Hai could also feel control over the five element light wall. He began to feel relief. He didn’t expect to receive the light wall at this time. And since it protected his sea of knowledge, those who plan to attack him using spiritual force would face a violent retaliation.

After gaining control of the five element light wall, Zhao Hai began to examine the information that Scattered Spirit gave him. Zhao Hai used his spiritual force to sweep his sea of knowledge before that clump of information came out.

This knowledge included matters about the Hundred Spirit Tree as well as the method to arrange and dismantle the Divine Five Element Killing Formation.

The Hundred Spirit Clan’s Hundred Spirit Tree was actually called Hundred Stars Tree. The tree would live for one hundred years before blooming for 100 days. If one was fast and harvested the tree’s parts after 100 days, then one would obtain great benefits The bark of the tree can be used as medicine in order to heal even fatal wounds. If it was used alongside other medicinal plants, then the effect would be strengthened.

Also, if one soaks a leaf of the tree in water and drank it, then their cultivation would be increased, their physique would be strengthened, and their spiritual force would recover much faster. It can be said that it was a very good spiritual force restoration medicine.

The most unusual thing about the Hundred Spirit Tree was the fact that flowers would bloom after one hundred years and would stay that way for 100 days. After 100 days, the flowers would begin to form fruits. Then the mature fruit would begin detaching themselves from the tree. The fruits would then begin to grow larger and larger. The largest fruit would turn into an island that was not less than 10 thousand square meters in surface area and not more than one million square kilometers. This small island would hover in the air and would have its own gravity. This island wouldn’t be able to detach from the land much further, but the island could be farmed and occupied. However, there wouldn’t be any minerals on this island.

As for the other 99 fruits, they could be turned into airships. This airship was actually a mix of a vessel, a planting area, and an energy source. No matter who it was, as long as they drop their blood on the fruit, then they would immediately turn into these airships. This ship would act like a small island with its own gravitational force. People could also live on its surface and even farm. The area of these ships wouldn’t go further than 10 thousand square meters, but this wasn’t a small area.

Moreover, this ship would provide energy to its owner. If its owner runs out of energy during combat, then the ship would provide some. If the ship was planted with high-ranked plants, then the energy supplied would be greater. If the ship wasn’t cultivated, then the energy it provides would be low.

During the war between the Humans and the Hundred Spirit Clan, the Hundred Spirit Tree’s fruits were turned into floating ships. This gave the Humans enormous losses. Because of this, the Humans sent out powerful experts in order to erase the Hundred Spirit Tree. Because the tree was destroyed, and the fact that the Hundred Spirit Clan was not that populous, it didn’t take long before the Spirit World was taken over by the Humans.

If nobody uses the Hundred Spirit Fruit, then the fruit would still last forever. This was because these fruits can absorb the energy of the universe in order to support its existence. The energy absorbed would also allow another Hundred Spirit Tree to grow. And when the tree grows up, it would release the same energy it borrowed back into the Universe. This would form a loop of interdependence between the universe and the tree.

As for the fruit that turned into an island, it was impossible to be owned by someone. This island would just float above the ground. However, if this island existed for a very long time, then it would ascend and become a planet. They would also have natural source transmission formations inside them. These formations form a direct link towards the place where the original Hundred Spirit Tree grew. In other words, as long as an island existed for a very long time, it can roam the universe as a planet. And with the transmission formation, the island could return to the planet where it originated.

Also, the small planet that the fruit turned into would be able to attract the energy of the Universe and then grow its own Hundred Spirit Tree. And this tree would return to the origin place of the planet.

After knowing these functions of the Hundred Spirit Tree, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but be shocked. He didn’t expect the Hundred Spirit Tree to be this heaven-defying. It can actually form islands and planets that have their own gravitational field. This was too inconceivable.

Zhao Hai could now understand why the Hundred Spirit Clan appointed the Hundred Spirit Tree as their sacred relic. In fact, any race that obtains this tree would no doubt make it their most precious treasure. This tree was just too heaven-defying.

Besides the Hundred Spirit Tree, there was also information about the Divine Five Element Killing Formation. This formation involved the five elements of the heavens and the earth. It can be said that no matter what type of energy, it could still be influenced by the formation, this includes spiritual force. There were rules to establishing this formation. The person who wanted to set it up would have to balance the power of the five elements. There must also be enough energy and spiritual force to power the formation. The reason why the Hundred Spirit Clan was able to establish this formation was because they had already sacrificed more than a million of their kin during tests. In the end, 100 people succeeded in establishing the formation. Those who failed were all consumed by the backlash.

On the other hand, dissolving the formation was actually very simple. To break the formation, one should meet the requirements set by the one who established the formation, just like what the Hundred Spirit Clan did. As long as you don’t destroy their bodies, not destroy the Hundred Spirit Tree, and then giving the tree some security, then the formation would break apart.

If Zhao Hai establishes the formation, then he could make his own requirements. For example, Zhao Hai can make a rule that as long as a person says the word ‘Hello’, then they would break the formation. It was that simple, using other methods would just get them killed. No matter what, accomplishing the requirements was the only way of breaking a Divine Five Element Killing Formation.

Chapter 1039: Five Element Killing Formation

The world has no certainties!

This was something that everyone who study magic formations knew. In fact, Zhao Hai believes that this sentence was also true for those who study magic formations in the Cultivation Realm.

This statement was also true regarding the Divine Five Element Killing Formation. It was the strongest formation that Zhao Hai had seen. It could strangle both yin and yang of the five elements. It could also retaliate against spiritual attacks. One might even say that it was almost perfect.

However, such near perfection still had to make way for an out. Otherwise, the formation wouldn’t have been successfully established.

In fact, for those who set the Five Element Killing formation, this out was the requirement that one needs to accomplish. As for those who wanted to try other methods in order to break the formation, it was almost impossible for them to succeed.

This was the unique point of the Five Element Killing formation. As for the other formations, as long as you find a weakness to break them, then they could do it. But this wouldn’t work on the Five Element Formation. If one couldn’t accomplish the requirements of the formation, then one wouldn’t be able to break it.

Strictly speaking, the Five Element Killing Formation couldn’t be identified into a type of formation. Instead, it can be said that it was a mix between a formation and a form of thought. It didn’t need formation flags nor formation disks, instead it needed the thoughts of those who set it up. Because of this, the formation couldn’t be broken using conventional methods.

And now, Zhao Hai’s sea of knowledge was surrounded by the five element light wall. Any spiritual force that had malicious intent towards Zhao Hai would be attacked by the light wall. And there was only one way to break this light wall, it was either by Zhao Hai dissipating it by himself, or if the Hundred Spirit Tree was removed from the Space.

Nobody else can achieve these requirements other than Zhao Hai. Therefore, Zhao Hai wasn’t worried about the formation in his sea of knowledge being broken.

However, Zhao Hai will certainly make good use of the Five Element Killing formation. In fact, the Space had already extracted the properties of the formation and then unified it with Zhao Hai’s staff. In other words, Zhao Hai can place his own Five Element Killing Formation. But this time, the formation that Zhao Hai could arrange was in no way comparable to the one arranged by the Hundred Spirit Clan.

There’s also another characteristic to the Five Element Killing Formation, its height went according to the strength of the people establishing it. And with Zhao Hai’s present strength, he certainly wouldn’t be able to match the Divine Five Element Killing Formation made by the Hundred Spirit Clan. After all, the Divine Five Element Killing Formation was set up by 100 high-ranked Immortals from the Hundred Spirit Clan.

Zhao Hai slowly opened his eyes. He was also made aware that the Five Element Killing Formation in the Underworld had completely vanished. At this time, there would be no forbidden land in the Underworld.

Zhao Hai’s figure moved as he appeared inside the Snake King’s Domain. The Snake King wasn’t actually inside its area. It was waiting for Zhao Hai in a place not far away from the light wall. This touched Zhao Hai somewhat.

Zhao Hai found the Snake King and they returned to its domain. He also told the Snake King that there wouldn’t be anything attacking them in the future. They can now go to the central region. After that Zhao Hai went back to the Space.

At this point, Zhao Hai’s territory in the Underworld couldn’t be said to be small. Naturally, this included the Dark Creature Domain. Now that the Dark Creatures had been subdued by Zhao Hai, their territory would naturally be his. However, Zhao Hai didn’t plan to use the Dark Creatures to help him fight.

When Zhao Hai returned to the Space, he saw Laura and the others looking at the Space in confusion. After seeing Zhao Hai come back, Laura immediately said, “Brother Hai, the formation arranged by the Hundred Spirit Clan just disappeared.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “I know. The Five Elements Killing Formation has been withdrawn by the Space and placed inside my staff. Moreover, another Five Element Killing Formation is protecting my sea of knowledge.” Then he relayed what happened to Laura and the others.

The women began to understand what happened, then they couldn’t help but feel afraid. Laura said, “I didn’t expect the Hundred Spirit Clan to be that careful. It’s good that Brother Hai has a tender heart and didn’t destroy their corpses. Otherwise, we wouldn’t have obtained the Hundred Spirit Tree.”

Zhao Hai nodded with a smile as he said, “You wouldn’t expect the abilities of the Hundred Spirit Tree.”

When Zhao Hia’s said this, Laura and the others began to anticipate his next words, they immediately urged him to continue. Then Zhao Hai told them about the function of the Hundred Spirit Tree. The women didn’t expect the Hundred Spirit Tree to grow an island, and these islands could actually go into outer space.

The group began to understand how extraordinary the tree was. Zhao Hai had the same reaction as them, even he didn’t think that the tree would be this formidable.

As Zhao Hai looked at the Hundred Spirit Tree, he suddenly said, “Cai’er, come here quick.”

Cai’er immediately appeared by Zhao Hai’s side. Then Zhao Hai pointed to the Hundred Spirit Tree and said, “Cai’er, pay attention to the Hundred Spirit Tree. After 100 days, the tree would die. But before it completely withers, make sure to harvest its parts for medicine. For now, collect some leaves so that everyone can drink it as tea.”

Cai’er complied, then she looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Young Master, can’t we just accelerate the area around the Hundred Spirit Tree?”

Zhao Hai stared, he forgot about this point. Now that Cai’er reminded him, Zhao Hai thought it through before he said, “Alright, let’s do that. I forgot about it, Cai’er is truly smart.”

When Cai’er heard Zhao Hai’s praise, she couldn’t help but smile like a young lady. Then she went on to accelerate the area around the Hundred Spirit Tree.

But just as Cai’er was about to begin, the Space issued a prompt, “Unable to accelerate time around the selected area. Host’s level didn’t reach the requirement. Hoping the host to work harder.”

Zhao Hai stared, then she looked at Cai’er and said, “What happened? How is my level insufficient for time acceleration?”

Cai’er shook her head and said, “I don’t know, this is the first time I’ve encountered this. Normally, time would accelerate no matter what. It’s possibly because the Hundred Spirit Tree is too high-leveled.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “That seems to be it. In any case, we can still wait until 100 days are up. When the time comes, we would have our own floating island.”

Cai’er nodded. Laura and the others also heard the prompt, so they ran over. After hearing Zhao Hai’s words, Laura said, “Brother Hai, this Hundred Spirit Tree is a treasure of the heavens and the earth, and we’re already lucky to get our hands on it. It doesn’t matter if we wait.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Obtaining the tree is a great fortune. It is truly worth the wait. Let’s go back inside. Cai’er, please fetch us a couple of leaves. Let’s make some tea to drink.” Cai’er nodded. Then Zhao Hai led Laura and the others back into the villa.

After the group had sat down, Laura looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, we’ve already unified the Resistance Army as well as conquered the Dark Creature Domain. What do you plan to do next? Do you deal with the Dark Temple, or the Neutral Alliance?”

Zhao Hai thought about it for a moment and said, “We’ll go against the Dark Temple next. The Resistance Army still has business relations with the Neutral Alliance. Going against the Alliance at this time would just push them towards the Dark Temple. Let’s take a step back and look at the Alliance’s actions. Once we destroy the Dark Temple, then even the Neutral Alliance would not be able to do anything to us. At the same time, we can also make use of the Dark Creatures. If the Alliance plans anything, we can have the Dark Creatures deal with them.”

Laura nodded, “That’s also good. Brother Hai, how about the Blood Spirit Beasts? When do you plant to capture them?”

Zhao Hai paused before he answered, “Let’s wait for a couple of days. After a few days of rest, I will proceed to capture some Blood Spirit Beasts. I’m sure the Dark Temple still had people stationed along the Blood River. If I went to capture Blood Spirit Beasts, then I would be announcing my existence to them. When the Dark Temple gets word about me, then that would be my declaration of war.”

Laura nodded, “I reckon we should call Addison and the others over to make them prepare. After you capture the Blood Spirit Beasts, we shall immediately begin our war with the Dark Temple. Lizzy, Megan, are there any issues with the Undead army?”

Lizzy and Megan shook their heads. Then Lizzy replied, “There are no problems on our part. But Big Brother Hai, you should make a map of the Dark Temple’s territory. This way, it would be more convenient to fight against them.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Rest assured, I will make sure to do so. I will use these couple of days to map out the Dark Temple’s territory. We still aren’t sure about how big the Underworld is. If we cannot completely eradicate the Dark Temple and they hide somewhere, then it would be troublesome if they hit us in the future.”

Laura nodded and said, “The Underworld is truly huge. Even Ancient Lich like Gimreden aren’t aware to what extent. I’m afraid it wouldn’t be easy.”

Zhao Hai replied, “It doesn’t matter. No matter how big it is, it surely has an end point. The Underworld would be our back garden in the future, we need to grasp into every inch of this land.”

Chapter 1040: Target, Blood River, Depart!

Laura nodded. She agreed to Zhao Hai’s decision. If they cannot assure complete security in the Underworld, then they would have to constantly worry about hidden dangers all the time.

Zhao Hai looked at the group and said, “Alright, let’s not think too much about it. This time, I intend to find the Blood River’s source. The Blood River is able to produce so much Blood Spirit Beasts, so its source should be extraordinary. Perhaps it’s another treasure.”

Laura smiled and said, “Brother Hai, now that you’re getting richer and richer, you’re beginning to look at treasures as though they are gold coins. You shouldn’t expect too much.”

Zhao Hai laughed. At this time, Meg arrived while bringing a pot of tea. She placed it on the table and gave Zhao Hai and the others one cup each. Then she smiled and said, “Young Master, have a taste. This is tea made from the leaves of the Hundred Spirit Tree.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he looked down at the teacup. The cup was white porcelain, inside it was a light green tea. He could taste the delicate fragrance even before he drank it. As soon as the fragrance entered his nose, it dashed straight into his head, clearing it up from distracting thoughts.

Just with the smell, one would know how good the tea was. Zhao Hai proceeded to take a little sip. It was a bit bitter, but it was very fragrant. The moment he drank it, Zhao Hai felt every single pore in his body breathing. It was a fantastic feeling.

Zhao Hai closed his eyes and savoured the taste for some time. Then he let out a long breath and said, “This flavor is fantastic. Meg, prepare some leaves and send them to WIld Dragon Island for Grandpa Green and the others to consume. This thing can supplement spiritual force, it should be very useful for them.”

Meg gave a nod. Cai’er also took a cup to drink. After hearing Zhao Hai, she couldn’t help but turn her head and said, “Young Master, we should try having the leaves analyzed in the Scanner. Let’s see if it can be matched with other herbs inside the Space, making it better. What do you think?”

Zhao Hai nodded, “We might as well try making herbal tea. However, we shouldn’t lose this fragrance, otherwise the experience wouldn’t be good.”

Cai’er nodded, then her body flashed as she disappeared. Zhao Hai didn’t follow behind, it really wasn’t worth it for him to personally go to the Scanner. The result would be printed anyway.

Before long, Cai’er came back, on her hand was a piece of paper with a formula for herb tea. Zhao Hai looked at the recipe, it seems to be made with dozens of herbs that can be found in the Space. He returned the paper to Cai’er and said, “Meg, please try making this herb tea along with Cai’er. Then hand the formula over to Wild Dragon Island as well.”

Meg nodded and then followed Cai’er. Laura looked at their backs and faintly smiled, “The Space is truly convenient with Meg and Cai’er. As long as matters stay normal, the family’s matters would always be handled by them.”

Zhao Hai smiled, his face had a gentle look. Speaking of which, among Zhao Hai’s women, he was with Meg the longest. However, Meg had the least exposure because she spends most of her time taking care of Zhao Hai’s trivial matters. Because of this less conspicuous position, she simply cannot attract anybody’s attention.

However, Zhao Hai knew that without Meg, he wouldn’t be able to take care of his basic necessities. Meg understood Zhao Hai the most, and she was the one who could take care of him the best. Zhao Hai could smoothly enjoy his downtimes largely thanks to Meg’s efforts.

After drinking another sip of his tea, Zhao Hai looked back at the monitor. His blood needles were then sent scouring through the Dark Temple’s Domain, investigating and recording the terrain.

After releasing the blood needles, Zhao Hai called Addison and the others into the Space. Addison used the past few days to integrate the entire Resistance Army into one entity. But this integration happened mostly under wraps. They still did business with the Alliance. Nothing changed in the trades, there simply wasn’t any way for the Alliance to find anything wrong.

Actually, there were a lot of Undead from both the Neutral Alliance and the Dark Temple that were roaming around inside the Resistance Army’s territory. They were here in order to detect any movement inside the Army. But unfortunately, even if those Undead were experts, as long as they were sent to the Space, they would no longer be able to send information back. Therefore, no news about the Army’s unification reached the Neutral Alliance and the Dark Temple.

Addison lead Guli, Jiang Zheng, and the Five Element Skeletons into the Space’s villa. After giving their salute, Zhao Hai had the group sit down before he said, “Now that the matter with the Dark Creatures has been solved, we should begin to act against the Dark Temple. Is everything prepared?”

When Addison heard Zhao Hai, his heart couldn’t help but move, “Young Master, rest assured. We have finished our preparations. We can depart at any moment.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “That’s good. But there’s no need to be anxious, it’s still too early to start. Wait for me to deal with the Blood River and the Blood River Beasts first. Then after that, we can begin.”

Addison nodded. However, his expression seems to be down. He really thought that it was already time to attack the Dark Temple. He didn’t expect to wait.

Zhao Hai looked at Addison’s expression as he smiled and said, “Alright Addison, there’s no need to worry about it. Whether it be now or later, we would still be attacking the Dark Temple. As long as I’m done subduing the Blood Spirit Beasts, then we could gain the advantage of being able to retreat and attack whenever we want. Wouldn’t that be better?”

Addison nodded and said, “Yes, Young Master. I understand.”

Zhao Hai looked at the group and said, “I called you over here so that you can increase your strengths using the Space’s plants and fiery souls. I also want you to purchase more goods from the Alliance, make them think that this is because you are promoting more Experts in order to fight each other. Also, it would be best for us to gain more King-level Experts. This way, we would be more confident in dealing with the Dark Temple.”

Addison nodded, then he looked at Zhao Hai with a questioning expression, “Young Master, are you going to make a move? If you do, then there’s no need for us to fear the Dark Temple.”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “Naturally I would make a move. However, you should know that there is an exceptional Expert in the Dark Temple. If I move, then I would be blocked by that person. You would have to deal with the other Experts from the Dark Temple. Understood?”

Addison and the others immediately answered, “We understand. Please rest assured.”

Zhao Hai waved his hand and sent the group out. He handed all of the affairs in the Underworld over to Addison. He knew that Addison would do well. Moreover, if Zhao Hai ascends in the future, it would still be impossible for him to step in the Underworld even with the Space’s help. His strength at that time would be too much for the Underworld’s laws to tolerate. Because of that, he would need to leave a person behind to manage the Underworld. And Zhao Hai plans to have Addison be that person.

Zhao Hai was very relaxed in the next couple of days. He drank tea everyday and he even enjoyed the hot spring from time to time.

The blood needles had also mapped the majority of the Dark Temple’s domain over these few days. It can be said that Zhao Hai now had a certain understanding about the Dark Temple. In fact, Zhao Hai didn’t only explore the Dark Temple’s lands, he also sent some blood needles over to survey the Neutral Alliance. Since the Alliance was a potential threat, he needed to be guarded against them as well.

After Zhao Hai felt that his spirit and body had recovered to their best condition, he prepared to head towards the Blood River.

Zhao Hai persisted under the Five Element Killing Formation’s pressure for 10 hours straight. This endeavor exhausted both of his body and spirit. Because of this, Zhao Hai needed to take a good rest in order to avoid any accidents.

Zhao Hai never underestimated his enemies. He acted like a lion would when hunting a rabbit. He would do his best in order to succeed with the least loss to his side.

With the matter regarding the Blood River, Zhao Hai took a very careful stance. Addison also said that among the numerous Blood Spirit Beasts were beasts with King-level strength. Even King-level Experts would need to be careful when crossing the river. Therefore, Zhao Hai needed to be more careful this time if he wanted to succeed.

This time, Zhao Hai didn’t plan to fly alone. He called the Blood Lotus out and rode it.

The Blood Lotus was the lotus that the Hell King’s ship turned into. This lotus can both be large and small. This time, Zhao Hai plans to reduce the lotus’ size before tunneling underground towards the Blood River. This was the method that would attract the least attention of the Dark Temple. Only when it was time to make a big move would Zhao Hai make a huge noise.

Zhao Hai originally didn’t want Laura and the others to follow him, he wanted them to stay inside the Space. However, Laura would have none of it. In the end, Zhao Hai caved in and allowed the women to stay inside the Blood Lotus’ Space.

It can be said that the Space inside the Blood Lotus was just the same as the villa, except it didn’t have the Hundred Spirit Tree. The Blood Lotus was also very strong. If there was any danger, Laura and the others could still return to the Space. And since the women liked to follow Zhao Hai, he didn’t have the courage to stop them.

Everything has been prepared, Laura and the others were also inside the Blood Lotus. Zhao Hai began to head towards the Blood River. They appeared in a place not far from the River. After coming out of the Space, the lotus immediately tunneled underground. Both the people from the Resistance Army and the Dark Temple would not be able to detect anything.

Chapter 1041: This is a Blood Spirit Beast?!

Zhao Hai leisurely sat inside the Blood Lotus. It can be said that the Blood Lotus was very comfortable. The lotus advances like how a flying saucer would. As it advanced, its petals would rotate, each layer at the opposite direction as the one on top of it.

Zhao Hai was currently with Laura and the others. At this time, the lotus had become as large as the palm of one’s hand while Zhao Hai and the others were small enough to stand on one’s thumb. This was a function of the Lotus that Zhao Hai named as microcosm.

.The Hell King’s ship also had this function. Zhao Hai used this a lot when he was dealing with the Divines. There were a lot of times when the Divines lost track of where Zhao Hai went.

One had to recognize how convenient the microcosm was. Take this time for example, it allowed Zhao Hai to make as little noise as possible as he tunneled underground. Making it less likely for the Undead on the surface to notice him.

Zhao Hai was very careful regarding these Undead. These Undead lived in the Underworld, they were experts in using spiritual force. If Zhao Hai didn’t properly consider his actions, then he would be discovered by these Undead.

Actually, Zhao Hai planned everything properly. Although these Undead had formidable spiritual force, it was impossible for them to penetrate deep below the ground. Only those who were exceptionally strong would be able to.

The place where Zhao Hai began to sneak in wasn’t far from the Blood River. After a short time, Zhao Hai discovered that the land around the Blood Lotus had began turning red. And after smelling a bloody fragrance, Zhao Hai knew that they were almost at their destination.

Sure enough, after a few minutes, Zhao Hai suddenly felt a current hitting the Blood Lotus. The Blood Lotus didn’t stop, it didn’t take long before the lotus was entirely covered with blood river water.

Zhao Hai thought that the Blood River would immediately send Blood River Beasts to attack. However, much to Zhao Hai’s surprise, nothing happened even after half an hour.

There were more things that were beyond what Zhao Hai expected. Zhao Hai thought that the Blood River had nothing other than the Blood Spirit Beasts. But after entering the river, Zhao Hai knew that there were more things inside.

Plants, animals, all of which were red, were present here. Naturally, Zhao Hai wasn’t polite and took some of these things to the Space.

Zhao Hai looked everywhere with curiosity. He had yet to see a single Blood Spirit Beast. This caused Zhao Hai to feel strange. During the fight between the Dark Temple and the Resistance Army, there were plenty of Blood Spirit Beasts present. How could it be possible for Zhao Hai to not meet one right now.

Laura and the others were also very curious about the surroundings. It was a completely blood red world. The river itself was red, the plants were red, the animals were red, everything around them was red.

What made Zhao Hai feel strange was the fact that despite smelling like blood outside, the water in the Blood River actually had a fragrant smell.

After going forward for a half hour without coming across Blood Spirit Beasts, Laura couldn’t help but turn to Zhao Hai, “Brother Hai? Where are the Blood Spirit Beasts?”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “I don’t know. This is truly weird. In any case, let’s take some of the blood river’s water first.”

After he said that, Zhao Hai opened a spatial rift beside the Blood Lotus. The spatial rift proceeded to suck in some blood water as well as some stone and sand nearby.

Almost immediately, the Space issued a prompt, “Sand and stones submerged in blood energy detected. May be used for crafting.”

Zhao Hai stared, he didn’t expect that even the sand and stones would have some use.

At this moment, Zhao Hai suddenly found a few dark spots flowing with the water. Zhao Hai used his spiritual force to sweep through these spots and found that they looked like very small octopuses, they were as small as an ant, black, and had small tentacles

Zhao Hai looked at these creatures and couldn’t help but feel his scalp tingle. This was because there were too many of them. The clump was very dense, who knows how many there was inside.

Then at this moment, the little creatures stopped as one of them swam towards Zhao Hai. As soon as it arrived by the Blood Lotus, it extended its tentacles, coming into contact with the Blood Lotus’ energy shield.

Although this little octopus was small, one shouldn’t forget that the Blood Lotus had also reduced its size. It can be said that Zhao Hai’s current size wasn’t any bigger than this creature.

Laura and the others looked at these octopuses, their faces began to turn pale. Although they weren’t afraid of these octopuses, they felt uncomfortable and disgusted at the sight of them.

Zhao Hai wanted to take the octopus into the Space, but he didn’t expect it to suddenly shoot out and distance itself away from the lotus. Then Zhao Hai suddenly felt that a formidable spiritual force coming from that small octopus. Then its tentacles began to reach out, Zhao Hai didn’t know what it was doing.

But it didn’t take long before he got his answer.  As the octopus’ spiritual force reached into the surrounding water, the river water began to compress before turning into thick blood drop. Then this blood drop grew a head, then a hand, before turning into a Blood Spirit Beast!

Zhao Hai looked at this with shock. He didn’t expect the Blood Spirit Beasts to actually be these small octopuses. No wonder it was almost impossible to kill Blood Spirit Beasts, they were small octopuses no bigger than an ant. At the same time, their manipulation of the Blood River was exponentially greater compared to their size. Most of the time, the attacks would just touch their temporary blood bodies. One would need a very strong spiritual force in order to have the possibility of killing them.

While Zhao Hai was in a daze, the Blood Spirit Beast began to launch attacks towards the Blood Lotus. The fighting strength of the beast underwater was much greater than in the air.

Moreover, Zhao Hai discovered something strange. Although the Blood Spirit Beast had just transformed, it could still operate the surrounding waters in order to attack him.

Zhao Hai was now very curious as to how these little octopuses were able to do this. However, the attacks of the small octopus wasn’t very strong. As the octopus proceeded to attack, Zhao Hai waved his blood ghost staff, sealing the octopus inside a transparent box. Then a spatial rift opened, taking the box into the Space.

When the Blood Spirit Beast entered the Space, a prompt was heard, “Variant octopus detected. It can survive in an environment full of blood energy. After forming their blood bodies, they can perform spiritual attacks. At the same time, their spiritual force would also be amplified, allowing them to control the water 100 meters around them to attack. However, the octopus has a flaw, it can only survive in environments with dense blood energy. Asking host for permission to fix the defect. The octopus can be upgraded to be able to live in all types of water. It can command the water around it to form its own body and carry physical attacks as well as have amplified spiritual force to control the water surrounding them to attack. Since the Host already has an upgraded ability for water, the Space wouldn’t ask for gold for the upgrade. Because of the octopus’ special ability, host’s abilities has been strengthened. Hoping for the host to work harder.”

There were quite a few prompts for the small octopus, but Zhao Hai understood them all. The small octopus was practically a special being that managed to survive in the Blood River. It can use its spiritual force to compress blood and turn it into a body. Not only this, their spiritual force would also be amplified during this form.

Moreover, Zhao Hai gained another ability. Before he goes to try it, he first gave a command, “Upgrade them immediately.”

Then the Space issued another prompt, “Fixing the flaws of the octopus. Successfully upgraded to water-controlling octopus. New octopus has been added to the Space’s shop. Host may purchase them there.”

After this, Zhao Hai tried to control the blood river water. Zhao Hai let out his spiritual force and slowly extended it towards the Blood River. Before long, Zhao Hai could feel the blood water reacting to his spiritual force. Zhao Hai immediately commanded it to compress.

Sure enough, the river water slowly compressed into a blood drop. This drop was evidently more dense compared to the surrounding river water. Then Zhao Hai started to use his mental image to form the image of a person. The person was wearing fish scale armor and held a large military glaive in his hand. His head was also covered with a helmet while leaving his red beard to flutter along the currents. The person also had lifelike phoenix eyebrows. If one was a Chinese native, then one could recognize this person as Yunchang, General Guan Yu!

After he imagined Guan Yu’s appearance, Zhao Hai felt the blood river concentrate to form the image. He could even feel the water flowing through Guan Yu’s body. Zhao Hai knew that this was because his spiritual force had already made a mold for the body to be formed into. In this case, Guan Yu was akin to Zhao Hai’s river incarnation.

But what made Zhao Hai somewhat puzzled was the fact that after Guan Yu’s figure was formed, it didn’t need to be supplied with spiritual force any longer. Instead, the spiritual force was supplied by Guan Yu’s body in order to operate the blood. Zhao Hai felt that this feeling was quite marvelous, it was like having multiple bodies. And the other body seems to magnify his own spiritual force.

Zhao Hai thought about lifting a hand, of which Guan Yu followed. Zhao Hai felt curiosity about this new incarnation.

At this time, a Blood Spirit Beast suddenly appeared in front. This beast was in wolf-form but it didn’t have an eye. It threw itself towards Zhao Hai’s Guan Yu incarnation.

While familiarizing himself with the Guan Yu incarnation, Zhao Hai was not able to notice the Blood Spirit Beast. As he was distracted, the beast already took a chunk of Guan Yu’s flesh.

Zhao Hai felt Guan Yu’s body being bitten, but he didn’t actually feel any pain. He only felt a sensation stating that a part of the body was bitten. Guan Yu began to heal, but this time, it seems like his body has been reduced by a bit.

Zhao Hai began to understand the uses of this river incarnation. It was a type of Divine Ability that would produce a weapon for its user. Breaking this ability wouldn’t affect the user too much. If it was damaged, it would just reduce in size.

Now, Zhao Hai wanted to see the Guan Yu incarnation’s fighting strength. Therefore, Zhao Hai used the Blood Spirit Beast as a testing specimen for Guan Yu.

Guan Yu’s glaive was very quick. Although they were underwater, it seems like the river had no effect on it whatsoever. The glaive sliced the Blood Spirit Beast in half. Even though the Beast had recovered, it was now half of its original size.

Actually, Zhao Hai didn’t expect the incarnation to be this strong. One must know that the compressed blood bodies were quite formidable. These Blood Spirit Beasts were able to fight the Dark Temple, even managing to be a threat to their High-ranked experts. Zhao Hai didn’t expect these Blood Spirit Beasts to be cut in half by Guan Yu’s glaive.

Zhao Hai tried to control the surrounding blood river water. Not only could he control it properly, it seems like this control was much better now that the incarnation was around. Zhao Hai knew that this was because of the incarnation’s ability to amplify spiritual force.

Upon thinking of this, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but feel ecstatic. He quickly controlled the Guan Yu incarnation and killed Blood Spirit Beasts in the four directions. And in addition to the glaive, the surrounding water was also used to help in the battle. When a Blood Spirit Beast was cut in half, it was immediately taken to the Space white it was recovering. It didn’t take long for the river to turn murky from the battle.

But little did Zhao Hai know, the underwater battle had caused a huge shock to the Undead on both banks of the river. These Undead were sent by the Dark Temple as well as the Resistance Army. They weren’t mainly here to look at the Blood River, they were also here to monitor the other riverbank, afraid that the other side would try to cross. Just as the Undead were feeling calm, they didn’t expect the Blood River to surge with waves upon waves. This turbulence continued on, this caused the Undead above water to be puzzled at what was happening to the River.

Chapter 1042: Tracing

Actually, Zhao Hai didn’t need to know about this, he was already aware that he would be making a huge mess and attract the attention of the Undead on both banks of the river. However, Zhao Hai didn’t care about it. This was because those who were above water would only think that it would just be Blood Spirit Beasts fighting. They wouldn’t think that it was another person who caused this disturbance.

The battle on murky waters continued on, and Zhao Hai lost count of how many Blood Spirit Beasts he already collected into the Space. As long as Zhao Hai kept fighting, then the Space would continuously receive Blood Spirit Beasts.

In the beginning, Laura and the others were eagerly watching the battle outside. But later on, they stopped watching. They found out that the Blood Spirit Beasts weren’t Zhao Hai’s opponents at all. There was no meaning to watching the current battle.

Zhao Hai kept fighting. This was because he discovered that the river incantation was very easy to use, the enemy simply couldn’t do anything to him. Although the incarnation’s defense was a little bit worse, its effect of amplifying spiritual force was something that Zhao Hai fancied a lot.

Amplifying spiritual forces wasn’t something that was easily accomplished. Every time Zhao Hai used his Blood Ghost Staff, he would always use his spiritual force. This was also one flaw of the Blood Ghost Staff. At the same time, the higher an item’s level was, the more spiritual force it would use. Finding items that can increase spiritual force wasn’t something that can be easily found.

Even something as tyrannical as the Hundred Spirit Tree wouldn’t be able to increase one’s spiritual force. The tree’s leaves could only restore spiritual force.

The reason why Zhao Hai continued on fighting wasn’t because he loved to fight, it was because he was taking advantage of this opportunity to train his ability to control the river incarnation. Zhao Hai always felt that the river incarnation would have great uses for him in the future.

Zhao Hai didn’t know for how long he has been fighting, he only came to normal when he had full understanding of the Guan Yu incarnation. At this point, the inexhaustible amount of Blood Spirit Beasts in front of him were no more than a group of kittens.

Zhao Hai wasn’t polite and sent all of these Blood Spirit beasts into the Space. Then he withdrew the incarnation before he urged the Blood Lotus to go forward.

On the other hand, the Undead on the riverbanks didn’t dare to make a move. The waves of the Blood River seemed to reach the heavens. They almost died, they were too frightened to make a move.

In fact, their inactivity was the correct decision. This was because Zhao Hai returned the Blood Spirit Beasts he captured. If they dared to cross the river at this time, then they would surely be decimated by the Blood Spirit Beasts.

While fighting the Blood Spirit Beasts, Zhao Hai also discovered the different stages of their strength. The Blood Spirit Beast who took a bite out of the incarnation was a middle-ranked beast. There were low-ranked beasts who were weaker defensively and offensively. These two levels of Beasts had spots that were blue. Meanwhile, the Blood Spirit Beasts who had the strength comparable to Addison and the others were colored gold.

At this time, Zhao Hai had 20 of these gold spotted beasts inside the Space. Naturally, in the Blood River, these beasts were much stronger than King-level Dark Creatures and Experts.

Also, Zhao Hai discovered that it was impossible for the Blood Spirit Beasts to wade through the entire river. The beasts were divided into their own colonies. What Zhao Hai captured were just members of one colony. There were certainly more colonies living along the river.

Zhao Hai continued moving forward. As long as the came upon something, he would immediately send it to the Space. It didn’t matter if they were animals, plants, or even sand and stones. As long as they were peculiar, all of them were sent to the Space.

Now that the underwater battle was finished, the river began to calm down. Although the Undead on both banks saw that the river had calmed down, they still didn’t dare to rush to the other side. They only rushed back to their domains in order to report what just happened.

Naturally, Zhao hai was able to discover their action. However, he wasn’t worried, the Blood River was completely covered with Blood Spirit Beasts. Even if the Dark Temple used this opportunity to move, they would still be eating severe losses.

Laura and the others had also walked out of the room. They really weren’t interested in seeing Zhao Hai overpower the Blood Spirit Beasts. Because of this, they went to their room to take a rest. Now that the Blood River had calmed down, naturally they would come out again.

After seeing the women go out of their rooms, Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Why did you come out? There’s nothing to see here. I’ve already collected most of the useful things in this river.”

Laura replied, “There’s nothing to see inside our rooms either, it’s better to look outside. Brother Hai, are you confident that the people from the Dark Temple wouldn’t dare to cross the river?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Rest assured, they wouldn’t dare.”

The group continued chatting as they went forward. It didn’t take long before they met with another colony of Blood Spirit Beasts. But this time, Zhao Hai didn’t intend to use the Guan Yu incarnation. Using too much force against these creatures was just too stupid.

Zhao Hai turned his staff into a huge net, catching the Blood Spirit Beasts and sending them to the Space. Although the Blood Spirit Beasts wanted to resist, they weren’t Zhao Hai’s opponents. In the end, they were easily caught by Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai wasn’t just simply moving forward. He also made blood needles and sent them ahead. He didn’t know how long the river would be, so he decided to map everything along the way.

As for how long the river was, Zhao Hai simply had no idea. What Zhao Hai knew was that he had already traversed the river for three days. He met 20 Blood Spirit Beast colonies, both large and small. But still, he had yet to see the source of the river.

What surprised Zhao Hai the most was the fact that they were now in a place beyond the Space’s map. This means that they were now in a place where the blood needles had yet to explore.

Zhao Hai has to admit that he needed to increase his estimation of the Underworld. He didn’t expect this plane to be this huge. The Blood Lotus might be slower while underwater, but it wasn’t far slower compared to flying in the air. Even so, despite having travelled for three days, it still wasn’t enough to see the full length of the blood river.

However, this also provoked the stubbornness inside Zhao Hai’s heart. He was now more eager to find the source of the river. Zhao Hai also discovered that the things he came upon was different to the ones he found three days ago.

Cai’er was also making calculations based on their progress. This way, they might be able to estimate the length of the river.

Zhao Hai didn’t stop this since he also wanted to find out. He wanted to find the river’s source first before he looked for the river’s end. This way, he would be able to estimate the Underworld’s exact size.

Before long, another three days passed by. There was no difference in these three days compared to the first three days. The Blood River was still the Blood River. However, Zhao Hai could notice that the river has gotten narrower.

Not only was the river beginning to narrow, the water current had also become much slower. After detecting this phenomenon, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile. This was because he might be closing in on the river’s source.

Another three days passed. This time, the Blood River’s properties had greatly changed. The river had gone much narrower while the current was getting even slower. In fact, instead of a river, it might even be called a small stream.

Zhao Hai also discovered that the density of the Blood Spirit Beasts was increasing. Moreover, all of the Blood Spirit Beasts along this small stream were high-ranked ones. Zhao Hai believed that if the Dark Temple dared to cross this part of the river, then they would certainly suffer catastrophic losses.

At this point, Zhao Hai’s speed had gone slower as he subdued each Blood Spirit Beast colony he came across. The beasts were getting stronger and stronger, the worst of them were at Guli’s previous strength. Wanting to capture such beasts would naturally prove to be more difficult.

However, by Zhao Hai’s present strength, the least these Blood Spirit Beasts could do was cause him a bit of trouble. Zhao Hai had a lot of methods to deal with them, these beasts were simply not his opponents.

After fighting against these Blood Spirit Beasts for quite some time, Zhao Hai began to find some flaws in them. The strength of the Blood Spirit Beasts might be very good, but their intelligence was evidently not that high. Compared to beings of the same level, the Blood Spirit Beasts were far worse intellectually.

Also, it seems like the Blood Spirit Beasts didn’t have to attack the Undead that flew over the Blood River. This was because the river was enough food for them. However, the fiery souls of the Undead were great supplements for their strength. Therefore, they chose to attack the Undead crossing the river.

These Blood Spirit Beasts weren’t evenly distributed along the entire Blood River. Like what was discovered before, they lived in their own colonies in their own domains. Once another colony encroaches upon another colony’s territory, then a conflict would immediately occur.

But once the Undead begin to form groups along the river, these Blood Spirit Beasts would gather on the surface. The more time passes, the greater number of beasts would accumulate.

It didn’t matter if it was the Dark Temple or the Resistance Army, both sides would need time to prepare their armies. This preparation time would naturally come into the knowledge of the Blood Spirit Beasts. When this happens, the beasts would begin to gather. And once the Undead begins to cross the river, these beasts would immediately attack.

It can be said that the Blood Spirit Beasts were creatures primarily driven by food, beings that lived in accordance to their base instinct. Additionally, the command structure of these beasts wasn’t flexible. It was this point that made Zhao Hai conclude that the beasts didn’t have very high intellect.

Zhao Hai had now traversed the Blood River for nine days. He didn’t know how far he’d gone, but from the blood needles he released, he was able to discover that the current of the river had slowed down and the river has also gone narrower. And with the evident depth becoming shallower, Zhao Hai began to see hope.

At this moment, Zhao Hai suddenly noticed a bone mountain in the distance. This Bone Mountain was very tall. At the same time, the blood river was flowing out from a cave on the foot of the mountain.

Chapter 1043: A Colossal Heart!!

The source, the Blood River’s source was here!

Zhao Hai can almost affirm it at this point. He immediately ordered the Blood Lotus to rushed towards the cave. As soon as he reached the cave, Zhao Hai could quickly sense the change in environment.

The water inside the cavern was thicker it also had a stronger scent. But although the scent was strong, it wasn’t something that would choke a person. Instead, this scent made one feel more energetic and comfortable.

Besides these, Zhao Hai also discovered that there were a lot of Blood Spirit Beasts inside the cave. Moreover, these beasts were all blood red in color, and were almost transparent, they looked very beautiful.

However, Zhao Hai could feel that each one of these beasts had formidable strength. Every single one of them were no weaker than Addison. If Zhao Hai’s strength hadn’t increased to its current state, then he wouldn’t have been a match against these Blood Spirit Beasts.

This cave wasn’t very big, at about a meter in diameter. The blood water stretched up to 50 centimeters deep. But in the depths of this 50 centimeters were the most powerful Blood Spirit Beasts.

After seeing this situation, Zhao Hai knew it would be unrealistic for him to go inside and fight. Because of this, Zhao Hai had no choice but to stop at the mouth of the cave. What was strange was the fact that the Blood Spirit beasts didn’t attack him despite him being just at the entrance of the cave. This was different compared to the beasts that Zhao Hai had met before.

In the end, Zhao Hai can only release his blood needles to search inside the cave. The needle was an inanimate object, therefore the Blood Spirit Beasts just ignored its presence.

While this was happening, Zhao Hai entered the Space and looked at the monitor along with the others. They knew that they had found the river’s source.

The blood needle flew for more than ten meters beyond the cave before it came upon another open space. Zhao Hai and the others didn’t expect this one to be a very huge area. There was a great blood red lake inside this space. There was a distinct absence of Dark Mist above the lake. From the surface of the lake to the roof of the huge cave was about a 100-meter empty area. The walls of the cave was naturally made out of bone, it gave a sturdy and strong appearance.

Zhao Hai commanded the blood needles to survey the entire place. Then suddenly, Zhao Hai’s attention was taken by a huge stone pillar in the middle of the lake. The pillar was quite huge. At a diameter of 5 meters, the pillar stretched up 100 meters upwards. Unexpectedly, the stone pillar was actually hollow. Moreover, Zhao Hao could note that this space’s Dark Mist was being sucked in by that stone pillar.

After this discovery, Zhao Hai immediately felt the urge to enter the stone pillar to take a look. However, Zhao Hai began to feel that this pillar might be one of those things he saw on TV. It was when someone uses a straw in order to breath underwater. At the thought of this scene, Zhao Hai lost courage in entering the stone pillar. He didn’t want to become another person’s food.

In addition to the stone pillar, Zhao Hai also found a spring not far from the pillar. There was a non-stop flow of blood water coming from that spring, it was quite spectacular.

Upon looking at this scene for some time, Zhao Hai shifted his focus on the deep lake. He already knew that this large lake was the source of the Blood River.

When Zhao Hai’s spiritual force searched below the surface of the lake, he was met with shock. Blood red plants grew in all directions. He can also see Blood Spirit Beasts leisurely swimming inside. There were also grotesque looking rocks shining amidst the plants.

Zhao Hai didn’t expect the lake’s underwater portion to be illuminated. He quickly commanded the blood needles to explore the vicinity, projecting the findings on the Space’s monitor.

But as the blood needles continued on, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but stare. This lake was simply a huge pit, it was very deep. It had already reached a point where the area around the blood needles became almost pitch black.

The pillar that extended out of the lake had a hole on its side. It was this hole that provided the blood water that the spring had been spewing out.

Zhao Hai commended the blood needle to go straight down. After diving for ten minutes, Zhao Hai suddenly spotted a tiled roof!

He didn’t see wrong, it was actually a tiled roof. It was glazed tile, and upon looking at the roof, it seems to be perfectly preserved.

Zhao Hai stared, then he quickly commanded the needle to stop. He didn’t expect to see a roof here. Moreover, it was a well-preserved roof.

This roof didn’t seem to be destroyed or damaged in any degree, which made Zhao Hai feel even more strange. If this structure was built and was plunged into such a deep body of water, it shouldn’t have been preserved this well. This structure being well preserved only meant one thing, it was built underwater.

Moreover, Zhao Hai noted another thing, the surroundings of this structure didn’t have any Blood Spirit Beast. There were only plants present, no beasts.

Because of this unusual encounter, Zhao Hai decided to be more careful. He investigated the surroundings and found nothing else. However, he discovered that the scouting range of the blood needles seem to have been restricted. The normal range of the blood needles was ten thousand meters. But now, it could barely scout 1000 meters around it. The suppression had reached more than ten times.

Laura and the others were also looking at this strange place, nobody spoke a word. All of them were staring at the monitor, trying to look for anything. At this time, Zhao Hai saw two pillars right behind this structure. This caused Zhao Hai to be confused, he remembered that there was only one pillar coming out of the lake’s surface. How come there was two?

After looking around and seeing that there was no immediate danger, Zhao Hai commanded the blood needles to continue its dive. Before long, a giant palace was projected on the monitor.

There was only a great hall inside this palace. There were no walls in this palace, it only had a fine stone-paved floor. The whole hall was about 50 meters high, 200 meters long, and 100 meters wide. The outside walls of the palace was made out of a kind of stone. This stone wasn’t red, it was only the blood red water’s shade that made the wall look bright red.

Zhao Hai could see glazed tiles on top of this hall. The flashing lights of these tiles looked dazzling.

Zhao Hai made two turns outside the great hall. He couldn’t find anything else that was special. There was a plaque that was hung on the front of the hall. However, the characters used to write on this plaque was something that was foreign to Zhao Hai. He couldn’t understand even a single word of it.

Outside the palace were 99 stone steps. Zhao Hai counted them as the blood needles proceeded to enter the hall.

Upon entering the Great Hall, Zhao Hai was met with a shock. Passing through the gate, one could see a copper cauldron. Who knows how long this copper cauldron existed. It was carved with intricate patterns. There were flowers, mountains, birds, insects, and everything else that can be found in a world.

However, Zhao Hai’s attention wasn’t on this copper cauldron. Inside this Great Hall, besides the copper cauldron, was an extremely huge heart floating in place!

This giant heart was 40 meters high, 100 meters long and a few dozen meters wide. It almost filled the entire great hall.

Zhao Hai sat in the Space as he stared blankly at the floating heart. After some time, Zhao Hai managed to calm down. Then his figure moved as his body appeared inside the Great Hall. Upon seeing the heart in close distance, Zhao Hai was met with an even bigger shock.

The flesh and blood of this heart was very fresh, each vein was clearly discernible. While Zhao Hai was carefully observing the heart, it suddenly moved, performing a full beating cycle. The sound of beating was like thunder to Zhao Hai’s ears. Zhao Hai was shaken, he didn’t expect this heart to still be alive, and beating!

When he saw this, Zhao Hai’s expression couldn’t help but change. Never even in his dreams would he expect to see a huge living heart like this. This was too inconceivable!

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but look around. He wanted to ascertain whether he had entered someone’s body and he just haven’t noticed it.

Unfortunately, Zhao Hai was met with the palace’s walls. However upon looking at the walls, Zhao Hai discovered that murals were painted on them.

Zhao Hai carefully inspected these murals. The drawings were very exquisite. Although this place was submerged underwater for who knows how long, the pictures were still quite vivid. This made Zhao Hai conclude that this palace was truly built with the thought of it being submerged underwater.

Zhao Hai browsed the murals, it seems like it was showing a story. Although there weren’t any writings for explanation, Zhao Hai could still understand it.

The first painting was of chaos, nothingness. Then there was a huge egg in this chaotic space. Inside this egg was a person. When this person grew up, he broke free of the egg. As he did so, he ended up splitting the heavens and the earth.

Upon seeing this scene, Zhao Hai’s body couldn’t help but shake. This was a story that was the same as Pangu’s story back on Earth.

What does this place have to do with Earth? While he thought about this, Zhao Hai’s heart couldn’t help but beat fiercely. He couldn’t help but look at the next drawings and follow on with the story. The body of this huge god turned into the mountainous earth. However, the story seems to have a deviation here. In this story, the being’s body didn’t completely become part of the earth. Instead, this being left behind his heart!

Different from the Chinese legend, this story didn’t include Lady Nuwa who created nature. Instead, when this being split the heavens and the earth, myriad beings begin to exist. Then a group of monkeys discovered this being’s heart and guarded it for generations. But then, the heart slowly transformed these monkeys. In the end, the monkeys completely evolved to become humans!

Chapter 1044: History, Belief, Resilience

This group of monkeys that turned into Humans didn’t forget their mission. They still protected the giant heart. As these humans grew more and more numerous, their strength was also increasing. But despite these changes, they still protected the heart, they even built a palace in order to house it. Then outside the palace, they placed a cauldron so that they could pay their respects.

The mural was painted in an exquisite manner. The lines were very smooth, making one feel as though they were looking at a work full of elegance, a work that can only be made by a deity.

But the next images depicted something different from the ones before. The humans began to fight, two groups killing each other. The scene was frigid. Even if it was just a drawing, Zhao Hai could somewhat smell the scent of blood.

These two groups were divided into those who wanted to take the heart and those who wanted to protect it. Naturally, these different ideals caused a conflict.

Moreover, the conflict became more and more fierce. The situation of the battles were getting more and more vicious. Zhao Hai has to recognize the skill of the one who painted the mural. These pictures weren’t very big, but each panel was brightly drawn, very lifelike. It made one feel like they were experiencing the event firsthand.

The following images were becoming more tragic. But it was clear that those guarding the heart were in a disadvantage, their numbers were getting lower and lower.

After being aware of their inevitable loss, those who wanted to protect the heart secretly hid it. Then they destroyed the palace they made using self-sacrificing spells. And because these people were very strong, the entire plane almost got destroyed. Meanwhile, those who wanted to take the heart broke the firmament and escaped.

Depicted in the last picture was a person. It seems like this person was one of those who protected the heart, and the place where he was in seems to be this palace.

Zhao Hai looked at these pictures and couldn’t help but let out a long breath. He looked all around the room but failed to sense anybody’s presence. This made Zhao Hai quite curious, did the person protecting the heart leave?

After looking around more, Zhao Hai discovered that there were more pictures painted on the floor. Zhao Hai rushed towards the pictures and saw that there was indeed more to the story. The painting depicted the last person guarding the heart. This time, he was already very old, in a state near incapable of guarding the heart.

Then Zhao Hai saw the person took the cauldron from outside and then placed something inside it. Later on, Zhao Hai saw that the person actually placed a small octopus on the cauldron. Then he placed his hand on the cauldron and then turned it one time. The octopus got smaller before turning into a Blood Spirit Beast’s main body.

After seeing this, Zhao Hai understood that the Blood Spirit Beasts were made by this person using a secret method. All because he wanted the heart to be protected.

In the last picture, the person went towards the heart. His body shone before finally disappearing. The moment the person disappeared, the heart began beating.

Zhao Hai began to understand.

When the heart first appeared, it didn’t beat at all. However, it was evident that the heart wasn’t dead. When the last person who guarded the heart found out that he could no longer protect it, he made the Blood Spirit Beasts before injecting all of his remaining life force into the heart. In the end, the heart regained some of its vitality and began to beat.

Zhao Hai was also certain that the painting was made before the man injected his vitality into the heart. The person knew very well what would happen if he injected his life force into the heart. And since this was the case, he drew the picture in advance. Zhao Hai also understood why he couldn’t find the person who protected the heart, he had already disappeared.

After getting a clear image of the entire event, Zhao Hai’s heart couldn’t help but feel heavy. These people actually did their duty up to the last man. This went beyond Zhao Hai’s expectation.

This time, Zhao Hai was even more curious about the giant heart. In Zhao Hai’s view, it was impossible to know if this heart was indeed from a world-creating god. However, these people actually drew the legend. Also, it seems like they didn’t treat it like a mere myth. The knowledge that they were monkeys evolved because of the heart seems to be embedded deep into their bones.

Since he couldn’t get to the end of it, Zhao Hai decided to leave it for later. Then he looked at the giant heart, not knowing what to do with it. Zhao Hai slowly flew towards the heart and watched it beating. It was a very powerful beat, but it seems to be erratic.

Zhao Hai seems to form a connection with the heart. He saw the people who eagerly guarded it from generation to generation. Then in the end, when they couldn’t protect it any longer, the last of them made the Blood Spirit Beasts. What Zhao Hai was looking at wasn’t just a giant heart, it was a piece of history, an object of faith, and a monument to resilience.

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but touch the heart. As his skin came into contact with the beating organ, he suddenly felt a huge amount of spiritual force entering his head. The five element killing formation acted quickly, keeping it off.

However, Zhao Hai discovered that the spiritual force wasn’t intending to attack. And although it had been kept off by the five element killing formation, the formation’s response wasn’t violent. It only blocked the spiritual force, it didn’t retaliate.

Zhao Hai gawked before he scanned the spiritual force with his own. Then he discovered the incoming spiritual force was indeed not intending to attack. It seems like it was going to relay information.

Upon this discovery, Zhao Hai immediately took the information in. This spiritual force was like a tsunami. As soon as it entered Zhao Hai’s head, Zhao Hai immediately passed out.

After seeing Zhao Hai passing out, Laura and the others immediately got anxious. Cai’er hastily opened a spatial rift and took Zhao Hai into the Space. After Zhao Hai’s body was taken to the Space, Laura immediately asked, “Cai’er, go take a look at Brother Hai, see if he is hurt.”

Cai’er nodded before she sent a white light to envelop Zhao Hai. After seeing the lack of response from Zhao Hai, Laura and the others became even more anxious.

Among those present, it was only Meg who stayed calm. After seeing Zhao Hai’s current state, she immediately said, “Sister Laura, there’s no need to panic. Young Master is fine, he’s just digesting something.”

Laura and the others looked at Meg in confusion. Meg smiled faintly and said, “I’ve seen the Young Master in this situation once before. At that time, the Young Master just acquired his Space. Since he didn’t know its function, information began to flood into his head. But since there was a lot to digest, the Young Master wasn’t able to wake up for a while. We should send Young Master to his room, let him take a proper rest.”

As soon as they heard Meg, Laura and the others began to calm down. The group quickly sent Zhao Hai back to his room. After everything has been settled down, they proceeded to drink tea in the living room.

Laura looked at Meg and said, “Meg, when Brother Hai became like this before, were you afraid?”

Meg shook her head and said, “You don’t know the miserable state the Buda Clan has been during that time. It can be said that the existence of the Buda Clan was completely reliant on the Young Master. Him not existing is equal to the Buda Clan not existing. Therefore, in Grandfather and Grandmother’s eyes, as long as the Young Master survives, then we would stay strong. If he dies, then we would die as well.”

Laura and the others stared. They didn’t expect Meg to talk about death at this time.

Lizzy looked at Meg and said, “Really? Are you really thinking about death at that time?”

Meg nodded and said, “At that time, the only legitimate heir to the clan was the Young Master. If the Young Master accidentally dies, then we would lose our reason to exist. Grandfather and Grandmother were both raised by the Buda Clan, they had already tied their fate to the clan. If the Buda Clan ceased to exist, then they would also lose their reason to exist. Because of this, Grandfather and Grandmother were prepared to die if ever the Young Master dies.”

Lizzy and the others breathed in cold air. They didn’t expect the situation to reach this point. The group looked eagerly at Meg, hoping for her to expand on the matter.

Meg smiled and said, “You should know that back then, in the Aksu Empire, the old Emperor wanted to deal with the Southern King. And since the Buda Clan was the sword of the old Emperor, we were right in the opposite camp to the Southern King. But when the old Emperor died, the next Emperor was someone who was supported by the Southern King. In this case, how can the Buda Clan continue existing? When the Buda Clan was on the cusp of being eliminated, they even had the Young Master drink the Water of Nothingness. After the Young Master drank the water, he didn’t wake up for several months.”

After speaking about this, Meg couldn’t help but recall more, “The reason why people couldn’t fully exterminate the Buda Clan at that time was because either they were afraid of my Grandparents or they simply didn’t care. As for the latter, they simply thought that the Young Master could never revive the previous might of the Buda Clan. At that time, the Young Master has become a famous offender in the Empire. Moreover, the Young Master was very weak. Otherwise, Sister Ruyen wouldn’t have proposed to remove their engagement.”

When Ruyen heard Meg speak about her, she couldn’t help but turn red as she said, “Brother Hai’s reputation in the Aksu Empire is quite terrible at that time.”

Meg forced a smile and said, “Not only was it terrible, it was completely rotten to the core. The Young Master even wanted to rape me. But because of my resistance, he wasn’t able to succeed. Because of this, I was very afraid of him even after arriving at the Black Wasteland. I didn’t even had the courage to look him in the face.”

As soon as Meg said this, Laura and the others couldn’t help but gasp. They couldn’t imagine Zhao Hai to have such a phase. There was a huge contrast with the current Zhao Hai. It even seems like Meg was talking about two different people.

Meg looked at their expressions and knew what they were thinking. She smiled bitterly and said, “The Young Master was really like that. He only woke up several months after taking the Water of Nothingness. When he woke up, we had already reached the Black Wasteland. And ever since the Young Master woke up, he changed. He started to do things seriously and rarely made a joke. He was very good to us, and he was even very good to the slaves. Bestowing commoner status to the slaves was thought up by the Young Master. And now that the Young Master had the Space, the Buda Clan began to recover bit by bit. It can be said that without the Young Master and the Space, it would be impossible for us to reach the Divine Realm, Demon Realm, and other planes.”

Laura and the others nodded. All of them knew what happened after that. First of all, without Zhao Hai or the Space, the Ark Continent’s people would either be already dead or had become slaves. They would still be clueless about the infinite mysteries of the Divine Realm as well as the myriad magic beasts of the universe.

Meg grew up together with Zhao Hai, so she knew everything about Zhao Hai from infancy up to now. This was something that Laura and the others didn’t have. Since Laura and the others were now Zhao Hai’s wives, they would like to know everything about him, even the bad parts. If they knew more about Zhao Hai, then they would feel closer to him.

Laura and the others listened to Meg’s stories as though they were looking through a time long passed. After all, the present Zhao Hai and the past were completely different. They fell in love with the Zhao Hai in the present, not the past.

The group chatted for a while. After seeing that Zhao Hai was still asleep, they decided to retreat to their rooms and sleep. They were already used to such a life, only on Zhao Hai’s side would they feel comfortable.

However, Laura and the others didn’t expect Zhao Hai to be out for a long time. It took Zhao Hai three days and three nights before he managed to wake up.

Zhao Hai opened his eyes only to see that he was lying inside his room. Zhao Hai began to think about it and understood what happened. He stood up and moved his body. Although he was out for a long time, his body didn’t feel stiff.

After stretching his body, Zhao Hai walked out of his room. Upon going out, Zhao Hai heard the voices of Laura and the others. It seems like they were somewhat worried about him. After all, he was out for so long.

However, since Cai’er said that nothing was wrong, they weren’t too scared of the situation. Because of this, they were now in the living room, chatting merrily.

Chapter 1045: Small Heart

Laura and the others immediately saw Zhao Hai when he went out of his room. They had been paying close attention to the door, therefore they were quickly able to see that he was awake.

After the women greeted him, Zhao Hai looked at their expressions and couldn’t help but smile faintly, “What happened? How long was I asleep?”

Laura replied, “You’ve been out for three days and three nights. We didn’t expect you to pass out, but Meg told us that you will be alright.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “I didn’t expect that guy to pass a lot of things to me. It took me a long time to digest it, but I did get a small benefit.”

Laura stared, then she asked, “What benefit?”

Zhao Hai smiled before going to the sofa to sit. Laura and the others also sat down. After everyone has been settled, Zhao Hai turned to the monitor and said, “I reckon you already know about the origin on the giant heart, right? Just like what was depicted on the murals, the giant heart was a holy relic guarded by those humans.”

While Zhao Hai was looking through those murals, Laura and the others were also watching from the monitor. Naturally, they knew what Zhao Hai was talking about. They also understood the origin of the heart from those murals.

After looking at their expressions, Zhao Hai nodded before he continued, “The information I received is directly connected to the Underworld. From its formation up to its current state. Everything was because of the heart.”

These words evoked the curiosity of the women. They were eagerly listening to what Zhao Hai would say next. Zhao Hai went on, “You already know some of the things that happened at first. When that great god was born, the Underworld began to form. What happened to the great god’s heart was already painted on the murals. It was said that before placing his entire vitality into the giant heart, the person guarding the heart placed it in the bottom of this lake. Therefore, in the beginning, the heart could only take the lake water in. Nobody knew how many years have passed, but a spatial rift suddenly appeared in the Underworld. What came out of the spatial rift weren’t people, instead there were corpses. These were the corpses of the people from the Hundred Spirit Clan.”

Laura and the other stared, they didn’t expect the heart to remember these things. Zhao Hai looked at them and smiled faintly, “You shouldn’t underestimate the heart. After all, it is a heart of a world-creating god, his most important organ. Its uses are near infinite. Alright, let’s continue. As more and more corpses from the Hundred Spirit Clan fell into the Underworld, the death energy here became stronger and stronger. Because of this, the Dark Mist that wouldn’t dissipate began to form. Since the heart can absorb the power of the heavens and the earth, it extended two arteries out while being escorted by the creatures of the lake. These arteries became the two pillars. One of them extended out of the lake, sucking in Dark Mist while the other artery stretched out sideways from the lake. Slowly, the blood river formed as well as the blood ponds which supply blood energy to the Underworld.”

Zhao Hai stopped for a moment before continuing, “The Underworld’s development happened under the gaze of the giant heart. The heart is actually aware and intelligent. It thinks that the Dark Temple wouldn’t just unify the Underworld for no reason. In fact, it thinks that those from the Cultivation Realm were the people who ran away in the past. Also, that person from the Dark Temple was someone from the Cultivation Realm. Otherwise, they wouldn’t have thrown the corpses of the Hundred Spirit Clans here. There were still some people who remembered the story and still wanted to take the heart. Because of this, they established the Dark Temple in order to unify the Underworld and find the heart.”

Laura and the others stared at Zhao Hai. They didn’t expect the events to tie up like this. The things that Zhao Hai spoke about seems to be reasonable. In the past, they didn’t know anything about the Underworld, so they best they could do was speculate. But now it was different, Zhao Hai became aware of the Underworld’s matters because of the giant heart. After adding it to their speculation, they believed that they weren’t that far from the truth.

Megan discovered something from what Zhao Hai said. She looked at Zhao Hai and asked, “Brother Hai, didn’t you say that the heart can absorb the Dark Mist and transform it into Blood Energy? And it could also make blood energy from the energy of the heavens and the earth? If we can subdue the heart, then we would surely gain huge advantages.”

Zhao Hao nodded. Then he looked at the heart on the monitor before he sighed and shook his head, “We’re not short of good things right now. Moreover, the giant heart is a crucial component of the Underworld. If we take the heart away, then the Underworld would lose its blood energy. Who knows what will happen to the Undead and the Dark Creatures then.”

Megan and the others nodded. If it was any other place, then they wouldn’t mind taking the heart. However, the Underworld would become their back garden in the future. It wouldn’t be great if a disaster would happen to this place.

Zhao Hai looked at the others and smiled, “Although the heart doesn’t have its own wisdom, it can actually understand simply communication. I will tell it to not worry. It wouldn’t be great if it suffered a heart attack.”

After hearing Zhao Hai, Laura and the others couldn’t help but chuckle. They spent a long time inside the Space, and ever since the Science and Technology Backgrounds has been unlocked, they were able to know more about people from the Earth. They also knew things about heart attacks and so on. Therefore, they were able to understand Zhao Hai’s small joke.

Zhao Hai returned to the Underworld. From the information he received, he knew that this palace was called the Heart Cauldron Palace, it was specifically made to house the heart.

The reason why Zhao Hai didn’t take the heart to the Space was because his conscience didn’t allow him to. He was moved by the people who fervently defended the heart.

These people guarded the heart up to the very last man. Zhao Hai was touched by their persistence. He couldn’t bear to take the heart away from them.

Moreover, in addition to the information he obtained from the heart, he also received a plea to not move the heart. As long as Zhao Hai didn’t move the heart, then the heart would bestow the copper cauldron to him. This cauldron could refine living creatures, an example of this were the Blood Spirit Beasts.

The predecessor of the Blood Spirit Beasts was a magic beast known as soul octopus. After being refined by the copper cauldron, it turned into the Blood Spirit Beasts. Also, this cauldron was made by the heart’s defenders, it would definitely be a rare treasure.

In the eyes of other people, they would see that the heart had no attacking power, and that the Blood Spirit Beasts were unable to enter the palace. And since this was the case, then people might have the idea of taking the cauldron and the heart away.

However, Zhao Hai didn’t think the same way. He was affected by the heart’s defenders. Also, the heart wasn’t very useful to him. The heart takes in the energy of the heavens and the earth and transform it into blood energy, Zhao Hai thinks that this wasn’t an ordinary ability. Therefore, Zhao Hai didn’t think about absorbing the heart into the Space.

Zhao Hai arrived by the giant heart, he gave it a gentle stroke as he said, “You can stay here. Since the cauldron is useful to me, I will be taking it away. Rest assured, I won’t let anybody harm you.”

After he said that, Zhao Hai let go. Just as he was about to head towards the copper cauldron, the entire hall suddenly vibrated. Zhao Hai stared, then he immediately erected a protective shield around him as well as the heart. But not long after that, he was met with a huge shock. Right below the heart was another heart, albeit this one was much smaller, about normal size. Moreover, this small heart was beating with more vigor than the giant heart.

Zhao Hai carefully looked at the small heart. At this time, the small heart shot out from the ground and headed towards Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai felt a red light flash before the small heart entered his body.

While Zhao Hai was startled, he suddenly felt a comfortable feeling in his own chest. Then Zhao Hai felt that his heart’s beat had become more powerful. His absorption of the heaven and earth’s energy has also increased, his body became more formidable as well. This made Zhao Hai very confused.

Then at this moment, a white light shot out from the heart. Zhao Hai knew that this was another string of information, therefore he had the five element killing formation let the light through.

Just like Zhao Hai thought, the white light was another batch of information. Moreover, it explained the origin of the small heart and why Zhao Hai felt his body growing stronger.

Chapter 1046: Inheritance and the Universal Processing Machine’s Upgrade

In fact, this wasn’t really that strange. Although the heart didn’t have any wisdom, it can still think for itself.

It had a purpose every intelligent lifeform needed to accomplish, and that was to pass on their inheritance, to continue their bloodline

Humanity was also like this. In order to pass on their wisdom, they invented writing. Other races had their own methods of continuing their line.

The giant heart was the same. Although it only had simple thinking, this didn’t mean that it didn’t have a desire to continue its bloodline. This small heart was a means to this desire.

Since the heart was just an organ, in a normal situation, it wouldn’t have any means of multiplying. However, the giant heart was an organ from a great god. Naturally, it had formidable abilities. It can record events, just like a computer that runs automatically.

Later on, when the last generation of protectors sent his last vitality into the heart, he also passed down some knowledge over to the heart. Because of this, the giant heart had some knowledge of its own, naturally it still couldn’t be as smart as the other races.

What was the strongest wish of the heart’s last defender? He wanted to continue his bloodline. Unfortunately, he was the only living human in the Underworld, so that was impossible to accomplish. However, this obsession was passed over to the giant heart. Because of this, the heart also had the idea of continuing its lineage.

The organ of a great god was something unusual. Although the wisdom of the heart wasn’t good, it still acted on its instinct and developed a method of reproduction, which was division.

The giant heart split itself into two and made a smaller version of its own form. This small heart had all the abilities of its parent. Unfortunately, this small heart didn’t have any intellect. Because of this, the giant heart didn’t produce a lot. At the same time, it also made measures in order to protect itself.

This was also the desire of the last defender. Because of this, the heart made several layers of tests. The first one were the Blood Spirit Beasts. If one cannot defeat them, then arriving at the palace was completely impossible. The second test was the tsunami of information to see if they can handle the mental pressure. If Zhao Hai wasn’t able to digest it, then he wouldn’t be able to interact with the heart.

If these two tests were passed, then the next was a trial for greed. The heart would express its request to not move it while handing the copper cauldron over. But if one was greedy and decided to take both the heart and the cauldron, then they would be met with misfortune. The copper cauldron would proceed to attack you. The cauldron’s attacking method was unusual, it would eat you up and immediately refine you. The copper cauldron was a treasure of the heart’s defenders. After many years of worship, it had become a top grade magic treasure. If the defenders were afraid of strong enemies, then they wouldn’t have placed the copper cauldron here.

However, if you didn’t take the heart and let it stay here in peace, then it would give you the copper cauldron as well as the little heart. That small heart was split from the heart of a great god. It could purify blood, improve one’s absorption of energy, widen one’s meridians, and many more.

After the heart entered Zhao Hai’s body, it replaced Zhao Hai’s original heart. Because of this, Zhao Hai gained the inheritance of the defenders of the heart. Only by having this inheritance would Zhao Hai not be attacked by the copper cauldron. At the same time, the Blood Spirit Beasts would no longer attack him. On the contrary, Zhao Hai can now command the Blood Spirit Beasts. This was because Zhao Hai was now the new defender of the heart.

This inheritance was the same as what Zhao Hai was expecting. The defenders of the heart were the original controllers of this plane. They left behind a lot of treasures as well as their cultivation methods and techniques. They weren’t any weaker than any cultivation sect. It can be said that the heart’s defenders were no weaker than the Hundred Spirit Clan. But when the war happened, this place became a cemetery. Slowly, the place turned into the current Underworld. Although the laws of the plane haven’t changed, it was completely different to what it was before.

But even so, the true inheritance of the heart’s defenders wasn’t in the giant heart, instead it was the copper cauldron. If Zhao Hai was greedy, not only would he fail to gain the inheritance, but he would also be refined by the cauldron. Now, since Zhao Hai has absorbed the small heart, the copper cauldron has recognized him as its new master.

Another shot of white light told Zhao Hai everything about the cauldron. Upon understanding its function, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but wipe a cold sweat. Although he wasn’t afraid of being refined by the cauldron, it would still be troublesome to solve.

After thinking about this, Zhao Hai let out a sigh. It was truly great to have good morals. If he was greedy, then he would have been in great trouble, and he wouldn’t have inherited the legacy of the heart’s defenders.

Zhao Hai sighed as he rubbed his left chest and said, “Since you have bestowed me a heart, then I will take on the task of guarding you. Rest assured, in the Underworld, I promise that nobody would be able to touch you. Even those from the Dark Temple wouldn’t be able to do anything. I will clean them all up.”

The giant heart seemed to be happy as it gave out a few quick beats. Then Zhao Hai took the copper cauldron before he returned to the Space.

The events that happened with the small heart and the cauldron were all seen by Laura and the others. However, they weren’t aware of most of what happened. What they saw was the small heart flying towards Zhao Hai. Then when they saw a white light going to Zhao Hai’s head, they couldn’t help but worry. But after seeing Zhao Hai open his eyes once more, they instantly became relieved.

When Zhao Hai returned, the women immediately greeted him. Laura had an expression of worry as she asked, “Brother Hai, what happened?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “It’s fine. Rest assured, nothing else other than something good happened.” Then he told the women about the heart’s inheritance.

As soon as they heard it, Laura and the others became happy. They didn’t expect that they would acquire something good. They actually obtained an inheritance of a race.

Zhao Hai looked at the group and said, “Alright, I still need to sort the inheritance that I’ve obtained. You should go and busy yourself. After I organize everything, I’ll see what treasures we have obtained, I don’t know whether we can use them right now or not.”

Laura and the others nodded. What Zhao Hai said was true, so they naturally wouldn’t object. After that, Zhao Hai turned his hand over and retrieved the copper cauldron. Just as Zhao Hai took out the copper cauldron, the Space suddenly issued a prompt, “Special treasure refining cauldron detected. Refining Cauldron has been found with the ability to refine a lot of items. Since the cauldron’s ability is close to the Universal Processing Machine, abilities of the cauldron has been copied and augmented to the Processing Machine. Universal Processing Machine has been upgraded. Special ability of the copper cauldron has also been joined with the Blood Ghost Staff. The Blood Ghost Staff can now use similar abilities as the treasure cauldron.”

Zhao Hai blankly listened to the prompt. He didn’t expect the cauldron to upgrade the Processing Machine. Moreover, the cauldron’s abilities has been fused with the staff. This was truly a good thing for Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai originally felt pity. This was because the cauldron was too useful for himself, but at the same time, he also knew that it would be more useful if the cauldron was in Wild Dragon Island. If Zhao Hai used the cauldron, then the people from Wild Dragon Island wouldn’t be able to use it. Who would’ve expected that the Space would solve this problem. Now Zhao Hai can use the cauldron’s abilities from his staff while the original cauldron was left behind on Wild Dragon Island.

At this moment, the Universal Processing Machine suddenly emitted light. After the light vanished, there was an evident change to the Processing Machine.

Originally, the Processing Machines were separated into ten structures, they didn’t look attractive. But now it was different. The ten structures vanished and was replaced by a huge factory. In front of the factory were ten magic formations. Then on the other side were another set of ten formations. It seems like if one wanted to refine something in the future, then they would just have to put the items on the formation and then the factory would just refine them itself.

Upon seeing the structure, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but think ‘Now this is a factory’. The structure was five storeys high. It had white outer walls that were embedded with glass windows. Its form wasn’t anything different than the small workshop from before. However, when people look at it now, they wouldn’t think about a factory but instead a beautiful building.

Zhao Hai went to the Processing Machine in order to take a closer look. Then he turned his head to Cai’er and said, “Cai’er, what can we do with the Processing Machine now?”

Cai’er pulled out a pile of paper before she said, “Young Master, this is the manual, you should take a look.”

Zhao Hai received the manual and gave it a read. The Processing Machine had truly been upgraded. Not only could it process non-living things, but it can also process living creatures. If Zhao Hai wanted the Argali to live longer, then he could just send one through to the Processing Machine in order to improve its genes.

Not only this. In the past, if Zhao Hai received a sword that he didn’t want to use, then he wouldn’t be able to do anything about it. Now, if Zhao Hai didn’t want to use a sword, then he could send it through the processing machine in order to restore the sword or augment it with other ores. This made things much more convenient.

Chapter 1047: World-Creating Merit Law

It can be said that the current Universal Processing Machine has become more powerful. The machine can now process living beings, which was a very formidable ability.

The new Processing Machine had lost its controls, instead it was replaced by voice commands. If Zhao Hai wanted something to be made, then he can just present the materials to the machine and tell it what to do.

Although there were still ten magic formations in front of the Processing Machine, its output actually increased by about five times. Before, one Processing Machine can make 5000 jin of liquor, ten of them would make 50,000 jin. But now, the Processing Machine can make 250 thousand jin of liquor. The difference in output was very huge.

After understanding the Processing Machine’s function, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but nod. The Processing Machine couldn’t make living things and could just improve them. But even so, it was very great. It’s just a pity that he didn’t know how to upgrade the Scanner.

Zhao Hai looked at the Processing Machine before he turned to Laura and said, “Now that the Processing Machine has so many functions, we shouldn’t waste it. Laura, see if you can find ways for the Processing Machine to improve the animals in the Space. Those we use for meat needed to live longer and grow larger. Those used for combat should become much stronger.”

Laura nodded, “Rest assured, Brother Hai, I know what to do. Not only the animals, we should also improve the plants. The Bread Tree can be improved so that it would produce more fruit.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he turned to Cai’er and said, “Cai’er, before helping with this matter, come with me first. I need to record all of the inheritance that the Heart Defending Clan had passed down. We’ll pass them over to the people inside the Space. The people inside the Space are still quite weak. If we went to the Cultivation Realm, they wouldn’t be able to help out much.”[1]

Cai’er gave a nod before she followed Zhao Hai. Meanwhile, Laura and the others studied the Processing Machine. The group looked at the machine’s manual to come up with ways to optimize its uses for the Space.

Zhao Hai returned to his room and immediately sat down in a cross-legged position. The Heart Defending Clan were able to fight against the people from the Cultivation Realm. In fact, a lot of the cultivation methods of the Cultivation Realm came from the people depicted in the mural. It can be said that the cultivation methods of the Heart Defending Clan were the roots of most of the Cultivation Realm’s manuals.

The inheritance that Zhao Hai acquired contains almost all of the methods used by the Heart Defending Clan. And most of these methods had the outline of the World-creating merit law, which was an incomparably powerful law.

The World Creating Merit Law was the most important cultivation method of the Heart-defending Clan. This cultivation method was developed after nine years of contemplation regarding the World-creating god’s feat. This method can be said to be the first method of the Heart-defending Clan.

The World-Creating Merit law had about 2000 characters. However, each character needed very difficult deliberation in order to be fully understood.

As time went by, Zhao Hai felt that the World Creating Merit Law and the Yin Yang Stellar Transformations art had common aspects. This caused Zhao Hai to become more careful as he read on.

Zhao Hai seemed to be in a wondrous state. He closed his eyes and kept understanding the merit law. The stellar transformations art seem to involuntarily rotate inside his body. Each revolution became smoother and smoother with each iteration. In the beginning, things seem to be unclear, but after this event things seem to become more and more transparent. Zhao Hai had benefited a lot.

Unaware of how long it has been, after in a daze for some time, Zhao Hai woke up from his wondrous state. He slowly opened his eyes before breathing out some foul gas. Then he turned to Cai’er who was beside him and said, “Cai’er, how long have I been sitting?”

Cai’er woke up, her face red before she answered, “Young Master, you’ve been sitting for two days.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he suddenly felt an intense urge to vomit. Zhao Hai couldn’t help but stare for a moment before running straight to the bathroom. Then he vomited some purplish black liquid straight into the toilet.

The purplish black liquid that Zhao Hai spat out smelled rancid. It had the same scent as decayed blood.

Cai’er saw Zhao Hai’s vomit and was terrified. She knew that it was impossible for people with Zhao Hai’s strength to get sick. She thought that Zhao Hai was injured. With the color drained from her face, she asked, “Young Master, what happened? Did you get sick?”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “I didn’t. I just had some breakthrough in cultivation. And with my new heart expelling bad blood, it’s just right for me to vomit some impurities.”

When she heard Zhao Hai say this, Cai’er felt relieved. Zhao Hai washed his mouth until he got rid of the rancid taste. At the same time, he also felt the unprecedented strength of his spirit. His body had also become more powerful. He also seemed to develop a new scent. It wasn’t strong, just mellow. And although it was also quite thick, it wasn’t overpowering. It was a scent that made people feel refreshed.

Zhao Hai knew that these things were because of the heart. However, he didn’t expect to develop a scent. To be honest, Zhao Hai has always been apprehensive about men using perfume. He didn’t think that his body would emit a scent, it made him somewhat annoyed.

Zhao Hai sighed, then he turned to Cai’er and said, “Cai’er, record it well. This World Creating Merit Law is the ancestor of most Cultivation Methods….. There is an energy that can create worlds. The energy of the heavens and the earth is found in one’s breath. The breath of the heavens and the earth is the Yin and Yang. The breath of yin-yang is the world. The heart is a mirror that reflects the universe. The body’s flesh and blood is the ocean. Breath in the sea and breath out an ocean…….”

Cai’er kept record of all these words. Before long, the entire World Creating Merit Law’s 2000 characters have been recorded. Zhao Hai breathed deeply and said, “Cai’er, this is the origin of most cultivation records. Make sure to preserve this well. When the time comes, we’ll place this World Creating Merit Law in our major academies for them to study. In the future, this cultivation method would be the Space’s foundation.”

Cai’er nodded. There was a reason why Zhao Hai wanted to set up the World Creating Merit Law in the academies. Although the Merit Law was quite profound, its words can be easily understood. Only people on Zhao Hai’s level could understand the law’s deepest meanings. Therefore, Zhao Hai was not afraid that people couldn’t learn this law.

After reading the merit law, Zhao Hai began to go through the other cultivation methods of the Heart Defending Clan. He wanted to add methods for the Space’s people to improve. Naturally, Zhao Hai would test these methods first before putting them out.

There Heart Defending Clan didn’t have a lot of cultivation methods. All in all, there were about 300 of them. Some of them were quite profound, and it also indicated what strength one should have so that they wouldn’t suffer backlash. Although Zhao Hai made Cai’er record these things, he wasn’t planning on putting all of them on the Academies. Even if the students wanted to study these methods, it wouldn’t be good if they were harmed.

After hearing Zhao Hai recount all of the cultivation methods, Cai’er had recorded 360 all in all. However, these were only cultivation methods, there were still crafting methods, medicine concoction techniques, and even formations inside Zhao Hai’s head. These things were precious resources from the Heart Defending Clan. Naturally, Zhao Hai wouldn’t put them to waste and recorded them all.

When everything has been written down, Zhao Hai told Cai’er to send some of them to the Academies. As for the more profound records, they were sent to Wild Dragon Island.

While Zhao Hai was dealing with these things, ten days have passed. These past ten days has been quite stressful for him. Besides the sheer number of things needed to be recorded, the profundity of each of them wasn’t making it easier.

Upon heading out from his room, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but stare since he expected Laura and the others to be in the living room. However, Zhao Hai changed his mind when he realized that the women were currently studying the Processing Machine.

Laura used to be a formidable businesswoman. So after finding out about the new uses of the Processing Machine, she put her all into studying the possibilities. She wanted to find ways to improve the plants and animals in order to maximize their benefits to the Space.

Among the things that needed to be improved, the most important one were the Argali. At this point, the Argali were the most eaten animal inside the Space. Not only was their meat tasty, they were also very docile. At the same time, their wool, skin, and bones were very useful. It was the magic beast that people inside the Space liked the most.

The Argali weren’t small, but Laura still wanted them to be bigger. After the modification, the Argali were now as big as a cow. This chang didn’t affect their taste nor their temperament. The modification also wouldn’t bring harm to the consumer’s body. It can be said that the Argali were optimized up to the genes.

Laura and the others also made modifications to the other farm animals inside the Space. Just these beasts were enough to occupy them for a while. Not to mention, they still needed to modify the grains and vegetables.

Sure enough, when Zhao Hai came out of the villa, he was able to see Laura and the others right beside the Processing Machine. They had a set of things in front of them. Zhao Hai looked at it and they were all kinds of plant seeds.

Zhao Hai walked over to the group. But since the women were too invested in the discussion, they weren’t able to sense him at all. Zhao Hai stood there looked at them, their faces seem to be very busy.

He gave the task of studying the Processing Machine over to Laura and the others because he wanted them to have something to busy themselves with. Actually, Zhao Hai expected them to be extremely bored, he didn’t expect them to sink deep into the task. After seeing Laura and the others concentrating deeply on the job, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but feel ignored.

But then, Laura suddenly stopped. She sniffed the air and said, “What is this smell? Did anyone of you put on any perfume?”

Lizzy and the others shook their heads. Zhao Hai scratched his head, he really didn’t know what to say. At this time, Meg turned and saw Zhao Hai. She was immediately surprised, “Young Master, you’re here.”

As soon as they heard Meg’s quip, Laura and the others immediately noticed Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai looked at them and smiled, “You guys are really concentrating on the job. You didn’t even notice me. I’ve been here for some time.”

Laura and the others spat out their tongues. They were indeed too busy on the Processing Machine. To be honest, they were secretly excited about the job.

Laura sniffed the air with her nose as she said, “Brother Hai, what smell is that? Are you using perfume?”

Zhao Hai forced a smile and said, “I don’t even know what scent this is. I don’t wear perfume, I don’t like that stuff. It’s because of that little heart. Now that it had become my new heart, it expelled impurities from by body. Then I suddenly had this scent.”

Laura sneaked closer into Zhao Hai’s body and smelled him. Then she nodded and said, “You really smell nice. It makes people feel comfortable. Right, Brother Hai, these are the things we are currently working on.” Then she pointed at the things in front of her.

Zhao Hai looked at the seeds, he nodded and said, “What seed is this?”

Laura smiled and said, “It’s nothing special. These are seeds of leafy vegetables. We want to improve them, but making leafy vegetables bigger would make their veins harder. In that case, it wouldn’t be good to eat. We’re still thinking of ways to do this.”

Zhao Hai nodded. These seeds seem to be cole crops. They’re very good to eat and they’re quite tasty as well. However, they grow too little. Laura and the others wanted to make them even bigger.

Zhao Hai smiled and then said, “Alright, I think we should just let it go. If we make them too big, we’ll be changing their taste. We don’t really need bigger cabbages. Let’s take a rest. Meg, can you arrange something delicious for us? These past few days made me very hungry.”

Meg nodded before turning around to leave. Laura seemed to not care about what Zhao Hai said. She still placed the seeds into the magic formation and then put forward  a bunch of parameters. In the end, the Processing Machine spat out new seeds. Although they had yet to see the seed’s true plant, Laura just placed a label on it before throwing it over to the Space’s warehouse.

After everything was finished, everyone returned to the living room. At this time, Meg had already prepared the meals. Each person had steak and lettuce. Zhao Hai looked at the food and couldn’t help but frown a bit. He seldom ate steak and Meg rarely made it. They usually ate chinese cuisine, he didn’t expect Meg to cook steak today.

After seeing Zhao Hai’s expression, Meg smiled and said, “Young Master, taste it. The steak came from our improved cows. The vegetables and spices used are new as well.”

Upon hearing Meg, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but pat his head. It seems like the food has been improved.

* * *

I changed heart’s defenders to Heart Defending Clan

Chapter 1048: Treasure Hunt

After eating their meal, Zhao Hai pulled Meg over to relax in the hot spring, amidst the teasing coming from Laura and the others. Then the women proceeded to return to the Processing Machine.

Zhao Hai had been very tired in the past few days. He had been reading the inheritance every day. In the end, he felt like he had read through two full brain’s worth of cultivation methods. If his spiritual force wasn’t that formidable, then Zhao Hai might have been taken over by a devil.

Now that everything has been recorded, naturally Zhao Hai needed to relax. And since Meg had an incredible massage technique, Zhao Hai brought her with him in the hot spring. The two had an affectionate bath together as a couple.

After having a good time with Meg in the hot spring, Zhao Hai laid on the spring’s flat stone, holding Meg in his arms. Meg was currently like an obedient kitten lying in Zhao Hai’s chest. It was a scene that made Meg look just like Zhao Hai’s wife. Normally, Meg would look like a servant and Zhao Hai was her Young Master.

While holding Meg, Zhao Hai talked with a soft voice, “Meg, I’m sorry. You’ve been silently following me for all these years. You’ve been taking care of our huge family without asking anything in exchange. I know that you have been working the hardest out of all of us. Thank you.”

Being in the arms of Zhao Hai, Meg felt that Zhao Hai’s words were as sweet as the sweetest drink. She whispered, “Young Master, these are all things I’m willing to do, so you don’t need to apologize. I know I’m not as smart as Sister Laura and the others, so as long as I’m able to take care of you, then I’m already happy.”

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but tighten his hold on Meg, then he replied, “Meg, your intelligence isn’t any less than Laura and the others. Moreover, your steadfast work is something that Laura and the others didn’t have. And if you want to do something else, just do it.”

Meg actually shook her head, “No, Young Master, I like my present life. I’d like to stay as it is until you are old, have trouble walking, or even stop wanting me.”

After Meg tightened her hold, Zhao Hai suddenly remembered a joke back on Earth when he still had the internet. It said that behind every successful man is a woman. However, that woman wasn’t his wife, but instead his mother-in-law. This was because his mother-in-law would always look after his faults. When the man corrects these mistakes, then he would be able to succeed.

At that time, Zhao Hai felt that although it was a joke, it actually made some sense. But now, Zhao Hai believed that this wasn’t the case at all. If a man had a woman like Meg by his side, then it would be difficult for them not to succeed.

Zhao Hai was very satisfied with his current life. Having Meg, Laura, and his other wives by his side made his life much more colorful.

Meg also felt that Zhao Hai’s love for her was genuine. She was similarly satisfied with her life.

Meg had known that she would be tied up with Zhao Hai for her entire lifetime. When Zhao Hai was still trash, she loved him, and now, she loved him even more.

Actually, Meg felt inferior compared to Laura and the others. Laura and the others were young ladies, one was even a princess. It was only Meg who had the status of a servant. Because of this, she couldn’t help but feel less than them.

After lying inside for some time, Meg and Zhao Hai went out of the hot spring. Outside the villa, Zhao Hai saw Laura and the others being busy. He didn’t say anything and just took out some small furniture and drank some tea.

Laura and the others were busy while Zhao Hai was relaxing at the side, however, they weren’t angry at all. This was because they knew that they were also relaxing during the times where Zhao Hai was working hard. It can be said that the person with the most things to do inside the Space was Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai rested inside the Space for three days. After three days, his soul has been completely relaxed. In this span of time, Laura and the others were very busy improving all of the Space’s crops. As Zhao Hai thought, they were secretly enjoying the job.

After three days, Zhao Hai finally recovered. He was now ready to claim the treasures of the Heart Defending Clan. The clan had dominated the Underworld for countless years. Their accumulation of wealth was truly rich. If not for the ones who wanted to snatch the heart, they still would have control over the place.

Now, the Underworld has been destroyed, even the laws of the plane seems to have changed a little. This was the reason why the Experts here were much stronger than the ones in the Divine Realm and in the Atlanta Plane. At the same time, this also explains why there are no genuine Cultivation-realm experts present in this plane.

Zhao Hai dug into the memories that the giant heart had passed on to him. After carefully scanning through them, Zhao Hai finally found something. When the last defender died, the laws of the plane seems to have changed. Part of the reason was the extinction of the Heart Defending Clan, another part was because the Cultivation Realm used the plane as a cemetery when they dumped all of the corpses here, and then another part was because of the giant heart.

The giant heart had simple wisdom. It knew that if it let the Cultivation Realm’s people come into the Underworld whenever they want, then it would be in danger. Sooner or later, the Cultivation Realm would discover where it was hiding. Because of this, the giant heart slowly changed the laws of the plane.

One shouldn’t think that this was a difficult matter. This plane was originally made by the great god. And since the giant heart was the god’s most important organ, it naturally had the ability to control the plane. Although this ability wasn’t much, and the giant heart couldn’t make abrupt changes, it could nudge the Underworld’s laws bit by bit into the direction it wanted it to be in. At this point, overly powerful people would find it impossible to enter the plane.

After finding out about this situation, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but feel relieved. At the same time, he couldn’t help but sigh. In the past, the Underworld was surely not at this state. This place used to be occupied by cultivators, who would believe that it would reach such a state?

But looking at it now, the whole place was ruined. One must say that humans had an inborn tendency to destroy.

Zhao Hai wasn’t planning on restoring the Underworld to its original state. At the very least, not now. With his current strength, it was impossible for him to protect the Underworld. If he restored the Underworld to its original appearance, then the people from the Cultivation Realm would surely come over. Zhao Hai still has no grasp on how to defeat these people.

According to what Zhao Hai got from the giant heart, if he wanted to acquire all the buried treasure of the Heart Defending Clan, then he would have to face some difficulties. This was because a large part of the clan’s buried treasure lay under the Dark Temple’s territory.

Fortunately, this didn’t have any conflict with Zhao Hai’s plans. He would have to deal with the Dark Temple anytime soon. In any case, the buried treasure had been there for many years. If it can be stolen, then it would have already been stolen a long time ago. If it was still intact, then a few more days wouldn’t be able to change anything.

Zhao Hai decided to clear the treasures buried in the Resistance Army’s lands first. The Heart Defending Clan buried five treasures in the Resistance Army’s domain. These treasures weren’t very valuable, they were just some ores.

According to the information obtained from the giant heart, the first treasure was supposed to be buried under a bone mountain. The huge battle in the Underworld had drastically changed its terrain. Fortunately, now that the Space has mapped the Resistance Army’s territory, Zhao Hai could follow the giant heart’s tips to mark a rough location on the map. It was much better than nothing at all.

After looking for a while, Zhao Hai found the bone mountain. The bone mountain wasn’t that tall, it was just average in height compared to the others. There were low-ranked skeletons sauntering on the mountain. Zhao Hai didn’t care about them as he summoned the blood lotus and went straight underground.

Once he reached 100 meters underground, Zhao Hai stopped. The first treasure room was in the vicinity. Inside were unique ores from the original Underworld. According to the giant heart, this ore seems to be ores used for medicinal purposes. One can extract liquid from the ore using a special method. If the liquid was drunk directly, it would improve the strength and defense of the human body. If it was mixed into other components, then it would be an effective potion.

Judging by Zhao Hai’s computation, he knew that the treasure room should be in this bone mountain. As for the specific position, it still needed some time to figure out.

Since this was the case, Zhao Hai could only roam the bone mountain’s underground hoping to come across the treasure room. Naturally, Zhao Hai didn’t go about this blindly. He was looking at the Space’s monitor that was marking his path, this way he wouldn’t explore the same region twice.

Zhao Hai wasn’t anxious. After all, this was something that required patience. He also prepared himself mentally for this. He continued to slowly explore using the blood lotus. He believed that the Space’s abilities wouldn’t fail him.

After one hour of exploration, Zhao Hai suddenly felt that the soil in front of him had a slight difference in quality. Zhao Hai immediately slowed down before looking at it really carefully. The soil did indeed have some changes.

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but be more attentive. As he slowly moved forward, a flat piece of rock suddenly appeared in front of him. He stopped and inspected the piece of rock. When he found traces of something on it, Zhao Hai’s heart couldn’t help but skip a beat. He knew that he had found the place.

To be honest, this treasure wasn’t that important for Zhao Hai. However, the prospect of discovering treasures still made Zhao Hai very excited.

Zhao Hai carefully maneuvered the blood lotus around the rock. The rock was about two meters thick and seemed to be very hard. However, this wasn’t a problem for him. Zhao Hai just flew through the rock and entered a huge stone room. And as soon as he entered the room, Zhao Hai was immediately stunned.

Chapter 1049: Luring the Tiger Out of the Mountain

Inside was a huge space. Zhao Hai made some estimations and this place should be no less than ten thousand square meters in floor area. There were no other things inside this place other than the stones that were piled up like a hill.

Naturally, the size wasn’t the thing that surprised Zhao Hai. What surprised Zhao Hai were the shining stones. They gave out a gloomy blue radiance, they looked beautifully mysterious.

The stones weren’t transparent, but they were faintly blue. Zhao Hai stared at them, he didn’t think that stones would be this beautiful.

Zhao Hai’s first thought when he saw these stones wasn’t to use them for medicinal purposes. Instead, he wanted to use them to make street lights.

Zhao Hai didn’t know how his mind comes up with these things. When he was in the middle of business, these thoughts suddenly come up, which were quite strange.

After staring for a moment, Zhao Hai took all of the blue stone into the Space. In this huge room, there was nothing else aside from those stones.

Zhao Hai left the room and slowly flew back to the ground. Upon resurfacing, Zhao Hai discovered that the treasure was buried right below the foot of the bone mountain.

Zhao Hai didn’t say anything and just returned to the Space. Then he continued to move towards the next treasure. With the Space’s ability, it didn’t take long before Zhao Hai collected all five treasures.

Once he collected all of the five treasures, Zhao Hai was finally able to continue to the next step. These five treasure rooms gave Zhao Hai a lot. Naturally, what he gained were only some ores.

According to the giant heart, there were a total of 22 treasures in the Dark Temple’s Domain. Most of these treasures were magic artifacts. It can be said that these were the true treasure of the Heart Defending Clan.

What Zhao Hai needed the most right now were these magic artifacts. Although he already had the Blood Ghost Staff, nobody would disagree to having more magical items. Zhao Hai didn’t want to use these magic artifacts. After he collects these treasures, he was prepared to send them to the people in the Space. The Blood Ghost Staff was already enough for him to use.

Zhao Hai called Addison and the others to the Space. They were becoming impatient lately. Now that Zhao Hai called them over, they immediately came.

After Addison and the others arrived, Zhao Hai looked at them and smiled, “What’s the problem? Worried? Don’t worry, we’ll be making our move.”

Addison’s two eyes shone, “Young Master, have you captured the Blood Spirit Beasts? Have you already mapped the Dark Temple’s domain?”

Zhao Hai gave a gentle nod. Then he waved his hand, showing the map of the Dark Temple’s territory on the monitor. The blood needles had succeeded in mapping the Dark Temple’s area. Zhao Hai was also introduced to the Underworld’s ocean.

The Underworld had an ocean with water that was very black. This body of water was different than the blood river. Once an undead or any creature tries to swim in the ocean’s waters, they would immediately be swallowed in, not even their fiery souls would remain.

Zhao Hai also decided to take some of this water into the Space. However, the prompt only said that it was an extremely toxic liquid that had the power to swallow everything. Also, it seems like it could also be used for making weapons.

Zhao Hai didn’t know how big this ocean was. However, Zhao Hai has to recognize the size of the Underworld judging by how big the Dark Temple’s territory was. The Dark Temple alone held territory almost the size of five Taurus Continents. Naturally, with land that size, it was impossible for the Dark Temple to gain complete control over it. There were still some Undead in the territory who loved their freedom and were still resisting control. But compared to the Resistance Army, these groups were just like two or three kittens. They simply didn’t have enough power to move the current status quo.

Zhao Hai pointed at the Dark Temple’s map and said, “This is the territory of the Dark Temple. The red areas are completely controlled by them while the green have yet to be managed. There’s still some resistance forces in the green areas, but their strength is very poor.”

When Addison heard this, his eyes shone. He looked at the huge expanse of red on the monitor, then he looked at the green spots. With a confused voice he asked, “Young Master, so you’re saying that there are still some resistance forces inside the Dark Temple’s territory? Why didn’t we know of this before?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “How would you know when you’re separated by the huge land of the Dark Temple? There’s no way for you to contact each other, so it’s natural that you would be unaware of them.”

Addison nodded. He didn’t say anything more as he closely looked at the map. The domain controlled by the Dark Temple was very huge. And in the middle of it was the Dark Temple itself.

After inspecting the map, Addison and the others looked back at Zhao Hai. Seeing their gazes, Zhao Hai said, “Prepare everyone, in a while I will be taking them to the Space. Tomorrow we will officially attack the Dark Temple, our main goal will be the Temple itself.”

When Addison and the others heard this, they couldn’t help but feel excited. Zhao Hai waved his hand and sent everybody out, making them prepare the army.

Actually, there was no need for them to prepare the army since Zhao Hai can just take all of them into the Space. However, Zhao Hai wanted to see how they would coordinate groups.

A well-trained army was much stronger than an untrained group. These days, Zhao Hai not only made Experts, he also trained the Undead. He wanted to use this time in order to check the result of their training.

Frankly speaking, the training time has been too short. Therefore, the results weren’t satisfying. At the very least, Zhao Hai was still not satisfied. The army was still very vulnerable.

The Undead in the Underworld were different from those in the Ark Continent or in the Divine Realm. In the Underworld, the Undead were born as an Undead, then they were subdued by the Space. On the other hand, the Undead from the Ark Continent and the Divine Realm were reanimated corpses using magic. Zhao Hai could completely control these Undead. This was even true for those Undead who had wisdom. If Zhao Hai wanted to, he could control them as though they were his puppets.

But for the Underworld’s Undead, Zhao Hai didn’t have complete control. Zhao Hai can order them directly to fight, but they weren’t as easy to control compared to the other Undead.

However, this didn’t mean that these Undead weren’t just taken by Zhao Hai and placed inside the Space. He trained those he can train. Now, they were easier to use. Zhao Hai basically had complete control over them.

After sending Addison and the others away, Zhao Hai called Lizzy and Megan over. Laura and the others were still busy with the Processing Machine. It was as though they were children that were handed new toys to play with.

When Lizzy and Megan arrived at the villa and saw the map on the screen, they immediately understood what was going to happen. They found a place to sit and stared at the map.

Zhao Hai looked at them and said, “We shall attack the Dark Temple tomorrow. I don’t plan to whittle them down this time. We will attack their core. As long as we take care of the Dark Temple, everything would be easier to deal with.”

Lizzy looked at the map, then after some time she said, “This is a good idea, but the Dark Temple’s defense is very strict. It wouldn’t be easy to attack them directly. There are also a lot of strongholds around them that could provide support in a short time. I think we should find a way to get lure those troops out of the temple.”

Megan also gave a nod, “I agree. The Dark Temple has too many defenders. There aren’t too many rules in their defense, but their numbers can provide some problems. However, judging by the previous clash between the Resistance Army and the Dark Temple, the temple seems to be unable to use army formations. Also, there seems to be no hierarchy in their army. So I think that if we lure the defenders out, just like Sister Lizzy said, the invasion would become much easier.”

Zhao Hai stared, then he thought for a moment and said, “I like this method. We’ll divide the army into two teams. Megan, you come with me to command the team that will attack the Dark Temple. Lizzy, you go with Addison and the others to cross the Blood River and attract the Dark Temple’s attention. Once the defenders are thinned out, it would become more convenient for us to do our attack.”

Laura and Megan gave a nod, then Zhao Hai added, “I will order the Blood Spirit Beasts to coordinate with Lizzy. Lizzy, if things go wrong, don’t hesitate to immediately withdraw. Do not go at them hard. Drag them over to the Blood River. With this, we would have more chances to succeed.”

Lizzy nodded, “Brother Hai, rest assured, I know what to do. You need to be careful of that person in the Dark Temple. He surely wouldn’t be easy to deal with.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Don’t worry. Even if I cannot kill him, I can still escape.”

Lizzy and Megan chuckled. Then the three proceeded to iron out their plan on how to deal with the Dark Temple. In this campaign, Lizzy and the others needed to constrain the Dark Temple in the Blood River. Moreover, they needed to delay the enemy for several days. Once the Dark Temple sends their reserves, only then would Zhao Hai’s group make a move.

Chapter 1050: Fortress

Addison stood beside the Blood River. He knew Zhao Hai’s plan and to be honest, he approved of it. He experienced Zhao Hai’s decapitation strategies, it was when they were dealing with the Five Element Skeletons and the Gibbon Brothers. With this strategy, they would shorten the time to conquer the Dark Temple.

Looking at the blood red body of water, Addison’s heart was on fire. They would finally start their true battle against the Dark Temple.

Although Addison and the others were now completely loyal to Zhao Hai, they still haven’t forgotten about their hatred towards the Dark Temple. They couldn’t help but feel happy now that this opportunity has arrived.

At this time, Zhao Hai appeared right by Addison’s side. Addison felt Zhao Hai’s presence, so he immediately bowed and said, “Young Master, we’ve gathered everyone. When do we make a move?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “We move now.” Then he waved his hand, the water on the river suddenly formed a bridge. The bridge was a couple meters wide and it stretched across the whole span of the river.

Zhao Hai proceeded to beckon towards the bridge and said, “Those who can fly, fly over. Those who cannot, walk through the bridge. Make a formation on the other side.”

Addison responded with an affirming grunt. Then although the Undead were still afraid of the Blood River, they still went to the other side.

Actually, Zhao Hai could just send them all instantly to the other side. However, Zhao Hai didn’t do so because he wanted the Dark Temple’s troops on the other side to see the approaching army.

Over the years, the Blood River has been the Resistance Army’s first line of defense against the Dark Temple. It was their most important line of defense. Also, in the past, the Resistance Army had tried to invade across the Blood River and they paid a huge price for it. If the Dark Temple’s troops saw how easily the Resistance Army crossed the river, they would know that it wouldn’t just be a simple attack.

The moment Addison and the others crossed the Blood River, the war had already begun. Psychological warfare, morale warfare, momentum warfare, all of these were critical to any army. One shouldn’t fail in establishing these aspects or else the war wouldn’t be good to you.

And sure enough, just like Zhao Hai thought, once Addison’s army gathered on the Blood River, the people on the other side immediately sensed them and then promptly sent a message back into the Dark Temple.

At the beginning, those Undead didn’t take this matter to heart. In their opinion, the Resistance Army didn’t have the strength to protect their lives in crossing the Blood River. Not to mention attacking them, the Resistance Army had to give their all in surviving. They didn’t believe that Addison’s army would have the strength left to pose a threat.

But much to their surprise, a bridge suddenly appeared on top of the Blood River. Then after that, in a relaxed manner, the Resistance Army just flew over the river. Nothing attacked them at all. This left the Dark Temple’s troops in a panicked state.

However, it was already too late for them to retreat. Although the Blood River wasn’t narrow, those who could fly could traverse the body of water in a short time. They didn’t leave any time for the Dark Temple’s troops to withdraw.

The Dark Temple’s troops immediately decided to defend. However, their numbers were too low. In almost an instant, they were overthrown by the Resistance Army.

But even though they were destroyed, the Dark Temple’s troops were still able to pass the situation back. Naturally, Zhao Hai knew about this outcome, and he had a way to stop it. The other party’s spiritual force wasn’t that strong, and the message would still have to go through a long distance. If Zhao Hai wanted to stop it, he can use his own spiritual force to intercept the message. But Zhao Hai didn’t do so since he wanted the Dark Temple to transfer some troops to stop the Resistance Army’s advance.

At this time, Zhao Hai and the others had arrived on the opposite shore. Addison looked at the lands that they had stepped upon. Although it was the same soil as the other side of the river, Addison and the others still felt that something was different.

Zhao Hai didn’t care about what they were thinking as he gave his command, “Pitch camp!”

Addison and the others recovered, then they quickly complied and pitched the camp. They were prepared to defend this place for some time, this was where Zhao Hai plans to attract the Dark Temple’s troops.

In Zhao Hai’s eyes, this wasn’t the main battlefield. The true battlefield would be at the heart of the Dark Temple. As long as they destroy the Dark Temple’s core, then everything else would be easy.

Zhao Hai also knew that for the coming days, the situation in this place would become beyond frigid. This was because the Dark Temple would regard this place as the main battlefront. Their armies would surely be unceasing. The pressure on Addison and the others would be very huge.

Although Addison and the others were Undead, after the establishment of the Academies, they had become their own race. This independence wasn’t only in Addison’s heart, Zhao Hai believed this to be the case as well.

Because of this idea, Zhao Hai didn’t want Addison and the others to die in vain. Therefore, Zhao Hai planned to attack the Dark Temple’s morale, decreasing the pressure placed on Addison’s group.

The base that Zhao Hai would construct wasn’t just any ordinary base, Zhao Hai borrowed the Divine Race’s fortress plans in order to make a stronghold. Not only was earth magic used in order to erect a hundred meter high stone wall, there would also be magic cannons and blood lightning javelins provided. All of these things were used to defend against the enemy. Zhao Hai wasn’t stingy this time, he took everything he can afford to take out.

The blood lightning javelins that the Space made had been upgraded Not only did they include a huge dormant energy inside, it also included deadly poison. This poison came from the Underworld’s Dark Ocean. It was very lethal against the Undead.

Besides these things, Zhao Hai also prepared a moat outside the fortress. This moat had the Blood River’s water flowing through it, complete with Blood Spirit Beasts. The Dark Temple would have to pay a very heavy price if they wanted to attack this fortress.

Zhao Hai regarded this war as his last war in the Underworld. Because of this, he didn’t spare anything in his preparations. He was going to use this event in to swallow the entire Underworld.

As long as he destroyed the Dark Temple, the Undead under the temple’s control would lose their power. As for the Neutral Alliance, Zhao Hai wasn’t concerned about them.

Because of this, Zhao Hai did his best in order to build this fortress into a solid defensive structure. This way, it would attract more attention from the Dark Temple, making Zhao Hai more relaxed in facing the man behind it.

Regardless of the enemy, Zhao Hai would still give his all. And even if Zhao Hai knew that the person behind the Dark Temple was probably just an incarnation and wouldn’t be that strong, he still didn’t underestimate him. What Zhao Hai wanted to do was to eliminate the other party while losing as least personnel as possible.

Zhao Hai was anxious to finish this thing because one, he wanted to obtain the buried treasures, and two, because his cultivation has increased beyond his imagination after gaining a new heart. Zhao Hai believed that it wouldn’t be long before he would complete the first stage of the Myriad Stellar Transformations Yin Yang Art. And when that time comes, Zhao Hai would have no choice but to ascend. Zhao Hai wanted to finish his matters in the Underworld before that happens.

With Zhao Hai’s efforts, the fortress was slowly being completed. Although the Undead wanted to help, most if not all of them could only use Dark Energy. For them, using earth element energy to make the wall was impossible. Therefore, they could only watch as the fortress was being made.

Fortunately, Zhao Hai was very powerful. It didn’t take long before the wall was finished. The magic cannons and the javelins have also been installed. After that, the experienced Undead inside the Space began to teach the other Undead how to operate the magic cannons and use the javelins. The tests proved that their might wasn’t small.

The Undead in the Underworld were strong, they were even stronger than the experts in the Divine Realm. Even the ordinary Undead had formidable defense. But now, Zhao Hai’s weapons have been improved. The magic cannons constructed by the processing machine now used materials that weren’t available before. This made the magic cannons last longer. The magic formations used on the cannons have also been upgraded, making each shot more lethal. Even if the Undead were defensively strong, they would still suffer under the magic cannons.

Zhao Hai finished making the fortress three days later. Making such a fortress in only three days, the only one who could do it alone was probably Zhao Hai.

The fortress was constructed right beside the Blood River, so it only had three walls. Moreover, these walls weren’t just ordinary straight structures, there were all kinds of edges and corners installed in them. Zhao Hai used his earth magic in order to provide the magic cannons and the javelins the best locations to fire from.

Outside the walls was a moat made with a branching stream of the Blood River. Inside this moat were Blood Spirit Beasts ready for ambush. At this point, they were waiting for the Dark Temple to arrive. At the same time, Lizzy was also using the Space’s monitor to pay attention to the Dark Temple’s movements.

Before long, the Dark Temple’s army was dispatched. But this time, the army they sent only contained a small number of troops. It seems like they didn’t think that the Resistance Army would be a threat. On the other hand, they concentrated their troops on the Neutral Alliance. It looks like they were planning to deal with the Resistance Army along the way before they clashed with the Neutral Alliance.

When Zhao Hai saw this, he couldn’t help but be speechless. He didn’t know how to react. The Dark Temple actually treats the Resistance Army as a side dish.

Upon seeing the situation, Zhao Hai didn’t immediately attack the Dark Temple. Although there weren’t a lot of defending troops left, the fact that the Dark Temple sent their troops to face the Neutral Alliance was something that was out of Zhao Hai’s expectation. The Neutral Alliance was quite close to the Dark Temple’s central area. If Zhao Hai can’t take out the core of the Dark Temple in a short time, then the army facing the Neutral Alliance would immediately return, and in a quick manner. Once they return, Zhao Hai’s surprise plan would be put to waste.

It was precisely because of this that Zhao Hai decided to wait. Once the fortress dealt with the first wave of troops, the army facing the Neutral Alliance would surely send people to deal with them. As long as that army moves, then Zhao Hai could immediately attack the Dark Temple. Even for the Experts, the distance between the Blood River and the Dark Temple’s core territory would take them several days of travel.

The fourth day after Zhao Hai completed the fortress, the Dark Temple’s army finally arrived. The army stood outside the fortress, dumbfounded. They didn’t expect a fortress here, there was even a moat.

The Dark Temple’s Undead stared at the huge fortress. They were speechless for a while. Zhao Hai made a large fortress, it can hold about 100 million Undead inside. The army sent by the Dark Temple this time contained 500 million Undead. It was impossible for these Undead to take a fortress that was armed to the teeth.

The Dark Temple’s high-ranking Undead were also left staring. They didn’t know what to do with the situation. After further discussions among them, they decided to make an attack first to see what would happen.

Before long, 100 million took flight and threw themselves towards the fortress. Zhao Hai wasn’t inside the fortress and was instead inside the Space. He was looking at the monitor while Lizzy was commanding the Undead, he didn’t plan on interfering.

At the same time, Lizzy didn’t make any great moves. He just commanded the Undead to man the magic cannons as well as equip themselves with javelins. Then they waited in place.

When the approaching Undead were about a kilometer away from the fortress, Lizzy finally ordered to launch the attack. Energy beams from the magic cannons immediately flew towards the Undead.

The Undead haven’t encountered this kind of attack before. They kept flying forward, they didn’t even try to dodge. But after the unending barrage of magic cannon fire and javelins arrived, batches upon batches of Undead began to fall from the sky.

However, this didn’t end there, another batch of attacks came in. Upon seeing the next wave, the Dark Temple’s Undead began to wake up. One after another they began to dodge, it was total chaos. However, they were still at a safe distance. Although there were a lot of deaths brought by the magic cannons and the javelins, there were even more Undead who were able to escape.

The Dark Temple’s undead were completely untrained, they were a motley crew. Just one hit from the fortress’ magic cannons and javelins was enough to send them back.

Chapter 1051: Contest of Strength

The Dark Temple’s high-ranked Undead couldn’t help but stare. They didn’t expect their attack to end this soon. Wasn’t this too fast?

At the same time, what were those things shooting out from the fortress? How can they be so lethal? They can actually one-shot the Undead?

The high-ranked Undead from the Dark Temple looked at the fortress. They really didn’t know what to do with it. Then at this time, one of the smarter high-ranked Undead suddenly said, “They managed to cross the Blood River. Does this mean there are no Blood Spirit Beasts here? In this case, we can cross the river. We will attack their nest and then come back to take care of them.”

The other Undead stared when they heard this. Then all of a sudden they all laughed. The loudest one of them said, “Right, right, you’re right. Since they can cross the river, we can do it too. Let’s go and attack their nest!”

After that was said, they immediately directed a group of undead to fly across the river. But as soon as they crossed over, the Blood Spirit Beasts immediately attacked .Moreover, the beasts this time seem to be more powerful than usual. No Undead who crossed the river survived from the attack.

Faced with this situation, the Dark Temple’s undead couldn’t help but stop. They were now made aware that there were still Blood Spirit Beasts in the Blood River. Wanting to cross the river at this time wouldn’t be an easy matter.

The Undead who commanded the army gathered together once more, each of their expressions difficult to look at. Especially the Undead who suggested crossing the Blood River.

The other Undead looked at him, not knowing not to say. They knew that the advice wasn’t a bad idea, it was in fact very good. They just underestimated the Resistance Army.

After several minutes of silence, one of them said, “We must inform the Dark God about this situation. I really didn’t expect the Blood Spirit Beasts to not attack the Resistance Army. This matter is very important. We need to ask the Dark God to send reinforcements. If we cannot take this fortress, then the Resistance Army would have a solid foothold in our territory. As this goes on, they would be able to sabotage a lot of our plans. They would be able to attack whenever they want while we would be in a passive state.”

The group nodded. Although they don’t understand basic troops formations, the current situation was simple enough for them to understand.

After seeing everyone nod, the Undead who suggested the idea continued, “Let’s send a group to head back with the message. Meanwhile we can organize our 500 million strong army to do something. Even if we cannot take the fortress down, we can still probe their capabilities. And once the Dark God’s army arrives, we can take the fortress in one go.”

The group nodded. Then the Undead who just spoke immediately arranged for a small team to inform the Dark God. Then he assembled another team, he looked at them and said, “You cowards listen to me! We’re already dead, but the Dark God has given us another life. Our lives belong to the Dark God. We have an enemy in front of us. If we cannot deal with them, then they would be a threat to our god. We need to take this fortress. I will personally command this team in the backline. If I find anyone retreating, I will kill them immediately. Now go ahead, for the Dark God!:”

The undead shouted loudly, “For the Dark God.” Then they proceeded to throw themselves towards the fortress.

The Dark Temple’s undead seems to be brainwashed by the man behind it. For their Dark God, they seem to stop their rationality, this includes their instinct to preserve their lives.

Zhao Hai was already prepared about this situation. It can be said that if one wanted to control people without the use of money, then they would have to rely on faith. The best way to control the Undead was through the use of faith.

Naturally, the one who used this method was the man behind the Dark Temple. This explains the burst of morale when the words ‘Dark God’ were mentioned.

Zhao Hai had thought about this before, so he really wasn’t that surprised. He didn’t make any moves or relayed any commands. He plans to leave everything to Lizzy and the others, they were good at these things.

Now that their morale had risen, the Dark Temple’s Undead began to rush towards the fortress.

However, what waited for them a kilometer away from the fortress were endless attacks. Both magic cannons and javelins were doing their part. They were advanced goods produced by the upgraded Processing Machine, so there was no need to doubt their quality. Additionally, there were enough ammunition present. And with the Dark Temple’s undead being unorganized, taking the fortress was truly impossible.

The high-ranked Undead didn’t participate in the attack and just observed the fortress. They wanted to see the defensive capabilities of the structure.

After observing for some time, these Undead couldn’t help but recognize that the fortress’ defenses were abnormal. The fortress seems to be an infinitely attacking machine. Wanting to reach the fortress walls seem to be impossible.

Some time after the attack started, a high-ranked Undead suddenly said, “We cannot just attack like this. We need to find a solution.”

The other Undead looked at him, so he sighed and said, “Gather the Lich together, the Undead archers as well. Have the Lich sneak into the fortress and attack it with magic. We’ll use the archers to draw their attention away from the Lich.”

The other Undead had no other ideas so they all agreed. Before long, a large number of Lich as well as Undead archers were arranged. The bows and arrows of the archers were made out of bones. The bows were refined from their own bodies. Undead who chose this path could only fight at long range.

The bodies of the Undead archers look more fragile compared to the others. But in return, this made them more agile. The arrows they used were made out of bones commonly found in the Underworld. But every one of them would have about ten arrows refined from their own bodies. These arrows were the true killers. Each one of them had their own special property.

After the archers and the Lich were gathered, the high-ranked Undead immediately gave them their orders. The archers and the Lich quickly understood their purpose and promptly prepared themselves.

To be honest, if the Undead Archers used their ordinary arrows, then it would be impossible for them to reach the fortress while being in a safe distance. In order to attract the fortress’ attention, they would have to use their special arrows.

It didn’t take long for Undead archers to arrive just beyond the 1 kilometer line. Then under the command of a high-ranked Undead, they began to fire their arrows at the same time.

As the arrows were shot out, the Lich began to progress towards the fortress. The high-ranked Undead focused their attention on the fortress. They wanted to see how the fortress would respond.

Originally, in the minds of these high-ranked Undead, battles were nothing more than leading a group, clashing for some time, and then having the Experts battle it out in order to find the winner. But now, the fortress had taught them that wars weren’t that simple.

These Undead also knew that wars were just like battles between two experts. One had to have the ability to look into their strength as well as their enemies. If they weren’t doing great, then they would fall behind, and in turn they would have more pressure during the fight.

Under the gazes of the high-ranked Undead, the fortress suddenly raised a bright red curtain, protecting the entire fortress. The arrows that went through this curtain were all blown up. They were rendered useless.

They also saw the fortress firing another round of their magic cannons. However, this salvo wasn’t heading towards the Undead archers, but to a different area instead. After the magic cannon fire exploded, one could see fiery souls on the ground. It was obvious that this was the place where the Lich were just in.

Upon seeing this situation, the high-ranked Undead could no longer sit still. They didn’t expect the enemy to be able to disrupt their plan. And they didn’t expect the enemy to be able to detect the stealthed Lich. This also made them very curious.

One must know that a Lich’s stealth technique was something that even high-ranked Undead wouldn’t be able to break. A stealthed Lich didn’t emit energy nor do they make noise. But despite these things, the fortress was actually able to find them, the fortress surely wasn’t simple. They also knew that although the Lich race’s stealth ability was formidable, it still conformed to the rules of the heavens and the earth. It was impossible for the Lich to achieve perfect stealth.

The Dark Temple’s Undead continued to make attacks ten more times. But each time, they were repelled by Zhao Hai’s fortress. Also, all of the fiery souls were taken by Zhao Hai to the Space. These fiery souls were good resources to improve the Undead.

In these attacks, the Dark Temple had lost a lot. They didn’t have any formations, they just blindly charged, and then after some time they would retreat. By the end of the attacks, the Dark Temple had already lost 100 million Undead. This showed how tragic their current situation was.

Chapter 1052: Yin Wind Ghost Emperor

The Dark Temple besieged the fortress for three days. The attacks made in these three days cost the Dark Temple 200 million Undead. But even with this much loss, they had yet to touch the fortress walls, they haven’t even reached the moat.. The fortress’ firepower was just too powerful.

This was the Dark Temple’s first encounter with this type of defense. They really didn’t know what to do. Although these Undead were practically unafraid of death, not being able to even come in contact with the enemy made them frustrated. At this point, the morale of the Dark Temple’s army was at an all time low.

The leaders of the Dark Temple Army also didn’t know what to do. Actually, the Dark Temple had no formal army. With this setup, it would be impossible for them to capture the fortress.

However, the Dark Temple Army still haven’t retreated. They were waiting for reinforcements to arrive. They sent their message three days ago. At the earliest, the reinforcements would take ten days. Because of this, the Dark Temple Army could only wait. At this time, they were afraid of attacking the fortress. If they kept attacking, then they would no doubt be wiped out.

The Dark Temple gathered 500 million Undead for this army. And in only three days, they lost 200 million. If things kept going as it is, they wouldn’t last ten days.

The Dark Temple’s high-ranked Undead were initially thinking of attacking themselves. However, the results weren’t ideal. Addison and the others simply didn’t allow them to make a move.

Although they made a few more rounds of attacks, the fortress’ defenses didn’t give them any opportunity to succeed. Not to mention the fact that Addison and the others were present on top of the walls. In this case, the high-ranked Undead had no choice but to surround the fortress without attacking.

While this was happening, Zhao Hai was paying attention to the Dark Temple’s response. The people sending the message were very fast. Since there was no need to move alongside an army, they were free of an enormous burden. It didn’t take long for them to reach the Dark Temple.

Currently, the Dark Temple was facing against the Neutral Alliance. It may even be possible that they were just waiting for the news about the Resistance Army’s defeat.

Since the battle of the fortress was put on hold, Lizzy finally had time to relax. Actually, it can be said that the fortress was already completely defensible. Especially in the Underworld where the Dark Temple didn’t have a lot of strategies in their attacks. Because of this, Lizzy was able to accomplish her task with ease. She hasn’t even used the Blood Spirit Beasts in the moat. The beasts were prepared as the main dish to oppose the incoming Army.

In the next few days, the fortress was quite calm. Although Zhao Hai had the strength to easily kill them all, this action would just alert the Dark Temple. Therefore, Zhao Hai just kept his hand and waited for the Dark Temple to make a decision.

Just like Zhao Hai calculated, the messengers reached the Dark Temple with the report at the proper time. Although the Dark God was in a murderous phase right now, he still transferred troops over towards the Blood River in order to eradicate the Resistance Army.

The Dark God’s present stance confirmed Zhao Hai’s theories. The Dark God was certainly an incarnation. Moreover, it seems like he can’t leave the Dark Temple. This was absolutely good news for Zhao Hai.

Since the Dark Temple’s Army had already been dispatched, readjusting their position was very quick. Zhao Hai calculated that they would take ten days to arrive at the Blood River, but in fact it only took them nine days.

There were a lot of Undead who were left behind in this operation. Looking at the messy march, Zhao Hai didn’t know what to say. If he cannot win against this kind of enemy, then he might as well kill himself with a slab of tofu.

The army sent by the Dark Temple this time numbered 5 billion. There would also be a continuous stream of reinforcements coming over in the next few days. However, this number of troops wasn’t a lot in Zhao Hai’s eyes. If he wasn’t planning on ending this war as soon as possible, then he could just abandon his plan of attacking the Temple and instead he would just slowly march his army forward while killing everything they meet.

This time, the Dark Temple sent most of their troops towards the Blood River. The Dark Temple’s Divine City only had 500 thousand Undead left inside. Although this city looked just like a trading hub, as long as an emergency arrives, everyone can become qualified soldiers. After all, each Undead in the Underworld were born fighters.

Also, there were four satellite cities around the Divine City. Each city had about 200 thousand Undead. When necessary, these Undead could present an army with strength that couldn’t be underestimated.

Zhao Hai discovered that the Undead in the Divine City wouldn’t be used in battle. It seems like the Dark God was very careful. However, Zhao Hai was already prepared for this situation. It was impossible for the enemy to not protect itself. As long as a large enough army was prepared by the Dark Temple, Zhao Hai wouldn’t care about those who were left behind.

After the Dark Temple’s Undead reached the fortress, they only had a simple rest before they immediately attacked. But at this time, Zhao Hai didn’t go and attack the Divine City. He waited. There were still troops trailing behind. He has to wait until all soldiers arrive before he attacks the Divine City.

In three days, the whole army would be finally gathered at the fortress. Zhao Hai made some calculations and the Dark Temple’s Army would end up numbering nearly 10 billion. This was a huge number.

However, Zhao Hai wasn’t worried. Instead, he was actually glad. With all these soldiers here, Zhao Hai’s assault on the Dark Temple’s core would be more relaxed.

The second day after arriving at the fortress, Zhao Hai brought ten million Undead to the Dark Temple’s Divine City.

When Zhao Hai came out, he divided the army into two batches. One group surrounded the Divine City, while the other group defended the vicinity.

Just as Zhao Hai thought, when the Dark Temple’s Undead saw that they had been surrounded, they immediately sprung out and attacked.

However, they were quickly met with an intense retaliation. The Undead that Zhao Hai brought this time were the old Undead of the Space. They had fought many battles and were very skilled even without any instructions. They were also well versed in battle formations. Not to mention Megan was their commander.

The encirclement immediately converged on the Dark Temple. Although it looks like they were protecting the temple, this was actually done so that nobody would be able to escape.

Zhao Hai stopped paying attention to the battle as he carefully observed the Dark Temple. The temple was completely made out of black bones. It was as high as a hundred meters and occupied land area of about a thousand square meters. The architectural style of the building made Zhao Hai feel as though it was a typical Chinese architecture.

Its great hall had two massive bone doors. The doors were engraved with various monsters. The temple’s roof was made with bone plates, and it also had upturned eaves. On each corner of the roof were skeletal monsters. The entire place looked like a haunted temple.

The monster designs included a bird-fish-insect hybrid. The ones engraved on the doors were traditional lion and beast carvings, just like those in ancient doors.

As Zhao Hai was carefully inspecting the appearance of the palace, a voice suddenly came from inside, “Why just stand there? Since you’ve come, why don’t you enter.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and then replied, “Thank you for your hospitality.” He said that as though he was visiting his friend’s home. Then he proceeded to slowly enter the Great Hall.

However, just as Zhao Hai was about to enter the hall, the eyes of the monsters on the doors suddenly lit up with fire. They turned to Zhao Hai and roared, it seems as though they were about to pounce.

Zhao Hai just smiled. He didn’t stop as he continued walking. At this time, the voice inside the hall said, “Stand down. Let him through.” After that, the monsters went silent.

Zhao Hai slowly entered the hall. The hall was built like a palace, but it was more grand than an average hall. The whole place had a total of nine steps, each step presented a higher status than the other. On the ninth step was a chair made of bones. The cover of the chair was made out of leather. On top of the chair was a huge dragon skull. The skull seemed to look at Zhao Hai, giving him intense pressure.

Sat on the chair was a person that didn’t look like an Undead. His clothes were black and were embroidered with all kinds of skeletons. In his hand was a scepter made out of bones. On the end of the scepter was a skull.

The entire scepter was gold. However, embedded in the eyes of the skull were two red stones. This made the scepter look like it was a ghost that could bite anyone at any time.

The person was thin, looking like bones covered by a layer of skin. He had grass-like white hair. His two eyes sparkled with ghastly flames while he looked at Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai could confirm that those weren’t fiery souls but instead a result of a certain cultivation method.

The person was also inspecting Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai had the appearance of the Dark Pharaoh who held his Blood Ghost Staff. After some time, the person said, “You aren’t Undead?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Naturally. I am just like you, not an Undead.”

The man’s expression changed, he immediately replied, “Who sent you? You actually dare to disrupt my plans? Just because this Yin Wind Ghost Emperor had stayed quiet all these years, it does not mean that I’ve turned soft!”

Chapter 1053: The Attack Has Already Begun

Upon listening to the Yin Wind Ghost Emperor, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but stare. Then he quickly understood that the Ghost Emperor was probing. First he asked Zhao Hai about who sent him and then he introduced himself. This was to see Zhao Hai’s reaction. Zhao Hai was now assured that the Yin Wind Ghost Emperor was from the Cultivation Realm, and that he was a fierce character.

Zhao Hai’s guess wasn’t wrong, Yin Wind Ghost Emperor was truly a hard to deal with character in the Cultivation Realm. This person’s cultivation on the ghost dao was immeasurably deep, to the point of being in control of countless ghosts. Moreover, his yin wind techniques were unparalleled under the heavens.

At the same time, this person had the attitude of holding on to grudges. He doesn’t care about his status. There was a case when the Elders of a huge sect managed to offend him, so he didn’t hesitate and target the lower-ranked disciples of the sect. This was an act that someone of his level generally wouldn’t do.

Because his cultivation was quite powerful, even if he cannot defeat you, you still wouldn’t be able to catch him. Therefore, in the Cultivation Realm, the name Yin Wind Ghost Emperor would always induce headaches to those who heard it.

In the Cultivation Realm, if your family or sect was strong, then it doesn’t necessarily mean that nobody would provoke you. People like the Yin Wind Ghost Emperor completely disregarded face. These kinds of evil people were the ones who gave people the most painful headaches.

Unfortunately for the Yin Wind Ghost Emperor, today was not his lucky day. This was because he was against Zhao Hai. Also, Zhao Hai wasn’t from the Cultivation Realm, something that Yin Wind Ghost Emperor wouldn’t be on guard against.

Zhao Hai looked at the Yin Wind Ghost Emperor and smiled, “This one has seen the Ghost Emperor. Please forgive me, I have never heard of the Ghost Emperor’s name before today. I just came here to ask the Ghost Emperor to leave the Underworld, this place belongs to me.”

The Yin Wind Ghost Emperor looked at Zhao Hai, he didn’t know what to say. Zhao Hai’s tone and voice looked very respectful. However, the contents of Zhao Hai’s message was actually impolite. This was the Emperor’s first encounter with this situation in a long time.

After a while, the Yin Wind Ghost Emperor finally reacted, his face turned blue as he said, “Kid, do you know who you’re speaking to? Tell me who sent you? Even the person who sent you wouldn’t dare talk to me this way.”

Zhao Hai wanted to roll his eyes, but then he suddenly had an idea. He laughed and said, “Yin Wind Ghost Emperor, if I said that I haven’t heard your name, then I haven’t heard your name. Also, I’m not afraid to tell you who sent me. The person who sent me is more powerful than you. Not only does he control the Divine Realm, he also controls the Ark Continent, the Demon Realm, the Barbarian Plane, as well as a lot of small and large planes. He’s someone you can’t compare to.” Although Zhao Hai didn’t say the person’s name, the mere fact that the person controls the Divine Realm, Demon Realm, Ark Continent, and Barbarian Plane was enough of a clue for the Yin Wind Ghost Emperor to know that the person was Lu Wei.

Even if Zhao Hai didn’t really know who Yin Wind Ghost Emperor was, he knew that it would be better if Lu Wei had more enemies. Also, the reason why Zhao Hai mentioned the Ark Continent and the Barbarian Plane was because he didn’t want the Yin Wind Ghost Emperor to get the wrong person. After all, the Divine Realm and the Demon Realm were names that high-level planes would commonly have. There would be no point if Yin Wind Ghost Emperor found the wrong guy.

Actually, Zhao Hai’s guess was correct. In the Cultivation Realm, there were groups who control other planes, but not as much as Zhao Hai thought. But even so, there were planes that called themselves the Divine Realm or the Demon Realm. After all, the people in these planes wouldn’t be aware of the Cultivation Realm as well as the multitude of other planes. If the leaders of these planes feel proud of their home, they would want to place themselves into an overbearing position. And what was more domineering than calling your plane either the Divine Realm or the Demon Realm.

When the Yin Wind Ghost Emperor heard Zhao Hai, his eyes flashed before he coldly snorted, “Is that so? Nevertheless, those who offend the Yin Wind Ghost Emperor wouldn’t be able to escape. Today, I will capture you and refine your soul. I will make sure that you will not be able to reincarnate.”

Zhao Hai laughed and replied, “Yin Wind Ghost Emperor, you overestimate yourself. Even if you are powerful, this is not the Cultivation Realm, this is the Underworld. It is impossible for your real body to come here, just your incarnation. How strong are you right now? One-tenth? One-twentieth? With that strength, and you still want to catch me? Are you dreaming? And you might as well stop using your spiritual force on me. Yin Wind Ghost Emperor, I didn’t know that you were this naive!”

Upon hearing this, the Ghost Emperor’s expression couldn’t help but undergo a drastic change. What Zhao Hai said wasn’t wrong. The moment he entered the hall, he was already being attacked. Zhao Hai just pretended that he didn’t discover anything. He used this moment to speak out in order to issue a blow to the Ghost Emperor’s confidence.

He didn’t know how long the Yin Wind Ghost Emperor has lived for, and he also didn’t know how many old monsters the Ghost Emperor has defeated. Because of this, Zhao Hai didn’t dare to treat this matter lightly. Before entering the Dark Temple, he already made the Scanner analyze the area. The design and construction of the Temple wasn’t just for looks, it was also crucial to this fight.

Built alongside the Dark Temple were numerous formations. Some of these formations focus on controlling the Undead, while some worked to improve the Yin Wind Ghost Emperor’s spiritual force.

Naturally, the Yin Wind Ghost Emperor was aware that his incarnation wasn’t invincible in the Underworld. Because of this, he needed to augment his strength, and amplifying his spiritual force was the best choice. While building the Dark Temple, he made sure to install magic formations in order to enhance his spiritual strength.

Another reason for these formations was to protect his incarnation. The incarnation isn’t very strong while in the Underworld. Also, the Yin Wind Ghost Emperor discovered something. The Underworld’s Dark Mist has an influence on the incarnation. If the Dark Mist was allowed to exist near the incarnation, then the incarnation might go out of control and become an independent Undead Creature in the Underworld.

The Yin Wind Ghost Emperor certainly wouldn’t let this happen. Therefore, he made the Dark Temple in order to protect the incarnation, keeping the Dark Mist from entering the temple. It was for this reason that the Ghost Emperor didn’t leave the Temple.

The Yin Wind Ghost Emperor had already discovered the peculiarity about Zhao Hai. With his profound insight, he actually couldn’t see the depth of Zhao Hai’s strength. This caused the Ghost Emperor to be startled. Because of this, he decided to deal with Zhao Hai from the very beginning. The moment Zhao Hai was about to enter the hall, the Ghost Emperor’s moves had already started. From the monsters at the door to the words he spoke, everything was done in order to exert pressure on Zhao Hai. And Zhao Hai seems to fall into his trap.

However, the Yin Wind Ghost Emperor didn’t expect that Zhao Hai also had plans against him, and that Zhao Hai started much sooner. Zhao Hai’s analysis of the Dark Temple didn’t come up with nothing. Ever since Zhao Hai acquired the Heart Defending Clan’s inheritance, he was able to learn about the formations that had been analyzed by the scanner. He knew that the Dark Temple was actually the Yin Wind Ghost Emperor’s weapon, a very formidable weapon. Not only could this weapon protect the Ghost Emperor, it could also deal with the enemies who dared to enter the Dark Temple.

However, Zhao Hai still decided to enter the Dark Temple. He wanted to see how strong the Yin Wind Ghost Emperor really was. Most importantly, Zhao Hai wanted to capture the Ghost Emperor’s incarnation so that he could gain a better understanding of the Cultivation Realm.

The Yin Wind Ghost Emperor’s face was pale as he looked at Zhao Hai. Then with clenched teeth, he said, “Good, good. I didn’t think that you would be aware of it for a long time. However, you have entered my Dark Temple. Don’t even think of escaping.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “I really don’t know how this Temple could be a threat to me. Although you have arranged magic formations, these formations only augment your spiritual attacks or trap your enemies. These formations are useless against me. Yin Wind Ghost Emperor, I advise you to withdraw your incarnation. Or else, don’t blame me if I choose to refine it.”

The Yin Wind Ghost Emperor laughed and said, “Alright, Kid. You’re really arrogant. You’re the first person to talk to me like that in many years. Hahaha. Do you think you can withstand the spiritual attacks of the Temple? Have you forgotten about those bone beasts? Are you aware of what kinds of beasts those are?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and replied, “I wouldn’t dare underestimate the Ghost Emperor’s schemes. Those bone beats should be famous monsters from the Cultivation Realm. In order to increase your security, you killed those monsters and sent them to the Underworld in order to protect your incarnation. Even if they are dead, they are still formidable. More importantly, you refined these beasts and made them into your puppets. Did I say anything wrong?”

The Yin Wind Ghost Emperor’s expression turned dark. He didn’t expect Zhao Hai to know about these things. This was equal to having one of his cards exposed.

The Yin Wind Ghost Emperor angrily shouted, “It’s useless to say anything more. I’ll let my subordinates do the talking!” Then the Ghost Emperor’s figure flew and slowly hid himself inside the Dark Temple. At the same time, several beast skeletons began to flood the hall.

The beast skeletons rushed into the hall but in a blink of an eye they vanished. Zhao Hai also discovered that the surrounding landscape had changed. It wasn’t the Dark Temple anymore. Instead he seems to be inside a Ghost Forest. There were various malicious ghosts wandering randomly all around him.

Zhao Hai knew that the Yin Wind Ghost Emperor had already activated his formation. This formation was the same type as the Five Element Killing Formation, it was a formation meant to kill.

However, Zhao Hai wasn’t worried. He also knew that the beast skeletons should be in the vicinity waiting for an opportunity to attack him. Zhao Hai just wanted to see how powerful this killing formation really was.

Zhao Hai had already made Cai’er look into the formation. In fact, when the formation started, Laura and Cai’er were already paying attention to the monitor. This killing formation wasn’t as good as the Five Element Killing Formation. Although Zhao Hai could see a lot of ghosts around him, these ghosts seem to be completely harmless. Those who can attack were those skeleton beasts that were lying in ambush.

On the Space’s monitor, these ghosts weren’t shown at all. This meant that the ghosts had no attacking power. They were only used to scare people and make sounds.

On the other hand, the skeleton beasts were clearly displayed on the monitor. Because of this, Zhao Hai wasn’t worried at all.

Zhao Hai quietly stood there and watched the ghosts. Although the ghosts looked very real, just like real malicious spirits, Zhao Hai just regarded them as mere showpieces in a movie, not threatening in any manner.

Zhao Hai had a lot of contact with the Undead. So regarding things like ghosts, he certainly would not feel anything.

On the other hand, the Yin Wind Ghost Emperor’s expression was quite ugly as he looked at Zhao Hai’s reaction. This formation was an imitation of the Ghost Emperor’s weapon, the Ten Thousand Ghosts Scepter’s Ten Thousand Ghosts formation. But unlike the real thing, the ghosts of this formation were almost illusory. Only after absorbing the Dark Mist for a period of time would these ghosts transform and carry out physical attacks. The ghosts from the real Ten Thousand Ghost Scepter were incomparably powerful.

Yin Wind Ghost Emperor’s Ten Thousand Ghost Scepter was the golden scepter that he was holding. However, that scepter was also just an incarnation. The Ghost Emperor certainly wouldn’t send his most important treasure to the Underworld. He placed a lot of effort in developing the treasure, and it was also the source of most of his strength.

A person like the Yin Wind Ghost Emperor can be said to have enemies in all places. Because of this, he wouldn’t dare even think about parting with his most important weapon. Although it would be very helpful for his cultivation to send the scepter, preserving his own life was much more important.

The Yin Wind Ghost Emperor didn’t tell this to Zhao Hai, but he had been behaving for quite some time. However, this wasn’t due to his own decision. This was because the Ghost Emperor had offended a very strong person. If he was found by this enemy, then he would be in great trouble. Because of this, the Ghost Emperor behaved and focused on managing Underworld.

Chapter 1054: The Attack of an Enraged Yin Wind Ghost Emperor

Zhao Hai looked at the ghosts. He sensed that the ghosts were winding up for attack. At the same time, Zhao Hai could feel the ghosts absorbing the Dark Mist and beginning to materialize.

Zhao Hai’s spiritual force has been greatly enhanced. Additionally, he has been training how to use his spiritual force with Berry these past few days. Because of this, he was now quite skillful in using his spiritual force.

It can be said that although the Succubi weren’t the strongest when it came to spiritual forces, no other race could compare to them when it came to control.

The Succubi were born with spiritual force, it was their racial skill. One shouldn’t underestimate this innate skill. It was said that reaching the peak needed 99% diligence and 1% talent. This 1% of talent was often much more important than the other 99%. Just like how the Dwarves were innately born with sensitivity towards metals, the Succubi were innately born to control spiritual force in a minute level.

Minute control and ordinary control were totally different. If ordinary control was sewing clothes, this minute control was embroidery.

Minute control was transforming spiritual force into filaments and controlling it. And this wasn’t just a two step approach, it was also a balancing act on what to focus on.

Zhao Hai trained in minutely controlling his spiritual force because he had analyzed the formations of the Dark Temple ahead of time, he was prepared for this attack. Just as the Yin Wind Ghost Emperor launched the formation, Zhao Hai immediately controlled his spiritual force to cover the entire formation.

He was able to look at the formation because of this ability. This allowed him to not only know that the ghosts could make spiritual attacks, but they could also inflict physical damage.

This caused Zhao Hai to be surprised. Spiritual and physical attacks were totally different. Moreover, it was very hard to defend against this kind of transforming attack.

For example, a ghost would throw itself over to Zhao Hai, but the ghost just passed through his body and didn’t do any harm. The next time, when a ghost would fly towards Zhao Hai, he could choose to ignore it. However, this time, the ghost would suddenly make an attack. In this case, the consequences would be unimaginable.

Because of this, Zhao Hai was thinking that the formation was adaptable and strong. However, Zhao Hai didn’t know that the formation didn’t actually have that many effects. This formation collects ten thousand living souls and refines them. Then it would release the souls to attack the enemy. Its only strategy was ghost swarming, nothing else.

A person’s living soul and fiery souls were completely different. Fiery souls were mutated souls that allowed the Undead to absorb energy and obtain life. On the other hand, living souls were souls obtained after a human just died. It was the thing that allowed humans to grow stronger when they were alive, it also allowed them to reincarnate after death. If its owner had grievances when they were alive, the living souls would turn into malicious ghosts. It was totally different from fiery souls.

The Yin Wind Ghost Emperor was also paying attention to Zhao Hai. After seeing Zhao Hai standing there and not moving, the Ghost Emperor began to form ideas in his mind. But he wasn’t thinking that Zhao Hai didn’t dare to move. He hasn’t fought with Zhao Hai before, and even if his incarnation wasn’t that strong in the Underworld, he still had his insight. He was aware that Zhao Hai wasn’t weak. It can be said that Zhao Hai was the strongest person he ever met after entering the Underworld. This formation shouldn’t be enough to scare Zhao Hai.

In fact, the Ten Thousand Ghosts formation’s use was just to surround Zhao Hai and confuse his sight and hearing. This way, the beast skeletons would be able to find an opportunity to make an attack.

Zhao Hai was paying attention to the formation as well as the beast skeletons. And in both subjects, Zhao Hai wasn’t able to find anything special. Then while observing the Dark Temple, Zhao Hai discovered that there was a small formation on the skull of a beast skeleton. This caused him to be startled. Then he traced the skull to see anything else special.

Originally, Zhao Hai wasn’t able to see any difference between these beast skeletons and the beasts in the Underworld. But then, Cai’er gave him a reminder. After looking at the skulls of the skeleton beasts, Cai’er suddenly said, “Young Master, these beasts aren’t from the Underworld. They have eyes!”

Those words reminded Zhao Hai that the beasts in the Underworld didn’t have eyes. On the other hand, these skeleton beasts had eye sockets. And after thinking about where they were and the Yin Wind Ghost Emperor, it seems like Zhao Hai had correctly guessed the identity of these skeleton beasts. In his dialogue with the Ghost Emperor, Zhao Hai just deliberately said those words as a probe. He didn’t expect that he was right.

The skeleton beasts were now making their move, their actions were very smooth and it seems like they were following a certain rhythm. Inside the Ten Thousand Ghost formation, they were able to walk discreetly. If Zhao Hai wasn’t paying attention to them using fine threads of his spiritual force, then he wouldn’t have been able to feel them.

The skeleton beasts were probably controlled by the Yin Wind Ghost Emperor. Because of this, they were able to hide their energy while moving.

Any creature, as long as they had energy, would emit energy when they move. On the other hand, these beast skeletons didn’t emit any energy while moving. This wasn’t an accident, the Yin Wind Ghost Emperor was certainly using tricks.

While Zhao Hai was thinking about this, a skeleton beast about five meters away from him began to crouch in preparation to strike!

Just as the skeleton beast pounced, Zhao Hai waved his hand and turned his Blood Ghost Staff into a sledgehammer and then swung it towards the skeleton beast’s skull. The skeleton beast shook, and before it could respond, Zhao Hai turned the sledgehammer into a huge net that covered the entire beast. After that, Zhao Hai pulled the net and just like a basketball, he flung it over and shot it straight into the Space.

The process might look very slow, but it actually happened very fast. It was like how you catch the ball and then lobbed it into the basket immediately.

When the skeleton beast was sent to the Space, the Yin Wind Ghost Emperor immediately felt that his connection to the beast was cut off. This caused him to be surprised. One must know that although the beasts weren’t that strong in the Cultivation Realm, a lot of time was spent refining them. Now that someone had stolen one, how could he not be angry?

The Yin Wind Ghost Emperor felt his lungs explode with rage. But at this moment, several skeleton beasts threw themselves towards Zhao Hai. Although Zhao Hai’s movements were quick, this also left him with an opening. The beasts used this opportunity to attack.

However, Zhao Hai did something that the beast never expected. His body flashed and then reappeared a few meters away. This change in position made the skeleton beasts attack the empty air.

Zhao Hai didn’t think too much about them as he moved and rushed towards the skeleton beasts. But the beasts were slippery, they immediately retreated to the sea of ghosts, disappearing from sight.

Zhao Hai wanted to catch the skeleton beasts, but unfortunately, he was stopped by the ghosts that have already materialized.

Because of the Dark Mist, the ghost were now tangible. Naturally, they were different compared to real malicious ghosts, and their strengths were worse. Nevertheless, they have materialized and now had fighting power.

At this time, Zhao Hai stopped. Then he turned the head of his Blood Ghost Staff into a lotus. Zhao Hai raised his staff as it emitted light, it was as though the sun had just risen.

This was light magic, moreover it was a wide-scale light magic called Descent of the Holy Light. Light element was the nemesis of Dark Energy, and these ghosts were made out of dark energy. Along with the flash of this light element magic, the ghosts screeched before they vanished.

After using his light magic, Zhao Hai moved and appeared beside a skeleton beast. While the skeleton beast was still struggling under the light magic, Zhao Hai caught its neck and then threw it into the Space.

The Yin Wind Ghost Emperor didn’t expect Zhao Hai to use light element magic in the Underworld. One must know that Dark Energy was prevalent in this plane, there were almost no other energy here. However, Zhao Hai actually managed to cast light magic, and a very strong one at that. It didn’t take long before the ghosts of the imitation Ten Thousand Ghost Formation vanished under the light magic assault.

The Yin Wind Ghost Emperor felt that he was going crazy. He couldn’t understand how a monster like Zhao Hai exists. The formation simply had no effect on him. He treated the temple as though it was his own back garden.

After seeing Zhao Hai steal another skeleton beast, the Yin Wind Ghost Emperor’s eyes turned red. He fiercely waved his Ten Thousand Ghost Scepter and then muttered an incantation.

The incantation made the eyes on the Ten Thousand Ghost Scepter’s skull light up with red light. However, this light didn’t shoot towards Zhao Hai, but to the Yin Wind Ghost Emperor instead!

Chapter 1055: Twilight Divine Water

As the red light entered the Yin Wind Ghost Emperor’s body, he began to turn paler and paler before he eventually vanished. On the other hand, the Ten Thousand Ghost Scepter began to grow and grow. In the end, the scepter’s handle vanished, leaving the golden skull flying in the air. When the skull became as large as a normal human head, it began to burst into flame.

Soul Sacrifice!

This was the Yin Wind Ghost Emperor’s special ability. He would offer his souls to the scepter in order to cast a type of self-destruct spell, amplifying the energy supplied by a factor of ten.

It can be said that if he wasn’t pushed into a corner, then the Ghost Emperor wouldn’t have used this move. Actually, this didn’t matter in the Underworld. The Yin Wind Ghost Emperor in the Underworld  was just an incarnation, so was the Ten Thousand Ghost Scepter. It would not be the worst if he lost these two things. What the Yin Wind Ghost Emperor wanted was to kill Zhao Hai!

Zhao Hai saw the changes that happened to the Yin Wind Ghost Emperor and his expression turned solemn. His was because he found out that after combining with the scepter, the Yin Wind Ghost Emperor had gotten very powerful.

At this time, the unification was done. The skull’s two blood red eyes looked at Zhao Hai before it opened its mouth and issued a loud cry! A sound attack went out of its mouth and headed towards Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai waved his hand, making a light blue shield appear in front of him. The shield looked like water as it rotated in place. It didn’t take long before the sound attack was neutralized.

Naturally, the Yin Wind Ghost Emperor wasn’t expecting that he would be able to easily deal with Zhao Hai. After this sound attack, golden yellow flames began to fiercely erupt from the skull’s eye sockets. The flames became golden silk as it fused into the ghosts.

The ghosts began to turn golden yellow. After that, Zhao Hai felt the Underworld’s Dark Mist surge into the ghosts. The strength of the ghosts was increasing at a clear rate.

“Jie Jie Jie Jie”” The Yin Wind Ghost Emperor smiled and said, “Kid, I will let you taste the feeling of getting bitten by 10 thousand ghosts. I will make sure that you suffer well before I kill you!”

After saying that, the Yin Wind Ghost Emperor directed the ghosts towards Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai lightly wrinkled his brows. The ghosts were now very powerful, they were no worse than the previous strength that Guli and the others had. In the Underworld, this strength already belonged to the top. And being attacked by ten thousand of these ghosts was truly not a fun thing.

Zhao Hai quickly cast Descent of the Holy Light. However, he didn’t expect the ghosts to remain unaffected.

“Hahaha. Kid, you’re underestimating my technique. If you expect your low-level spell to break my ghosts, then you are too naive! Now die!” After he said that, the Yin Wind Ghost Emperor sent the ghosts towards Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai looked at the ghosts and coldly snorted. Then he waved his Blood Ghost Staff and turned it into a sword, the same one he used to battle Addison. Zhao Hai traced his hand on the curved sword, then the sword hummed as it shone with golden yellow light. Zhao Hai wielded his sword and attacked the ghosts. Each swing hitting one ghost at a time.

However, Zhao Hai soon found something wrong. The ghosts were just immobilized as he hit them. Then after some time, they would resume their attack. And it also seems like they were becoming stronger and stronger.

“Kid, there’s no use struggling. After my sacrifice, my ten thousand ghosts can absorb everything. Any attacks you have will be useless. Just accept your death.”

Zhao Hai just coldly snorted as he waved his hand and sprinkled blood red water on the surroundings. This water came from the Space’s Blood Pond. Inside this water was a huge amount of blood energy. Moreover, this energy was yang-type. Almost all ghosts would melt upon meeting this water.

However, Zhao Hai didn’t expect that sprinkling the red water onto the ghosts would produce an effect similar to pouring gasoline on fire. Upon being splashed by the blood, the ghosts became enlarged. Every one of them burned up and grew. Their appearance became even more threatening.

“Hahahaha” The Yin Wind Ghost Emperor burst into laughter, “I have to thank you. I didn’t expect that you would give them so much energy. Hahaha. Are you afraid of not dying? Just stop struggling.” The attacks of the ghosts became even more violent. Zhao Hai looked at the ghosts and frowned. Ghosts were evidently from the yin-attribute, so they should be most afraid of yang-attribute.

The water in Zhao Hai’s Blood Pond has been improved several times. After Zhao Hai obtained a new heart, the blood evolved into a substance of pure yang. It had a perfect compatibility with the Black Sea Pond.

The Black Sea Pond was made after absorbing the water from the Underworld’s Black Sea. After entering the Space, the water evolved and became a liquid of pure yin. Because of this, the Space had achieved a balanced yin-yang condition.

Both waters from the Blood Pond and the Black Sea Pond can be used to make formidable weapons. The Yin-Yang Pond in Zhao Hai’s Blood Lotus changed and turned into a half-black and half-red pond. Naturally, these two held extreme power in their respective areas.

Naturally, if Zhao Hai wanted to deal with yin-attribute ghosts, then using the Blood Pond water was the right decision. But now, the ghosts who used to be illusory have now turned into a full entity.

The present situation made Zhao Hai puzzled. While he was repelling the ghost attacks, he was also trying to find a solution for the problem.

The ghosts became more powerful once again. If they had Guli’s previous strength last time, then now they had king-level strength. They were starting to annoy Zhao Hai.

Then all of a sudden, Zhao Hai noticed a gold glint on the faces of the ghosts. This was a sign of yang-attribute. How could it appear on the faces of the ghosts?

After he thought about this, Zhao Hai decided to try something. He waved his hand and sprinkled black water into the ghosts.

As the black water got in contact with the ghosts, azure smoke began to appear. The ghosts seem to be in pain.

The Yin Wind Ghost Emperor gawked, then he screamed and said, “Impossible. How could you have Twilight Divine Water? Impossible, absolutely impossible!”

The Yin Wind Ghost Emperor actually defined the Space’s pure yin water as Twilight Divine Water. It seems like this water was a treasure in the Cultivation Realm. Otherwise, the Ghost Emperor wouldn’t have been this surprised.

Upon thinking about this, Zhao Hai secretly reminded himself to be careful. Items from the Space might be high-grade goods. If he casually took them out, then he might attract greedy people.

Zhao Hai coldly snorted and said, “Twilight Divine Water isn’t that great. My Young Master has a lot of it.” Then after he said that, he waved his hand once more, sprinkling even more water towards the ghosts.

At this time, the Yin Wind Ghost Emperor had already escaped far away. As someone from the Cultivation Realm, he naturally knew how strong Twilight Divine Water was. Water made out of pure yin could dissolve a lot of items. It was heavy as mercury and was extremely toxic to the soul.

In the Cultivation Realm, even if it was an ordinary item, as long as it achieved the peak of purity, then it would be deemed as a great treasure. An example of this was the Twilight Divine Water, a water of pure yin. It can break through practically anything and could be used to refine weapons. Its power was endless. In the Cultivation Realm, there was a weapon made from Twilight Divine Water known as Divine Water Flowing Cloud Skirt. It was a ribbon-type weapon that can be formed and deformed into anything. It can be as hard as ice and as soft as water. It can also erode weapons. If a person was wounded by this weapons, then they would be poisoned. Moreover, it would be hard for them to live for long. This weapon was a treasure of the Divine Water Palace. It was one of the most infamous weapons in the Cultivation Realm.

However, Twilight Divine Water was a very rare treasure. Producing it requires a very special environment. Luck was needed in order to acquire this treasure. Even the Divine Water Palace set up a special place a thousand meters underground in order to harvest it. The cavern would produce one drop every one thousand years. Each drop was enough to make one die of jealousy. If the people from Divine Water Palace became aware that Zhao Hai was using Twilight Divine Water in order to kill ghosts, then they might kill themselves on the spot.

Actually, even if the Underworld’s Black Sea water enters the Cultivation Realm, it still couldn’t become pure yin water. It was only after being refined by the Space and integrated with numerous poisons and yin ingredients did the Black Sea Pond slowly came into existence.

At this time, the Twilight Divine Water Pond and the Blood Pond had fused and became a Yin-Yang Pond. it was situated not far from the Hundred Spirit Tree. The pond that was divided into half-black and half-red was quite eye-catching.

After eliminating the ghosts, Zhao Hai decided to go after the Yin Wind Ghost Emperor. Currently, the Ghost Emperor only had four skeleton beasts remaining. It can be said that the skeleton beasts were more intelligent compared to the ghosts. Upon seeing the effects of the Divine Water, they immediately escaped early in order to save their lives.

Chapter 1056: Conquer the Underworld

The golden skull that the Yin Wind Ghost Emperor turned into hovered in mid-air, the four skeleton beasts standing by his side. It might be his imagination, but Zhao Hai could see a trace of fear on the Ghost Emperor’s red eyes.

Yin Wind Ghost Emperor looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Kid, what is your relationship with Divine Water Palace? If you tell me the truth, then I will give the Palace face and let you go.”

Zhao Hai stared. Although his contact with the Yin Wind Ghost Emperor wasn’t that long. But from the few times he spoke, and even using his incarnation as a sacrifice, Zhao Hai knew that the Yin Wind Ghost Emperor was definitely a vicious and merciless guy. He handles things like an unscrupulous fellow. For this person to be willing to give the Divine Water Palace some face and let Zhao Hai go, this signifies how terrifying the Divine Water Palace was.

However, Zhao Hai wouldn’t pretend to be connected to the Divine Water Palace. If he did, then his plan for incriminating Lu Wei would fail. He didn’t want to hug a huge tree and give up an opportunity to deal with a personal foe.

At the same time, Zhao Hai also knew that if he was too arrogant, then it will cause Yin Wind Ghost Emperor to be suspicious. The Ghost Emperor dreaded the Divine Water Palace. If Zhao Hai didn’t care about this fact, then the Ghost Emperor would certainly get some ideas.

After some deliberation, Zhao Hai looked at the Yin Wind Ghost Emperor said, “Yin Wind Ghost Emperor, there’s no need to face the Divine Water Palace some face. I’m not related to the Palace at all. It’s either you or me today.”

After saying that, Zhao Hai waved his Blood Ghost Staff and attacked the Ghost Emperor. The Ghost Emperor had calmed down now. He also understood that the pure yin water can completely restrain him. But after thinking about the Twilight Divine Water as well as the Divine Water Palace, Yin Wind Ghost Emperor didn’t believe that Zhao Hai would really waste this pure yin water. This kind of treasure wasn’t easy to acquire.

Upon thinking about this, Yin Wind Ghost Emperor began to believe that even if Zhao Hai used a yin attribute water, it might not be Twilight Divine Water. His fear began to disappear as he said, “Kid, it’s time to stop bluffing. I’ll let you see the power of this Emperor today.” Then after he said that, he injected golden fire into the four beast skeletons. After being covered by a golden yellow light, the four beast began to throw themselves towards Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “It’s useless. If I can break your ten thousand ghost formation, then I can deal with these beasts.”

Zhao Hai began to move and turned his Blood Ghost Staff into four huge nets, catching the four beast skeletons together.

Yin Wind Ghost Emperor snickered and said, “Hehe. My ghosts are pura yang, the polar opposite of yin. They can burn all things…..” However, the Ghost Emperor had to stop there. This was because the four beast skeletons couldn’t get loose from Zhao Hai’s large net. Instead, they were quickly sent towards the Space.

Zhao Hai looked at the Ghost Emperor and laughed, “Yin Wind Ghost Emperor, I told you that you shouldn’t look highly upon yourself. Don’t underestimate me, otherwise you wouldn’t be able to know how you died.” Then Zhao Hai waved his staff and sent an attack towards the Ghost Emperor.

The Yin Wind Ghost Emperor opened his mouth and sent another sound attack. However, Zhao Hai’s shield continued to block the attack. Zhao Hai turned his staff into a huge bell and then gave it a gentle swing, sending a sound attack towards the Ghost Emperor.

The Ghost Emperor didn’t expect Zhao Hai to send a sound attack. Before he could block, the sound attack already hit him. Zhao Hai knew that these kinds of attacks could be used to deal with ghosts. After all, sound attacks belonged to the type of attack that targeted the soul. And to put it bluntly, ghosts were creatures who were completely made out of souls, this attack was very effective against them.

As for the Twilight Divine Water, Zhao Hai didn’t dare to use it easily. This was because Zhao Hai was afraid of the incarnation’s ability to transmit information to the main body. If Zhao Hai continues to use the Divine Water, then the Ghost Emperor would truly chase him once he reaches the Cultivation Realm.

Zhao Hai’s sound attack extinguished much of the Yin Wind Ghost Emperor’s fire. Then Zhao Hai followed up with another sound attack. But this time, the Yin Wind Ghost Emperor countered, issuing his own sound attack to offset Zhao Hai’s.

However, Zhao Hai found a way to deal with this. He kept sending attacks towards the Ghost Emperor, forcing the latter to be on the back foot.

After fighting for one hour, Zhao Hai discovered that the Yin Wind Ghost Emperor began getting slower and slower. Moreover, his flames were slowly getting paler.

Zhao Hai knew that the Ghost Emperor was close to his end, but he still wouldn’t dare to treat it lightly. The Yin Wind Ghost Emperor dared to sacrifice his soul, this meant that he was quite a ruthless person. One needed to think things carefully when faced with such a character.

The Yin Wind Ghost Emperor truly doesn’t have much time to live. Although sacrificing his soul made him obtain a massive burst of strength, this move also consumed the soul. Once the soul was burned up, the person would also die.

If the real Ghost Emperor was here, then he would be able to fight for a long time. However, he could only send and incarnation to the Underworld. Because of this, he couldn’t withstand this consumption. At this point, his soul was akin to a completely dried out lamp.

The Yin Wind Ghost Emperor looked coldly at Zhao Hai and said, “Kid, I didn’t think that you would be strong. Good, this Emperor shall accept today’s defeat. However, my people will certainly find out who you are. When the time comes, I will kill you as well as your superior.” Then the Yin Wind Ghost Emperor made one last sound attack before he exploded. He wanted to try blowing up the entire Dark Temple.

But at this time, Zhao Hai already returned to the Space. He looked at the Dark Temple’s ruins on the monitor and then muttered, “Yin Wind Ghost Emperor, this person is truly ruthless. He still wanted to deal with me up to the very end.”

Sitting nearby, Laura nodded and said, “This person is quite dangerous. He showed weakness before finally blowing himself up. He intends to injure you, that explosion wasn’t normal. With all those formations amplifying the effect, even a peak God-rank would perish.”

Zhao Hai nodded,  then he walked towards Zhao Hai and said, “Now let’s go see Megan and Lizzy.” Laura nodded.

Laura and Cai’er were currently inside Zhao Hai’s room, helping him with his fight against the Yin Wind Ghost Emperor. The monitor outside in the living room was handed over to Lizzy while Megan used another monitor inside her room. Because of this, if Zhao Hai wanted to know the situation, he would have to go to them himself.

They went to Megan’s room first to see her situation. Megan was doing quite well. Presently, almost all of the Divine City’s Undead had been dealt with. Most of these Undead were captured while the rest were killed.

Now, Megan was prepared to storm the Divine City’s four satellite cities. After seeing Zhao Hai come in, Megan immediately said, “Brother Hai, are you fine? The Dark Temple just exploded, it killed a lot of our Undead. I was worried that something had happened to you.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Rest assured, I’m fine. You continue on while I go take a look at Lizzy. They should be tidying up by now. After that we’ll help you.”

Megan nodded, then she continued to focus on the battle. At the same time, Zhao Hai and Laura went out of the room and went towards the living room.

In the living room, Lizzy was fully concentrated on commanding the fight. The Dark Temple’s undead were frantically attacking the fortress, however their advances were drowned by cannon fire and javelins. Additionally, there were also Blood Spirit Beasts. Also, the fortress was fully equipped with troops. The Undead that attacked the fortress were quickly captured and turned into Zhao Hai’s men.

Zhao Hai stood by Lizzy for some time, looking at the monitor. One has to recognize that Lizzy was very good at command. Her strategy was methodical, advancing and retreating was carefully controlled. The battle looked quite pleasant.

Presently, there weren’t a lot of troops stationed in the Blood River. The fortress currently had the most priority. Lizzy wasn’t planning on counter-attacking, she was just planning on keeping the enemy here. If she pushes the Dark Temple’s Undead too much, then they might become too frightened and retreat. If this happens, then they would certainly cause trouble to Zhao Hai.

After spectating for some time, Zhao Hai said, “Lizzy”

Lizzy’s body shook, then she turned towards Zhao Hai. Surprised, she said, “Brother Hai, are you done?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly he nodded and said, “Finish things up here. After that, go help Megan.”

Lizzy nodded, then she waved his hand, causing countless amounts of Undead to surround the Dark Temple’s Army.

Altogether, the Dark Temple army had about 10 billion Undead. They haven’t fought with Lizzy for a long time, so they haven’t lost that much. On the other hand, Zhao Hai’s Undead was close to 20 billion. It can be said that Zhao Hai had a  2 to 1 advantage. In this case, wanting to annihilate the Dark Temple Army wasn’t something impossible.

Zhao Hai wasn’t thinking of persuading the Dark Temple’s Undead to surrender. These Undead weren’t controlled by a contract, instead they were convinced by faith.

Zhao Hai was very clear about this point, therefore, instead of persuading, he prompted to defeat them by pure military force. In any case, he wasn’t afraid of the other party’s strength.

Also, Zhao Hai wasn’t worried that the Dark Temple’s Undead would cause wind and waves. Even if they escaped from this place, they still wouldn’t be able to do anything since the Temple had already been destroyed. Zhao Hai believed that news of this would certainly be a huge blow.

An army gathered in the name of faith would directly be destroyed once their subject of worship disappears. Because of this, Zhao Hai didn’t plan to deal with the Undead on the side of the river. The reason he surrounded the army was because he wanted to use them to improve the Space’s strength.

Sure enough, after being surrounded, the Dark Temple’s undead began to feel flustered.  At this moment, Lizzy’s attack also began. As Lizzy commanded the Undead, she made sure that those at the frontlines were those who had become adept in army formations. Just like a sharp knife, they sliced through the Dark Temple’s army. The Undead who were in formation didn’t falter and just continued to advance.

The Dark Temple’s army were originally flustered. Now that they had met this attack, they began to disperse in all directions.

However, Lizzy wasn’t intending to pursue the escaping Undead. Instead, she focused on capturing the Undead and sending them to the Space. And then, after they had surrendered, they were released back into the Underworld.

The battle was now basically over, there was no need for Lizzy to issue further commands. At this time, Meg arrived carrying a teapot. The teapot was filled with leaves from the Hundred Spirit Tree as well as some medicinal herbs. Meg placed the teapot on the table and then smiled at Zhao Hai, “Young Master, Sisters, have some tea and take a rest.”

Lizzy chuckled as she rubbed Meg’s face, “Our little Meg is truly the best. You always know I like.”

Meg’s face turned red under Lizzy’s teasing, “Sister Lizzy, if you tease me again, I will never bring you delicious snacks.”

Lizzy paused for a moment before she chuckled, “Even if you don’t bring me snacks, you would still give some to Brother Hai. I will eat with him then.”

Zhao Hai looked at the two bickering and couldn’t help but smile. He liked this atmosphere. Everyone sat together, drinking tea, playing jokes on each other, it feels much like a family.

There was no need to look at the monitor since the war was basically done. Zhao Hai can also affirm that the Underworld was now his.

Chapter 1057: Response of the Neutral Alliance

Now that Zhao Hai had dealt with the Yin Wind Ghost Emperor, taking care of the other Undead would be easy. And just like Zhao Hai thought, since the Dark Temple has been razed, battles ended with no suspense.

The status of the Dark Temple had been too high. The undead regarded the Dark Temple as the place of their Dark God. And under the instruction of their god, they were invincible, nobody can block their army.

But now, they suddenly discovered that their omnipotent god was unexpectedly been defeated. The Divine Palace was also razed to the ground. The attack of these events to their morale was beyond comparison.

On the other hand, the morale of Zhao Hai’s army was at sky high. With the Dark Temple’s undead having very low morale and without no leader, winning the war was simple.

In fact, these days, Lizzy and Megan didn’t command the Undead. Instead, the control was handed over to Addison and the others. The two would just give instructions when it comes to formations during marches.

Zhao Hai began to relax. The Dark Temple’s territory had already been captured by them. While watching the increasing number of his Undead, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but feel numb.

Nobody could blame Zhao Hai. He wasn’t expecting the number of his Undead to jump by hundreds of millions every day. It was as if the numbers had been injected with dog’s blood, it was frantically increasing.

Although the Dark Temple’s territory was slowly being absorbed, Zhao Hai wasn’t anxious in searching for treasures. He wanted to wait until he had dealt with the Neutral Alliance before he begins his search.

The Neutral Alliance was weaker than the Dark Temple, and they seem to not have a person they worship. However, Zhao Hai was still worried. What if the Neutral Alliance had a high-level person controlling them from behind? If Zhao Hai revealed too many secrets in his body, then the people from the Cultivation Realm might do whatever they can to deal with him. And even if they couldn’t kill him, Zhao Hai would still have to run for his life, hiding inside the Space. Zhao Hai didn’t want that kind of life. He wanted to explore the world and see its wonders.

Besides dealing with the Dark Temple’s Undead, Zhao Hai was also mapping the Neutral Alliance’s territory in the past few days. At the same time, he was also monitoring the Alliance’s various cities.

Zhao Hai did these things because, one, he wanted to prepare to deal with the Alliance, and two, Zhao Hai was very clear that if the Neutral Alliance gets any news of the Dark Temple being eliminated, then they would certainly be on guard. Because of this, Zhao Hai monitored the Alliance’s cities in order to see their response.

Sure enough, there was a reaction from the Neutral Alliance. The people from the Alliance didn’t expect the Resistance Army to completely pressure the Dark Temple. They were even able to assault the Dark Temple and kill their Dark God. This event was beyond their imaginations.

The Neutral Alliance was an existence that placed itself between the Resistance Army and the Dark Temple. They also used their power to maintain this delicate balance. This was in order to maintain the business they had on both sides.

And this balance was very easily achieved. The Undead wanted to get stronger. And in order to do so, they would need plants and high-ranked fiery souls. The Neutral Alliance would use their business in order to control the strength of both sides. For example, if they sell high-ranked fiery souls to the Dark Temple, they would also sell similarly ranked fiery souls to the Resistance Army. The same was true for plants. This way, the power balance of the Underworld would remain as it was.

But now, this balance was broken by the Resistance Army. Now that they had usurped the Dark Temple, this meant that the two sides had become one. In this case, would the Resistance Army leave the Neutral Alliance alone?

Naturally, the answer was no. Even low-ranked Undead would be able to give this answer. Because of this, if the Neutral Alliance didn’t react, then it would be strange.

From what Zhao Hai can see, the Neutral Alliance was a very loose organization. Moreover, the alliance was mostly dominated by businessmen. In this case, they should be actively seeking the Resistance Army and rely on them to survive. This was in line with a businessman’s mindset.

However, Zhao Hai didn’t expect that after gaining news, the Alliance didn’t contact the Resistance Army. Instead, they used their accumulated resources over the years in order to promote their subordinates. This allowed the Alliance to produce massive amounts of experts in a short time. It seems like they were prepared to deal with Zhao Hai’s group.

Zhao Hai looked at this outcome and knew that the Alliance wasn’t planning on being friendly. Since this was the case, then Zhao Hai could only make a move. He wasn’t a kindhearted person, so after seeing this reaction, he couldn’t just let them go free. Fighting them was the way to go.

However, one must recognize that the Alliance was worthy of being called the Underworld’s merchants. They were very rich. They were able to make large quantities of experts in a short span of time. This was something that Zhao Hai didn’t expect. But Zhao Hai also had a card he could play. He didn’t use it before, it was time to take it out now.

Previously, Zhao Hai was able to buy a small beast skeleton from the Alliance. This beast skeleton could turn into bone armor. Moreover, these bones armors could be turned into seeds. Zhao Hai handed the armors over to Gimreden to take care of. Now, the bone skeleton seeds had been planted, and Zhao Hai already had a battalion’s worth of bone armor.

The undead in this bone armor battalion weren’t just ordinary undead. They were Undead who followed Zhao Hai for a long time, the ones most familiar with army formations. Moreover, Zhao Hai had increased their strength using fiery souls. At this point, this group had reached King-level strength.

This king-level strength was still worse than a peak King-level character. However, the battalion numbered 10 thousand strong. Ten thousand King-level Undead wearing bone armor, moreover, they were trained to use army formations, an army of this strength was enough to fully sweep the entire Underworld.

This group had the same training as the Devil Legion. They were made in preparation for Zhao Hai’s ascension to the Cultivation Realm. They were only taken out right now because the Neutral Alliance’s response had annoyed Zhao Hai.

The Neutral Alliance could produce experts in a short time. If Zhao Hai couldn’t stop this trend, then he would be losing a lot of Undead in the future. Because of this, Zhao Hai wanted to use the bone armored Undead to deal with them.

But before dealing with the Neutral Alliance, Zhao Hai needed to completely extinguish the Dark Temple’s influence. This way, they could safely deal with the Alliance.

Naturally, Zhao Hai wouldn’t just lower his guard against the Alliance during this period of time. The Alliance produced a lot of Experts, this defined their position in this struggle. One couldn’t say what moves the Alliance would do. Zhao Hai couldn’t just allow them to perform a sneak attack on him.

Because of this, Zhao Hai made some preparations. He concentrated a lot of Blood Spirit Beasts on a portion of the Blood River closest to the Alliance. At the same time, he also used magic in order to make several branches to the Blood River. These branches would surround the Alliance, shackling them in place. If the Alliance wanted to make a move, then they would need to remove these shackles first.

With the Blood Spirit Beasts facing the Alliance, Zhao Hai began to feel relieved. At the same time, he assigned Cai’er to monitor the Alliance’s actions. If the Alliance decided to move their experts, then Cai’er was to send the Bone Armor Legion.

Regarding the fight against the Dark Temple, Zhao Hai didn’t really care too much, there was no need to do so. Although there were still some forces that were resisting, they were just grasshoppers after autumn, they only had a few jumps left. What he needed to do was to clean these guys up. It would be annoying if these people came out during the fight against the Alliance.

However, Zhao Hai handed this matter over to Addison to take care of. Zhao Hai was beginning to groom Addison to be the person who would manage the underworld in the future.

During this period of time, Addison wasn’t only learning army formations from Lizzy. He was also studying how to manage the underworld under Laura.

It was fine if Addison learned only some of Lizzy’s army formations. After all, wars would be very rare in the Underworld in the future. Also, if they clash against the Cultivation Realm, depending on the Underworld’s strength was already impossible. Because of this, learning basic formations was already fine.

As for managing the Underworld, it was also quite simple. Zhao Hai could just arrange the same system that he established inside the Space. He would install churches at key places, allowing the Underworld’s undead to exchange for goods. There was no need for Addison to manage this.

But in the end, the Underworld wasn’t inside Zhao Hai’s Space. Someone like the Yin Wind Ghost Emperor could still appear here in the future. Because of this, some management was still needed, and Addison was a fitting candidate for this spot.

Chapter 1058: Does the Neutral Alliance Have Cards to Play?

The Dark Temple’s territory has been settled. The lands of the Resistance Army and the Dark Temple now belonged to Zhao Hai, the only one remaining was the Neutral Alliance.

Completely out of Zhao Hai’s expectation was the Neutral Alliance doing nothing as Zhao Hai continues to swallow the Dark Temple’s territory. Instead, they just defended their lands. It seems like they’re planning on holding on to it for a long time.

Zhao Hai couldn’t understand the Alliance’s decision. The Alliance went all out in making experts, putting out a message that they would desperately go against the Resistance Army. So why were they quiet now? This caused Zhao Hai to be puzzled.

But now that the Dark Temple has been taken over, the damages caused by the war needed to be repaired. There were many things that needed to be restored, and the Undead needed to be restructured. Only after completely consolidating the territory could Zhao Hai’s group begin to deal with the Neutral Alliance.

Zhao Hai was now quite relaxed. He has handed almost all of the management problems to Addison to take care of.

The same was true for Lizzy and Megan. After they dealt with the Dark Temple, the two returned to the processing machine to resume their research. Zhao Hai didn’t prevent the two from going. To be honest, the processing machine was still a mystery to them. This machine needed to be completely understood in order to unleash its true capabilities. Zhao Hai’s understanding of the machine was still very small. He had been too busy to give time to this matter. And now that Laura and the others were interested in studying the machine, he just let them continue doing so.

It took five days for the Dark Temple’s influence to be fully eliminated. In these five days, Addison and the others were rebuilding the site where the Dark Temple used to be. This wasn’t an easy task because they weren’t just rebuilding the structure, they were also expanding it.

Zhao Hai knew about the perils of the Underworld; the acid rain, the winds, and so on. And whenever these disasters occur, a lot of low-level Undead were killed. Zhao Hai decided to expand the cities in order to provide shelter to the Undead who lacked the strength to survive on their own.

However, Zhao Hai also knew that this was a long-term project, it cannot be achieved in a short time even with his current strength. Because of this, he wasn’t too anxious about its completion. Also, this reconstruction was just a form of disguise. What Zhao Hai wanted to do in the meantime was to study the Neutral Alliance!

The only lands that didn’t belong to Zhao Hai were the ones that were under the Neutral Alliance. Moreover, Zhao Hai began to feel that the Alliance was hiding a secret. How could these Undead do business so smoothly? Thinking about it, it was too strange. Because of this, Zhao Hai didn’t immediately make a move and instead decided to take some time to investigate the Alliance.

Zhao Hai was currently sitting in his study, contemplating. At the same time, he was also scouring through the Heart Defending Clan’s inheritance inside his mind. Zhao Hai has to recognize how good the clan’s inheritance was. It can be said that he profited a lot.

Then all of a sudden, he felt that Addison was calling for him. Zhao Hai stared, he had given Addison an order to not disturb him unless it was an important matter. Addison wasn’t someone who would disobey instructions. Now that Addison was asking for his attention, it seems like this wasn’t an ordinary matter. After he thought about this, Zhao Hai immediately contacted Addison using his mind.

Addison was akin to Zhao Hai’s contracted creature. Therefore, Zhao Hai could contact the vampire using their connection. Addison could also use this method to call Zhao Hai.

After getting Zhao Hai’s response, Addison immediately said, “Young Master, someone from the Alliance just approached me. He says he wanted to meet you.” Zhao Hai stared, he gently knit his eyebrows and said, “Someone wants to see me? How did they know about my existence? Did you tell them?”

Upon hearing that Zhao Hai was somewhat unhappy, Addison quickly replied, “We didn’t. They discovered it on their own. Its possible that they were able to remember our transaction from last time. Because of that, they asked for your presence. Young Master, how do you want me to respond?”

Zhao Hai gave a nod. He also believed that Addison wouldn’t talk irresponsibly. The man was perfectly discreet, he wouldn’t do such a foolish thing.

Zhao Hai thought for a moment and then said, “They want to see me? Good, then I will meet them. Tell them I agree. I also want to know why they came.”

Addison complied, then there were no other news. Zhao Hai waved his hand as a monitor appeared in front of him, showing the place where Addison was currently in.

Addison was currently in the Divine City. In place of the destroyed Dark Temple, Zhao Hai constructed a church. Zhao Hai didn’t choose to make the church according to Chinese customs, instead, he used European design, making the structure look extraordinary and full of artistry.

The reason Zhao Hai used European architecture instead of Chinese was because he wanted to distance himself from the Yin Wind Ghost Emperor. He wanted the people from the Underworld to understand that he was different from the Ghost Emperor.

Not only can this church be used to exchange goods, it was also a dwelling place. Addison was currently living inside the church.

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but find it interesting that a vampire was living inside a church. At this moment, Addison was inside the reception hall meeting with a Lich.

Zhao Hai carefully inspected the Lich and discovered that it was Yuri, the City Lord of Dry Bone City. It was the merchant that Zhao Hai once bought goods from.

When Addison returned to the hall, he sat down and said, “May I ask why City Lord Yuri wants to meet with the Young Master?”

In any case, it seems like Yuri had guessed Zhao Hai’s status, so he didn’t bother hiding anything and just called Zhao Hai ‘Young Master’. When Yuri heard Addison, his eyes shone for a moment before he quickly concealed it, “I came because the high-ranks of the Alliance wanted to meet with Mister Zhao Hai to discuss a matter of alliance.”

Addison looked at Yuri and said, “May I know what this alliance means?”

Yuri smiled faintly and said, “The Neutral Alliance always believed in freedom, naturally we are hoping that we could maintain our autonomy. We’re hoping that Mister would agree to this request.”

Addison coldly snorted and said, “City Lord Yuri should know your current state, and you still think we can agree to this request?”

When Zhao Hai heard Addison’s words, he couldn’t help but praise the Vampire King in his mind. The Resistance Army had the absolute advantage, so how could they give up the prospect of unifying the entire Underworld? Addison’s question was very good.

Yuri seems to expect Addison’s response, so he smiled faintly and said, “This is why we wanted to invite Mister Zhao Hai. If Mister visits the Alliance, then he would surely change his mind.”

Addison didn’t know what the Neutral Alliance was planning. Therefore, he couldn’t help but hesitate to answering Yuri. At this time, Addison heard Zhao Hai’s voice in his mind, “Tell him that making a lot of high-ranked Undead in a short time is useless against us.”

When he heard Zhao Hai, Addison’s eyes shone. He looked at Yuri and said, “City Lord Yuri, you just used your stockpiled resources to make a lot of high-rank Undead. Are you thinking of using them to deal with us? Let me tell you that it’s useless. If you’re planning to do that, then I would suggest that you should stop.”

Yuri gawked when he heard Addison. His expression changed as he looked at Addison and said, “I didn’t expect Mister Addison to know this despite being very busy. But the Neutral Alliance didn’t only do that, we also have another thing prepared. I’d bet Mister Zhao Hai would be interested in it.”

Not only Addison, even Zhao Hai was moved by Yuri’s words. What does Zhao Hai need to see in the Alliance? Do they still have another card to play?

After thinking of this, Zhao Hai told Addison, “Tell him I’ll go. Let him set a time and place. I will personally go there for a discussion.”

Addison complied, then he looked at Yuri and said, “City Lord Yuri, I have nothing else to ask. Please set the date and time. The Young Master said that he will go.”

Yuri stared at Addison who accepted the request. In the Underworld, it was rare for someone to be unaware about contracts. And as long as a contract was made, the master and his subordinates would be able to mentally communicate. Yuri looked at Addison, it seems like he was communicating with Zhao Hai, could it be?

Addison’s reputation in the Underworld was quite resounding. Not only because of his formidable strength, it was also because he was an unruly fellow. In Yuri’s eyes, people like Addison would rather die than enter into a contract. Therefore, Yuri was surprised when he saw that Addison seems to be in a contractual relationship.

However, Yuri didn’t dwell on it too long. He quickly replied, “That would be best. We’re inviting Mister to visit Holy Bone City in three days. Is that fine?”

Addison received Zhao Hai’s confirmation, naturally he nodded and said, “Alright, then three days later the Young Master will visit Holy Bone City.”

Yuri nodded, then he stood up and gave Addison a bow before saying, “Then I will say my goodbyes. I will be waiting for Mister Zhao Hai three days later in Holy Bone City.”

Addison also stood up and said, “Alright, City Lord Yuri can go. I won’t be escorting you out.”

Yuri nodded, then he fluttered towards the exit. Addison looked at Yuri’s back and coldly snorted. In his mind, he told Zhao Hai, “Young Master, we should teach him a lesson. This guy is too impolite.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “No need. I’ll see what they plan to do in three days. You will remain here.” Addison complied.

Chapter 1059: Backer from the Cultivation Realm

Zhao Hai was currently sitting inside Guli’s bone carriage. Holy Bone City was now quite close. Naturally, he was using his spiritual force to scan the city. Holy Bone City was just like any other city in the Underworld. It was unlike the Dark Temple that had the ability to keep the Dark Mist away.

Holy Bone City’s outer image didn’t differ too much from Dry Bone City, it was just slightly larger. However, Zhao Hai noticed that while city walls were made out of ordinary stone besides the gates, one shouldn’t discount the gates, they seem to be made out of the huge jade-white bones that Zhao Hai had taken into the Space. Although the city was low-key in its other aspects, this door shows how extraordinary the city was.

Zhao Hai smiled faintly, he knew that this was hidden arrogance. It was like back on Earth where there were rich people who loved to act low-key. Things such as riding a bicycle, wearing normal looking clothes, without people knowing that the watch they were wearing was actually a limited edition luxury item. The watch would be so expensive that it would be enough to scare people.

Zhao Hai didn’t have too many following him, only Guli and Jiang Zheng. They were one of the first people who followed him when he arrived in the Underworld. Naturally, his feelings towards them were more than normal. After they dealt with the Dark Temple, the two followed Zhao Hai.

Normally, the two would be inside the Hell Space practicing, they wouldn’t always follow Zhao Hai. But when they do, they would be in their human-form. They don’t appear as a zombie or skeleton in front of Zhao Hai.

This time, Zhao Hai took the two with him to see Holy Bone City and the Neutral Alliance. Naturally, the two would be in their zombie and skeleton form.

The bone carriage slowly went closer towards the city. When the carriage arrived outside the gates, a bang was heard before it opened. What met Zhao Hai’s eyes were two lines of skeletons wearing armor. However, their armor wasn’t the same as the bone armor that Zhao Hai had inside the Space. Instead they were just armor made out of ordinary bones. Nevertheless, these skeletons still looked quite majestic.

The weapons of these skeletons were also the same in the form of a long spear. Each Undead stood still, showing majesty and power.

After that, more Undead walked out of the city. These Undead were in all forms, skeletons, zombies, vampires, and many more. What was common between these Undead was the fact that they were all King-level experts.

Zhao Hai made the bone carriage stop. Then he walked out of the carriage followed by Guli and Jiang Zheng. The three proceeded to walk towards the Undead.

In front of this group was a zombie. It had black skin and its muscles had completely withered. With his dark and thin arms, he looked like an old tree root.

However, this shrivelled looking zombie actually made Zhao Hai’s eyes shrink. This was because he can feel a dangerous aura on this Zombie.

Most importantly, Zhao Hai felt the same energy on this zombie on the Yin Wind Ghost Emperor’s beast skeletons. This was what caught Zhao Hai’s attention.

Also, Yuri was following behind this zombie, showing that it held a high position inside the Alliance.

While Zhao Hai was sizing up the zombie, the zombie stepped forward to greet Zhao Hai. He laughed and gave a bow before saying, “Tiande has seen Mister ZHao Hai. Mister’s presence is a great pleasure.” Zhao Hai gave a smile as he replied, “Mister is too polite. Just call me Zhao Hai.”

The other Undead also gave Zhao Hai a salute. Even though these Undead had a hint of hostility, Zhao Hai didn’t care and just returned their greeting.

After the two sides exchanged greetings, Tiande gestured towards Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, please.” Then he led Zhao Hai towards the city. Naturally, Zhao Hai wasn’t too polite. He took Guli and Jiang Zheng as he followed beside Tiande in heading towards the city.

Holy Bone City had five towers, of which Zhao Hai was taken to the top floor of the middle one. The room was cleanly arranged and had a lot of chairs inside. These chairs were made out of bones and were covered with animal leather. There was a magic formation inside the room to keep the Dark Mist out. There was also another formation on the ceiling, providing the place with a soft light.

After everyone has been settled, Tiande didn’t wait any longer as he began to talk, “We invited Mister over in order to discuss a future alliance. Mister destroyed the Dark Temple, fully intending to unify the Underworld. Although the Alliance had the same aspiration, we still hoped to see peace in the Underworld. We don’t want too many conflicts to occur in the Underworld. Because of this, we shall recognize Mister’s rule of the plane.” After he spoke those words, Tiande stopped and looked at Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai’s face was covered, therefore nobody could see any of his expressions. Zhao Hai didn’t answer immediately, he knew that the other party still had more to say, so he waited.

After seeing that Zhao Hai didn’t respond, Tiande added, “The others and I would submit to Mister. However, we hope that we would be able to obtain freedom, maintaining our present life. Mister, what do you think?”

Zhao Hai looked at Tiande. He completely understood what Tiande wants, he wanted to be an autonomous state inside Zhao Hai’s rule. They would surrender to him, giving him reputation. However, with this set-up, Zhao Hai wouldn’t have much power inside the Neutral Alliance.

Zhao Hai was puzzled at Tiande. What gave this Zombie confidence to discuss terms with him?

Although the Alliance had amassed a lot of Experts in these past few days, they still fall short compared to the Dark Temple. And after Zhao Hai conquered the Dark Temple, the resources in his hands had steadily increased. In normal conditions, the Alliance simply didn’t have the strength to discuss anything with him. However, the Alliance actually did, and with huge confidence at that. Zhao Hai couldn’t help but be confused.

This time, Tiande looked at Zhao Hai, worry completely absent from his face. He just sat there and watched Zhao Hai, looking like a piece of black-colored bamboo.

Zhao Hai looked at Tiande and said, “I need a reason. Why would I grant you this treatment?”

Tiande seems to expect Zhao Hai’s question. He smiled and Zhao Hai and said, “Mister you should have already seen the strength of the Alliance. We aren’t that weak. If we fight, then Mister’s losses would be huge.”

After he said this, Tiande stopped. Then Zhao Hai responded, “This isn’t a good reason. You and I both know that death doesn’t mean anything in the Underworld.”

Tiande nodded and said, “Mister is correct, in the Underworld, death doesn’t mean anything. But Mister, how much do you know about the Dark God?”

Tiande’s words made Zhao Hai’s eyes shrink. The Dark God that Tiande meant was naturally the Yin Wind ghost Emperor. But it seems like Tiande wasn’t talking about the Ghost Emperor’s incarnation, but the Ghost Emperor himself!

Zhao Hai was surprised because he was certain that the Yin Wind Ghost Emperor was from the Cultivation Realm. Judging by Tiande’s words, it seems like he knew about the ghost Emperor. Was Tiande also connected to the Cultivation Realm?

At the thought of this, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but probe Tiande. He nodded and said, “I know something. The Dark God used several mystical spells while fighting me. He also said that he was a Ghost Emperor, was he the Emperor of the Plane? But even if he was the Emperor, I still wasn’t afraid. If I can defeat him once, then I could defeat him twice.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, a smile couldn’t help but bloom on Tiande’s face. He looked at Zhao Hai and shook his head, “Mister, you don’t know much about the Dark God. He calls himself the Yin Wind Ghost Emperor. And he isn’t the Emperor of the plane. Instead, he is an Expert from a higher realm.”

Zhao Hai pretended to be shocked, “Higher realm? There’s a plane higher than the Underworld? That’s impossible. I have been amassing subordinates ever since I was born. All of them might come from different planes big and small, but none of them described a plane higher than the Underworld!”

Looking at Zhao Hai’s reaction, Tiande couldn’t help but sneer a little. He said, “Then Mister has misunderstood. The Underworld isn’t the highest-level plane. There is a plane much higher, it is a plane called the Immortal Realm!”

“Immortal Realm?” Zhao Hai was startled, he expected Tiande to mention the Cultivation Realm. He didn’t think that Tiande would say Immortal Realm, is it a plane higher than the Cultivation Realm?

Tiande looked at Zhao Hai and nodded, “Right, the Immortal Realm. The Yin Wind Ghost Emperor is from that plane. And he isn’t an Emperor of that plane, but merely an ordinary expert. In the Immortal Realm, there are a lot more Experts like the Yin Wind Ghost Emperor. Also, what Mister fought before isn’t the realm Ghost Emperor, but merely his projection. And that projection only had 1% of the real Yin Wind Ghost Emperor’s strength.”

When he heard this, Zhao Hai could affirm that the Immortal Realm that Tiande was talking about was actually the Cultivation Realm, it was just another name to make it sound imposing. Zhao Hai looked at Tiande and said, “How did Mister know about these matters? How can I be sure that you’re not lying to me?”

Tiande looked at Zhao Hai and smiled, “Mister doesn’t have to suspect my words. The Neutral Alliance has a backer from the Immortal Realm. It is because of this backer that the Yin Wind Ghost Emperor didn’t dare to be ruthless against us.”

Although Zhao Hai had already guessed this result, he could still say that he was surprised upon hearing Tiande. Zhao Hai looked at Tiande and said ,”Is that really true?”

Tiande nodded and said, “Of course its true. Our backer is different from the Yin Wind Ghost Emperor. While the Ghost Emperor is just an ordinary expert, our backer belongs to a huge group in the Immortal Realm. However, our backer’s group isn’t an overbearing influence, but instead a group that focuses on business. The Neutral Alliance is no more than an acquisition point that our backer placed in the Underworld. We aren’t even considered a branch. Ninety-nine percent of the things in our hands is useless in the Immortal Realm, this goes to show how little we are in comparison.”

Upon hearing Tiande, Zhao Hai knew that this so-called backer was someone from a trading company or something like that. However, the fact that they were able to penetrate the Underworld while having the Yin Wind Ghost Emperor ignore them means that their group is not small in the Cultivation Realm.

Zhao Hai looked at Tiande and said, “Mister, I don’t know how any of these things could be useful to me. Is it because of your backer that I would have to give you face? Mister Tiande, don’t forget, the Yin Wind Ghost Emperor only gave the Neutral Alliance face because he is from the Immortal Realm. He is afraid that your backer would retaliate against him. However, I’m not from the Immortal Realm. Any person from the Immortal Realm couldn’t come here. Even if they are strong, how could they eliminate me? If they really had the ability, then you wouldn’t have invited me over. Instead, your backer could just send someone to eliminate me.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Tiande stared. Zhao Hai’s words were on point. Those from the Cultivation Realm couldn’t come to the Underworld. If they were able to mobilize the power of the Cultivation Realm, then there wouldn’t have any discussion with Zhao Hai, they would have already came and occupied the plane.

Also, Tiande wasn’t telling the truth. The Underworld had a lot of things that were valuable to the Cultivation Realm. Otherwise, the forces behind Tiande wouldn’t have risked offending someone like the Ghost Emperor. Even if it was dangerous, they still went forward and made an acquisition point in the plane.

Despite his expression changing, Tiande still said, “Mister, think about the Underworld, this plane is poor in resources. Even if Mister becomes the plane’s ruler, what could you gain? Mister will just look at the Dark Mist and Blood Ponds all day. But as long as Mister establishes an alliance with us, then Mister would be able to trade and enjoy the unique items from the Immortal Realm. Mister can eat immortal fruit and drink immortal wine. That is a life a king should live, isn’t it?”

Zhao Hai pretended to be distracted, he looked at Tiande and said, “Can I have the good fortune of knowing the name of your backer?”

When Tiande heard Zhao Hai, he couldn’t help but feel awkward. He wouldn’t dare say the name of their backer. He hesitated for a moment before he finally shook his head, “I’ll have to be unfair to mister. I cannot just mention the name of our backers. But Mister can rest assured, every transaction you do will surely be completed.”

Zhao Hai looked at Tiande and laughed, “Tiande, are you that naive? If I kill you, then what stops your backers from talking to me? Why would they need the Neutral Alliance?”

Chapter 1060: Tiande’s Instruction

When Tiande heard Zhao Hai, he couldn’t help but gawk. He looked strangely at Zhao Hai, he didn’t expect him to turn ruthless this quickly. The other Under also looked at Zhao Hai with strange expressions, it seems like they were watching a good show.

Naturally, Zhao Hai didn’t really intend to replace Tiande’s position. The reason he acted this way was because he wanted to force Tiande’s last hand. Only then would he make a move.

Tiande looked at Zhao Hai, then he suddenly smiled, “Mister Zhao Hai is truly realistic, thinking about this too quickly. However, I would have to disappoint you. Our backers fully support me and would only work with me. Besides me, they wouldn’t work with other people. So if Mister really wants to trade with the Immortal realm, then it would be incorrect to dispose of me.”

At this time, everyone turned to look at Zhao Hai to see what his next move would be. Zhao Hai looked at these people and smiled, “So you’re saying that your backer wanted you to monopolize the transactions in the Underworld?”

Tiande looked at Zhao Hai, his two eyes flashed a cold glint as he replied, “Correct, that is what I am saying.” He wanted to give Zhao Hai a lesson. He wanted to let Zhao Hai understand that if Zhao Hao wanted to live a better life in the Underworld, then he would have to rely on the Alliance.

Zhao Hai looked at Tiande’s expression. He gently sighed as he waved towards Guli and said, “Guli, tell him. We’ve been playing for some time now, I’ve run out of patience.”

Guli just received Zhao Hai’s message mentally, naturally he knows how to respond. He nodded to Zhao Hai and said, “Yes, Young Master.” Then he turned to Tiande, “Tiande, the person behind you is too greedy. Also, your understanding of the Young Master is too little. Do you really think that the Young Master is unaware that your Immortal Realm is just the Cultivation Realm? Do you really think that the Young Master is clueless about the Yin Wind Ghost Emperor? The Young Master initially wanted to find out who your backer is, but since you won’t tell, the Young Master has lost interest. To be honest, the Young Master’s presence in the Underworld is also because of a Cultivator. Our backer is in control of the Divine Realm, the Demon Realm, the Ark Continent, and other big and small planes. Or do you really think that the Young Master reached his current position by relying on his own ability? You want to monopolize the plane’s resources? Stop dreaming. The Young Master is here to take the entire Underworld. As for our backer, I have to apologize but I can’t tell you. Now, are you ready to die?”

If Lu Wei heard these words, then he would be mad to the point of spitting blood. Zhao Hai just pointed two powerful enemies his way, and these were people who shouldn’t be provoked.

Of course, Guli said all these things because Zhao Hai told him to. Zhao Hai was going to put out an arrogant demeanor, showing that someone from the Cultivation Realm was truly behind him. This will prompt Tiande’s backers to look into it and bring trouble to Lu Wei.

Now that things had reached this point, even if Lu Wei wanted to explain himself, he wouldn’t be able to. From what Zhao Hai can see, the Yin Wind Ghost Emperor as well as Tiande’s backers weren’t pushovers. They wouldn’t give Lu Wei any opportunity to explain.

Lu Wei was Zhao Hai’s greatest worry. After Zhao Hai enters the Cultivation Realm, Lu Wei would be his greatest threat. After all, Lu Wei had already lost too much face by dealing with Zhao Hai. As long as Zhao Hai ascends, Lu Wei would certainly chase him down.

Because of this, Zhao Hai would take every opportunity to splash filthy water towards Lu wei. If the Yin Wind Ghost Emperor or Tiande’s backer kills Lu Wei, then Zhao Hai’s greatest threat would be eliminated.

As soon as Tiande and the others heard Guli, they were shocked. Then their expressions changed, they didn’t expect Guli to say this.

Zhao Hai looked at Tiande’s expression and smiled faintly, “Tiande, the Underworld belongs to us. Wanting autonomy is just courting death. In any case, I can’t blame you. I will be taking my leave. The next time we meet will be in the battlefield.” After saying that, Zhao Hai waved his hand, making a spatial rift appear. The rift took Zhao Hai, Guli, and Jiang Zheng in before vanishing.

Seeing Zhao Hai vanish, Tiande’s face turned dark. He can affirm that Zhao Hai was playing with them. The Neutral Alliance had just been played.

Tiande looked at the Undead around him, then he sighed and said, “Everyone, we’ve been played by Zhao Hai. There’s no need to ponder over it, you all go back and prepare. There is going to be a fight. In the meantime, I will relay this matter to the Exalted Immortal. Let’s hope that the Exalted Immortal would help us.”

The Undead complied before they turned around and left. After seeing that everyone had left, Tiande flew towards the ceiling and knocked on several spots. The ceiling immediately opened up, allowing entry. Tiande proceeded to fly in.

Inside the opening wasn’t a large space, just a normal room inside a building. Only a few people knew about this place. But on the floor of the room was a formation. The formation was made out of glowing, glittering stones. With the sparkling light that they were emitting, they looked more attractive than gemstones.

This was a unique stone to the Cultivation Realm called the spirit stone. This formation actually needed spirit stones to function. Besides the formation, there was also a table with a beast skin and bone pen on top.

Tiande went towards the table and then wrote on the beast skin, “My lord, we’ve found out that Zhao Hai has been sent by someone from the Cultivation Realm. His master has control over the Divine Realm, the Demon Realm, and the Ark Continent that is near the Underworld. As for who the person was, Zhao Hai didn’t give any other clue. At this time, Zhao Hai has decided to fight against us. I ask my Lord for guidance.”

After he finished writing, Tiande curled the beast skin and then placed it on the formation on the ground. Then he injected his own energy into the formation. After the formation flashed a few times, the curled beast skin disappeared.

Seeing the curled beast skin disappeared, Tiande sighed and said, “This transmission formation is really good. It’s a pity that the formation isn’t powerful or else I would have returned to the Cultivation Realm. Meanwhile, they could send an expert to deal with Zhao Hai. Leaving us with great resources to sell.”

Right, what Tiande just used was a transmission formation. It was a paired formation, specifically used for transport. As long as an energy was provided, the transmission formation would send things towards the formation it was paired with. It would arrive almost instantaneously, it was very convenient.

However, this transmission formation has a weak point, it cannot transport life nor could it send things with spirituality. It can only send ‘dead’ items. Even if the item had intellect, as long as it possessed spirit, it would be broken by the formation, losing its soul in the process.

Actually, there were transmission formations in the Cultivation Realm that allowed the transport of people. However, this type of formation also had its own weakness, it cannot transport people across planes. Just like in the Underworld, one couldn’t send people from the Cultivation Realm  across a transmission formation. It was precisely because of this that Tiande could only send inanimate objects through the formation.

But even if one removes the limitations of the formation, Tiande’s hope of sending Experts to deal with Zhao Hai was still impossible; the laws of the plane just wouldn’t allow it. One must know that the stronger a person is, the more the plane would want to reject them. Just like travelling from the Divine Realm to the Ark Continent. If a God-rank went to the Ark Continent, they would definitely be repelled by the plane, they wouldn’t be able to stay too long in the continent.

This rule would affect the people from the Cultivation Realm more. The difference in strength between the Cultivators and the God-ranks was very huge. Because of this, it was practically impossible for them to step foot in the Underworld. At the same time, if they came, then their strength would have to be reduced to the point where they would be as strong as the Underworld’s residents. In this case, nobody from the Cultivation Realm would want to do it. Not only would they be punished by the plane, they would also be taking a risk on their lives.

The reason why the people from the Cultivation Realm only sent incarnations to the lower realms was because these incarnations weren’t too strong and wouldn’t be punished by the plane.

As for Tiande’s existence, it was an expensive matter. Since the transmission formation couldn’t transport spiritual beings, the force behind Tiande had to refine his Zombie body first and had it sent to the Underworld. After that, they used a special artifact to send Tiande’s soul over. And using the magical connection between the body and soul, Tiande was able to recover his body. This made it possible for Tiande to exist.

The Yin Wind Ghost Emperor used the same method to send his beast skeletons. This process didn’t need transmission formations. Instead, they would use techniques in order to find weak points in the firmament. Then they penetrate these weak points in order to send things through. This method consumed too much resources, therefore not a lot of people could do it.

Chapter 1061: Response from the Cultivation Realm

Establishing an acquisition point in the Underworld caused Tiande’s backer to spend a lot of resources. However, they still had to do it. This was because the Underworld had plenty of treasures that the Cultivation Realm needed.

Normally, lower realms wouldn’t have much treasures that Cultivators would fancy. This was because the environment of the Cultivation Realm and lower realms were fundamentally different. Therefore, treasures normally wouldn’t appear in the lower realms.

However, the Underworld was different. This was a plane that was bordering pure yin. Such a place could give birth to valuable yin attribute treasures. These treasures has  huge uses in the Cultivation Realm.

Tiande’s identity in the Cultivation Realm was a mere battle corpse. However, his backer painstakingly made him go to the Underworld. He was selected because he was fairly weak. And after he was refined to strengthen him a bit, he was sent to the Underworld in order to obtain the plane’s treasures.

Tiande’s actions in the Underworld were controlled by the person behind him. It was precisely because of this that Tiande was able to direct the Neutral Alliance to do business as well as keep the plane’s power balance. His backers were good at this aspect.

However, everything changed with Zhao Hai’s arrival. Zhao Hai’s strength and the number of his Undead was beyond their imagination. He was able to become a supreme power in the Underworld in a short time. Within that short time, Zhao Hai completely destroyed the calculations that Tiande made. The situation that they had maintained for many years have been completely destroyed.

It was for this reason that they wanted to have a discussion with Zhao Hai, hoping that Zhao Hai would give them autonomy. They thought that Zhao Hai wouldn’t have any connections with the Cultivation Realm.

But to their dismay, not only was Zhao Hai connected to the Cultivation Realm, he was also unafraid of gaining more enemies. They didn’t think that Zhao Hai would actually dare to be so bold against people from the Cultivation Realm. He was even planning to go against them and contend for the ownership of the Underworld.

Before long, the transmission formation flashed with brilliant lights. A rolled beast skin appeared in the middle of the formation. Tiande immediately took the beast skin and read its contents: “You must protect our position in the Underworld. In a while we would be passing a few weapons to you. Use these weapons to defend against Zhao Hai. It would be best if you could kill him and completely control the Underworld.”

At this moment, the formation flashed once more. This time, a pile of weapons appeared. The weapons numbered several hundred. They weren’t big, there were swords that were at the size of a hairpin.

However, Tiande knew that these were weapons from an upper realm, and they were very strong. The weapons of the Underworld wouldn’t be able to contend against these.

Tiande immediately took the weapons from the formation. After that, the formation flashed once more, another pile of weapons was seen. Before long, Tiande had taken out about 3000 weapons from the formation.

When the transmission formation stopped shining, Tiande took another beast skin and wrote, “My Lord can feel relieved. This subordinate will surely kill Zhao Hai and protect the Underworld.”

After sending the beast skin, Tiande took the weapons to the hall below. Then he called over his subordinates and told them about the uses of the weapons. After that, Tiande had the stronger Undead pick the weapons for themselves

Naturally, the Undead wouldn’t be polite and picked the weapons they most liked. Although these weapons looked small, they would enlarge as soon as energy was injected to them. Moreover, the Undead didn’t need to use their hands to wield the weapons. The weapons could fly in the air and attack enemies from several li(0.5km) away

It can be said that if one’s spiritual force was strong enough, then they would be able to send their weapons hundreds of li to kill their enemy. Naturally, the spiritual force needed to control these weapons was quite huge, and the requirements to make it fly was even bigger. Even if these Undead had great weapons, the most they could control the weapons would be several li ahead. Also, they can launch their weapons no more than five times. If they attacked more than that, then the weapon might not be able to return.

But despite these limitations, the weapons still improved their strengths by at least threefold. This was enough to tip the scales of a war.

However, what they didn’t know was the fact that everything that just happened had fallen into Zhao Hai’s eyes. After vanishing and returning to the Space, Zhao Hai opened the monitor to see what Tiande and the others would do. Zhao Hai believed that after Guli said those words, Tiande would immediately ask for instructions from his backers. And it seems like he guessed correctly. After asking for guidance, Tiande was able to gain a lot of weapons from the Cultivation Realm.

When Zhao Hai saw these weapons, his expression turned dark as he coldly snorted and said, “You want to kill me using those weapons? Continue dreaming.”

Laura and the others weren’t by Zhao Hai’s side, they were still busy with the Processing Machine. However, Zhao Hai didn’t care about it. He waved his hand, then a map appeared on the monitor. On this map were small points. These dots were places that Zhao Hai wanted to scour, the places under the Dark Temple where the Heart Defending Clan buried their treasure rooms.

From the inheritance he gained from the giant heart, there were many treasures hidden in the Dark Temple’s territory. Some of these treasures were ores while some were plant essences. These things were prepared by the Heart Defending Clan, therefore they wouldn’t expire after a long time.

And besides these things, there were five treasure rooms that had magic artifacts inside. However, even if the artifacts were refined to an advanced level, they had yet to undergo the last step, so they were still incomplete.

Zhao Hai also learned the Heart Defending Clan’s refinement process. From the clan’s records, refining treasures was divided into four stages. These stages were: Smelting, Tempering, Forming, and Spirit Attachment.

Smelting and Tempering were the simplest steps. As long as one had the material, then one could smelt it with the appropriate flame. The length of smelting affected the quality of the weapon.

As for tempering, there were plenty of methods to do so. The simplest way was to use a hammer to temper the metal. But generally, this method could only be applied when making low-level equipment. As for high-level items, one generally used the spiritual force in addition to their own strength in order to temper the materials. Materials hammered using this method would become stronger.

The third step wasn’t so simple. If one wanted to make a personalized weapon, then Forming was very important. The weapons used by each person were different. Even if two identical blades were handed to two people, the way they use it would be different. In the end, after numerous uses, the blades would wear in accordance to their user’s habits.

If one wanted to make a weapon for himself, then they would need to be careful in the forming process. One must make a weapon that one was accustomed to. This way, one would not need to take a long time to use the weapon to their full potential.

The last step, Spirit Attachment, was the most difficult part in refining weapons. The spirit attached to the weapon would determine its level. Low-level items, categorized as 1st – 3rd level artifacts, couldn’t be attached with spirits. These weapons were limited by their materials. Because of this, artifacts up to the 3rd level were called low-level magic artifacts. The Heart Defending Clan deemed these artifacts as Inferior-grade artifacts.

But starting from the 4th-6th level, artifacts would be able to hold spirits. As for these weapons, only low level spirit souls could be attached. These souls would act just like puppets, listening to any instructions but couldn’t think for themselves. Such artifacts were called Intermediate-grade artifacts.

Artifacts on the 7th-9th level were called Advanced-grade artifacts. These artifacts can be attached with high-ranked souls. After Spirit Attachment, these artifacts would have autonomy and would be able to absorb energy from the surroundings. Aside from helping their masters attack, they could also aid their masters in their cultivation. These weapons were very formidable.

Above 7th-9th artifacts were items that were called Great Treasures. These treasures also had spirits inside them. Moreover, the wisdom of these spirits was very high. Great treasures were items that choose their masters instead of the other way around. They were leagues better than 9th-level artifacts. After being made, these treasures would then be able to freely choose their masters. Naturally, creating these Great Treasures needed world-shaking materials as well as difficult manufacturing methods. After years upon years of effort, the Heart Defending Clan managed to make five of these treasures. However, of these five, four of them were destroyed in the great war while the last treasure received great damage. That treasure was the cauldron that was now in Zhao Hai’s hands. And since the artifact’s spirit was seriously damaged, it can be said that it was an incomplete Great Treasure.

The magic artifacts that the Heart Defending Clan had in their treasure rooms were 7th-9th level artifacts. However, these artifacts didn’t have spirits. But once these items undergoes Spirit Attachment, they would then be able to demonstrate the strength of Advanced-grade Artifacts.

From what Tiande told his subordinates, Zhao Hai was able to tell that the weapons sent through transmission formations didn’t have spirits inside. In other words, Intermediate-grade and Advanced-grade weapons couldn’t be transported. This means that Tiande only had Inferior-grade artifacts in his hands.

Chapter 1062: A Sigh

The weapons that Tiande acquired were 1st-3rd level artifacts, inferior-grade goods. But despite so, these weapons were still formidable when used in the Underworld.

The materials used by the weapons were different than what Zhao Hai had seen in the Ark Continent or in the Divine Realm. These inferior-grade weapons used very advanced materials, some of which weren’t present in the Ark Continent and the Divine Realm.

Despite being inferior-grade weapons, these weapons were sharper than those found in the Ark Continent or the Divine Realm. It can be said that these items were very powerful.

However, Zhao Hai wasn’t worried about them. Although the buried treasures of the Heart Defending Clan weren’t complete, they were supposedly advanced-grade artifacts. Even if they were semi-finished, this didn’t mean that they couldn’t be used.

In fact, 1st-3rd level items only underwent the first three methods, there didn’t go through the last step. These advanced-grade weapons, although they had no spirit, were still much stronger than their inferior-grade counterparts.

The reason why Zhao Hai decided to take the Heart Defending Clan’s buried treasures was because he wanted to completely destroy Tiande.

Originally, Zhao Hai wanted to find these weapons after the Neutral Alliance had been dealt with. But now it seems like this matter needed to be taken care of immediately. Time was running out and Zhao Hai couldn’t wait, so he could only use the weapons now.

Although Zhao Hai had the Bone Armor Legion, he was still unsure if the bone armors were capable of blocking these inferior-grade weapons.

Zhao Hai was very clear about Tiande and the others’ strength. If it was only them, then he wouldn’t have been worried. However, now that these inferior-grade weapons had appeared, Zhao Hai began to feel a headache.

It was obvious that Tiande intended to hand the weapons over to the powerful undead. A team formed by these Undead was a force that shouldn’t be underestimated. The purpose of this team was the same as Zhao Hai’s Bone Armor Legion. To deal with this group, only something like the Bone Armor Legion would suffice.

However, Zhao Hai doesn’t know the attacking prowess of these inferior-grade weapons. If the Bone Legion couldn’t stop them, then the Bone Legion would lose a lot. This wasn’t what Zhao Hai wanted to see. Because of this, Zhao Hai decided to take out the weapons made by the Heart Defending Clan. Magic weapons needed to be dealt with using magic weapons, otherwise Tiande’s team would become Zhao Hai’s biggest challenger in unifying the Underworld.

Zhao Hai wanted to use the magic weapons to kill Tiande, deal with the Neutral Alliance, and destroy the transmission formation as soon as possible.

For Zhao Hai, the biggest threat wasn’t just Tiande. He was afraid of Tiande’s backers as well as the transmission formation. If Tiande fails to kill Zhao Hai, then he might send another message to the Cultivation Realm. In turn, this would cause more and more of these inferior-grade weapons to be sent over.

In a battle for attrition, Zhao Hai would certainly suffer a loss. After all, compared to the Cultivation Realm, the things in his hands still fall short. Because of this, Zhao Hai needed to end this matter quickly!

Only after dealing with Tiande and the transmission formation would Zhao Hai be able to break the Cultivation Realm’s connection with the Underworld. Only then could the Underworld be his.

Since Zhao Hai was now in complete control of the Dark Temple’s domain, he naturally wouldn’t be discreet in his search. He dug in the open since the Undead in his domain wouldn’t be able to betray him.

However, this bold and open digging was also still something Zhao Hai had to personally do. This was because the dots on the map didn’t represent a position, instead it showed regions of land. If Zhao Hai wanted to find these treasure rooms, then he would have to scour the area himself.

Extracting the treasure wasn’t a very difficult matter. The Heart Defending Clan’s treasure rooms were prepared for people on their own side. Because of this, there were no mechanisms nor traps on the path to the rooms.

While Zhao Hai went to pick up the treasures himself, he had Addison mobilize the army and station themselves on the border of the Neutral Alliance. Five days later, after Zhao Hai gained the treasures, the army had completely encircled the Alliance.

Zhao Hai’s harvest wasn’t small. The ores and plant essences that he took from the treasure rooms were all high quality goods. Not only did Zhao Hai gain these things, the Space had also levelled up to 120, it was a huge harvest.

Besides these, Zhao Hai also obtained 10 thousand advanced-grade artifacts. These artifacts were still incomplete, but in the meantime, they were still enough for Zhao Hai to use.

Zhao Hai prepared to hand these magic artifacts over to the Bone Armor Legion. With these weapons, as well as the bone armors, dealing with Tiande’s 3000 Undead would be no problem.

Tiande had been in the Underworld for many years. And during this time, he was not worried at all. He knew that although his weapons weren’t advanced-grade goods, they were still very useful in the Underworld.

The reason for this strong confidence was the fact that he had been a battle corpse back in the Cultivation Realm. After he was carefully refined, he was still able to maintain his memories. He was clear that magic artifacts were impossible to appear in the lower realms. Because of this, he knew that even 1st-level artifacts were extraordinary treasures in the Underworld. Now that he had 3000 of these artifacts, how could he be afraid of Zhao Hai?

Although Zhao Hai had already surrounded them, Tiande wasn’t too worried. Along with his high-ranked Undead, he just continued to look at the army outside the city. Both sides had a lot of undead, enough to blot out the skies. They were now ready to clash.

At this time, Zhao Hai’s bone carriage arrived just in front of Dry Bone City. He looked at Tiande on the city wall, he smiled faintly and said, “Tiande, I advise you to surrender. Or else you will surely die.” Tiande looked at Zhao Hai with disdain as he coldly snorted and said, “Zhao Hai, stop joking around. You should do the right thing and surrender to the Immortals. Or else, I will make sure that your soul will be crushed.”

Zhao Hai looked at Tiande and smiled, “Good, good. Let’s see who’s souls gets crushed first.” After he said that, Zhao Hai waved his hand and beckoned towards Dry Bone City.

Tiande also waved his hand, making the army behind him charge. Wars of the Undead have always been like this. They rarely did other preparations, everyone just goes into a huge melee. If you lose, you lose. If you win, then you win. The more experience you gained, then the more advantages you would have.

Zhao Hai didn’t command the army, this matter has already been handed over to Lizzy and Megan. He was just paying attention to Tiande.

On Tiande’s side were several high-ranked Undead. These were the Undead who were armed with the Cultivation Realm weapons. Zhao Hai wanted to wait for them to move, or else they would become a hindrance. Because of this, Zhao Hai wasn’t anxious to move. He wanted to see when Tiande would begin sending his people, and that would be the time that he would move as well.

Zhao Hai’s subordinates were very fierce. Moreover, although the army looked chaotic, with Lizzy and Megan as their commanders, the army was actually very well coordinated. This was very different compared to Tiande’s unsupervised Undead.

One side was coordinated while another was disorganized. With both sides having the same strength, victory and defeat could already be seen.

When Tiande saw that his Undead were being pressed by Zhao Hai’s, he couldn’t sit still anymore. He waved his hand as the 3,000 people team rushed out of the city. Each Undead in this team held magic weapons in their hands. Zhao Hai knew that Tiande’s final ace had appeared. It seems like he was planning on using this team to reverse the situation of the war.

As the team rushed out, Zhao Hai waved his hand. Then in front of Tiande’s Undead team, the Bone Armor Legion appeared, each one also having magic weapons in their hands. All in all, the legion numbered ten thousand people.

Tiande was anticipating to see his Undead kill in four directions. But now, a team of bone armored soldiers appeared. Tiande stared, especially at the weapons in the hands of the Undead. He couldn’t help but feel dizzy.

Tiande didn’t expect that, besides him, there was also another person who could obtain magic artifacts. Zhao Hai had artifacts! Moreover, he had more than him!

Tiande suddenly thought about Zhao Hai’s background. When he was reminded of this, he couldn’t help but feel annoyed. He was too proud to remember this matter.

Besides being annoyed, Tiande was also startled. His backer wasn’t just any small power in the Cultivation Realm, otherwise they wouldn’t have been able to scare the Yin Wind Ghost Emperor, making him keep his hands from the Neutral Alliance. But despite this, they were only able to send 3000 magic artifacts. Such endeavor wasn’t cheap.

And now, Tiande was actually facing a battalion of ten thousand undead, each carrying a magic artifact. Ten thousand magic artifacts, more than three times as many as Tiande’s. Who or what was Zhao Hai’s backer in the Cultivation Realm? Were they extremely terrifying beings?

At the thought of this, Tiande suddenly lost the mood to stand on the city wall. He had his men defend the wall before he hurriedly left Dry Bone City.

Tiande was now planning to return to Holy Bone City and pass the information over to his backers. However, he didn’t know that Zhao Hai noticed him leaving. Although the battle was very lively, Zhao Hai didn’t make a move. He focused all of his attention to Tainde. Now that Tiande was planning to depart, Zhao Hai’s figure also disappeared from sight.

Tiande was currently flying, burning with impatience. He knew that he would certainly suffer defeat, and it would be a disastrous one. After seeing the enemy take out 10 thousand magic artifacts, he knew that he would have no chance to change the situation.

At this time, Tiande was hoping that Zhao Hai’s attention would be placed on the battlefield. This way, he would be able to reach Holy Bone City smoothly and relay the news to his backers.

Holy Bone City wasn’t that far from Dry Bone City. In order to cope with Zhao Hai, the alliance had concentrated their military force. At this time, the Neutral Alliance only had 10 cities under their control. These cities formed a circular defense system with Holy Bone City in the middle.

Because of this, it wouldn’t take long for one to reach Holy Bone City using flight. Upon seeing Holy Bone City’s walls, Tiande couldn’t help but relax a bit.

But at this time, Tiande suddenly heard a sigh. His heart contracted, he listened and noticed that this sigh belonged to Zhao Hai. Then along with this sigh, a spatial rift appeared a hundred meters away. Zhao Hai’s figure was seen walking out from the spatial rift.

After seeing Zhao Hai, Tiande’s heart sank. He pulled his own sword out and pointed it towards Zhao Hai, “Zhao Hai, do you really want us to fight?”

Zhao Hai looked at Tiande and smiled, “Tiande, do you really think that I would give you an opportunity to report? You and I should know that we are just pawns, the real fight isn’t between us. Since my lord wants me to unify the Underworld, then I naturally wouldn’t want to make any mistakes. Otherwise, I would have a hard time explaining. I wouldn’t just let you report back to your superiors or else it might bring trouble to my lord. Because of this, you need to die today!”

Tiande’s heart sank deeply. He knew that today was his end. But then, he noticed that Zhao Hai was alone. As long as he can kill Zhao Hai, then everything else would be easy to do.

After thinking of this, Tiande sneered and said, “Zhao Hai, you really overestimate yourself, you even pursued me alone. Let me tell you this, I am from the Cultivation Realm. My body has been refined by my master, so I am far from an ordinary undead. It is you who will die today!”

Zhao Hai looked at Tiande with curiosity, “Really? Then prove it.”

Zhao Hai’s figure moved and proceeded to charge Tiande.

At the same time, Tiande gave out a grunt before throwing out his own sword. Despite seeing this, Zhao Hai didn’t stop. Instead, Zhao Hai’s body was suddenly wrapped by a layer of bones!

Clang! A loud sound was heard as Tiande’s flying sword hit Zhao Hai’s bone armor. But to Tiande’s surprise, the bone armor was actually able to successfully defend. The flying sword unexpectedly wasn’t able to puncture through the bone armor!

Chapter 1063: The Might of a Flying Sword!

While Tiande was stunned, Zhao Hai had already reached him. After which, Zhao Hai waved his blood ghost staff towards Tiande’s head.

Tiande immediately moved his body to the left. However, Zhao Hai already stretched his other hand and threw a net over.

The action was very sudden, Tiande simply didn’t have time to dodge. At this moment, his flying sword expanded in size and attempted to block the net.

Zhao Hai’s expression changed, he didn’t expect the flying sword to be this quick. The reason why he let the sword puncture him was in order to see the bone armor’s capabilities. And if the sword punctures through, it didn’t matter, he had already crystallized his body. It would be impossible for the other party to injure him.

Zhao Hai also wanted to use this opportunity to get close to Tiande while the flying sword was still away.

However, Zhao Hai seems to have underestimated Tiande’s flying sword. The sword was truly too quick. It seems like it had come back in just a snap. Zhao Hai never expected this.

Tiande also used this opportunity to quickly withdraw. He looked at Zhao Hai and sneered, “Zhao Hai, since you have a backer from the Cultivation Realm, then you should also be aware that there are different levels when it comes to magic artifacts. Although my subordinates are equipped with inferior-grade weapons, this weapon in my hand is an advanced grade weapon.”

Zhao Hai stared, then he smiled faintly and said, “It seems like your lord values you greatly, they even bestowed you an advanced-grade artifact. It seems like you weren’t just picking scraps in the Underworld all these years.”

Tiande coldly snorted as he looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Zhao Hai, this Underworld is too big. Do you really want to occupy all of it? Aren’t you afraid of choking?”

Zhao Hai laughed and said, “This Underworld originally didn’t belong to anyone. Those who have the strength would naturally own it. There’s no need to talk nonsense. Receive my attack!” Zhao Hai’s figure proceeded to move as he threw himself towards Tiande.

Tiande looked at Zhao Hai’s move, then he sneered, “Zhao Hai, I really pity you. You have done all these things for your master, yet he didn’t even give you a decent weapon. Is it really worth it following a master like that?”

Zhao Hai pretended to be angry as he swung his magic staff towards Tiande. In order to block, Tiande also attacked using his flying sword.

The speed of Tiande’s flying sword was truly astonishing. Upon seeing it, most King-level characters would surely turn red with hate. Moreover, besides the strength of impact provided by the sword, it would also emit a hidden ripple when met with an enemy’s attack. This ripple would target the enemy and proceed to destroy their body from the inside out. It can be said that the attack was quite vicious.

Zhao Hai had already crystallized his body the moment he fought with Tiande, this even included his internal organs. Zhao Hai clearly knew how powerful advanced-grade artifacts were. Because of this, he wouldn’t dare underestimate the strength of Tiande’s weapon.

Zhao Hai’s magic staff could also be used as a flying sword. However, Zhao Hai wasn’t able to learn how to control flying swords. After all, he always felt that using the staff as a flying sword wasn’t something easy to do. Because of this, he was intending to wait until he reaches the Cultivation Realm to do so. At this time, Zhao Hai was still using his staff as a melee weapon.

In his fight against Tiande this time, Zhao Hai was planning to see how Tiande would use the flying sword. Zhao Hai would also want to see if he could learn from watching Tiande. Being able to control the flying sword freely and with such distance, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but be astounded at the Zombie. This made him even more curious about Tiande’s identity.

Moreover, after a few clashes with Tiande, Zhao Hai discovered that the Zombie did indeed have the same aura as Yin Wind Ghost Emperor’s beast skeletons. In other words, he underwent the Corpse Refining method of the Cultivation Realm. This was what Zhao Hai was most curious about.

On the other hand, Tiande was very surprised at Zhao Hai. He knew very well about how strong advanced-grade flying swords were, he didn’t expect Zhao Hai’s staff to be able to block his sword. And it seems like there wasn’t even a hint of damage.

What Tiande didn’t know was the fact that Zhao Hai already had a lot of advanced-grade weapons. But despite this, Zhao Hai still felt that the flying swords were useless to him, his magic staff was already enough. Nevertheless, after acquiring these weapons, Zhao Hai tried them a few times.

After he tried the flying swords a few times, Zhao Hai began to understand the difference between advanced-grade and inferior-grade swords. Low-level swords only had basic functions such as turning bigger and smaller while also having the ability to fly. On the other hand, high-level swords had plenty of formations inside them. Additionally, the functions of these formations were different. Take Tiande’s flying sword for example. In addition to being fast, it could also use dark energy in order to wound its foe. Compared to low-level swords, this weapon was much more powerful.

What Zhao Hai wanted to do now was to mainly experience how people from the Cultivation Realm used their flying swords. It can be said that those from the Cultivation Realm had reached a superb level of control when it came to flying swords. Zhao Hai was sure that if Tiande was placed in the Cultivation Realm, then he wouldn’t be anything special. But one could see that the zombie’s control over his flying sword was still quite flawless.

Zhao Hai can also affirm that if nobody else appeared, Tiande could single-handedly dominate the Underworld. Nobody would be able to match his strength.

While Zhao Hai was feeling delight with his fight with Tiande, the battle at Dry Bone City still went on. Lizzy and Megan commanded the Undead Army in order to surround the Alliance’s Undead, the latter simply had no strength to push back. As for Tiande’s special team, they had already been overwhelmed by Zhao Hai’s much more superior Bone Armor Legion. The 3000 inferior-grade artifacts had already been sent to the Space.

But despite being sent to the Space, of the 3000 magic artifacts, less than 1000 had been perfectly preserved. As for the rest, they were all damaged, some of them couldn’t even be used anymore.

There was no other way to prevent this. Against Zhao Hai’s advanced-grade weapons, these inferior-grade ones would just crumble. It was lucky for these weapons to even survive a clash.

However, Lizzy and Megan didn’t feel bad about these damaged weapons. This was because they could still be recycled. With the Processing Machine’s help, these weapons would be patched up easily.

By now, Lizzy and Megan weren’t too frantic in their attacks. The two just sat in the living room alongside Laura and the others. The women looked like aunties shopping for groceries. They looked at the Undead on the monitor and would pluck any Undead they liked and sent it to the Space. Those who weren’t pleasing to their eyes were killed and harvested for their fiery souls.

The group treated the battle as a game as they pointed at several Undead. As for Zhao Hai’s battle, they simply didn’t care.

After going through a lot, they weren’t that worried about Zhao Hai anymore. They already knew that if Zhao Hai cannot beat his enemy, then he could just escape to the Space at any time. So instead of worrying about Zhao Hai, they might as well look for things they were interested in. Just like what they were doing at the present, as long as they find an Undead amusing, then they would just capture them.

If Addison and the others knew about what Lizzy and the others were doing, then who knows what their expressions would be like. It seems like the only ones capable of being this nonchalant in the Underworld would be Zhao Hai’s wives.

Zhao Hai didn’t know about any of these. He was currently trying to make Tiande go all out. In his estimation, Tiande was a bit stronger than Addison. But after using his flying sword, Tiande’s strength would be elevated by at least five layers. If Tiande used his flying sword to clash with Addison, then Addison would certainly die.

At the same time, Zhao Hai came to realize that using this battle to learn how to control flying swords was impossible. Presently he couldn’t even properly let the weapon fly. If he wanted to learn, then he would have to acquire a sword manual.

After coming to terms with this situation, Zhao Hai knew that there was already no use in trading hits with Tiande. It was time for the fight to end.

Upon thinking of this, Zhao Hai’s body moved as he began to turn back. To be honest, for Tiande, fighting with Zhao Hai gave him a lot of pressure. Although Zhao Hai didn’t have a flying sword, his weapon was no worse than one. Tiande’s sword could use dark energy in order to corrupt the opponent’s weapon, but this seems to be useless against Zhao Hai. After seemingly thousands of clashes, no damage could be visibly seen on Zhao Hai’s staff.

After seeing Zhao Hai turn back, Tiande was shocked, but he didn’t pursue. This was because he was very clear that Zhao Hai didn’t retreat because he didn’t have the strength. Zhao Hai just retreated because he wanted to.

When two people fight and one person suddenly retreats, then this meant that he might fully retreat or make a big move. Moreover, the outcome would most likely be decided by this move.

After thinking about this, Tiande became more careful as he made his flying sword go back. The sword proceeded to circle around his body, protecting him.

Zhao Hai looked at Tiande and smiled, “Let’s end this.” After he said that, his hand moved and threw his blood ghost staff!

Chapter 1064: Myriad Treasures Pavillion

After seeing Zhao Hai throw his weapon, Tiande couldn’t help but stare. However, he still heightened his senses. He knew that Zhao Hai’s weapon wasn’t anything ordinary. It seems to be harder than a flying sword. The only downside to this weapon was that it couldn’t be used as a flying sword, otherwise it would have been extremely formidable.

Tiande also knew that Zhao Hai wouldn’t just throw his weapon for no reason. There would certainly be a more ruthless move afterwards.

Under Tiande’s gaze, Zhao Hai’s magic staff didn’t fall to the ground. Instead, it just floated in mid-air, albeit not as graceful as a flying sword.

Tiande continued to focus his attention on Zhao Hai, he didn’t dare be careless even for a little bit. He was aware of Zhao Hai’s accomplishments. Would someone who eliminated the Dark Temple be a simple character? Tiande knew that although that old ghost only had his incarnation in the Temple, the strength of that incarnation couldn’t be underestimated. The old ghost was able to govern the Dark Temple for many years, that wasn’t something ordinary people could do.

Because of this, Tiande was very careful when he was fighting against Zhao Hai. He was clear that even if he brought his flying sword to the Dark Temple, he still wouldn’t be able to conquer it.

Zhao Hai looked at Tiande and chuckled, “Tiande, you said that I don’t have a flying sword. You’re correct. However, my master already told me that flying swords with no spirits inside are nothing. Because of this, he prepared another magical artifact for me. A sealing artifact!”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai speak about a sealing artifact, Tiande’s expression changed. He was aware about how terrifying sealing artifacts were.

These sealing artifacts weren’t used for sealing areas, but instead it can seal entities. It uses a secret method in order to seal the laws itself. Sealing artifacts were originally made by Cultivators in order to seal a demonic artifact.

In the Cultivation Realm, there were also distinctions between Cultivators and Demon Cultivators, like Lu Wei and Yin Wind Ghost Emperor. Powerful Demonic Cultivators would certainly use weapons with the yin attribute or something that was made with either ghost qi or demon qi. Wielded by Demonic Cultivators, the might of these items was formidable.

And after being used by Demonic Cultivators, these artifacts would be contaminated with demonic aura. If a weak Cultivator takes hold of these demonic artifacts, then they would certainly be corrupted. If this Cultivator doesn’t practice demonic arts, then they would surely die soon.

Because of this, people would generally destroy these artifacts once they acquired them. It was just too difficult to refine demonic items.

But there were a lot of advanced-grade demonic artifacts. The materials used to make these weapons were extremely valuable, it would be a pity to destroy them. Therefore, people could only find ways to refine these weapons. It was for this reason that sealing artifacts were invented.

The principle of these sealing artifacts was to seal a demonic artifact inside another artifact. Only then would the artifact be safe for others to use. While being sealed, the demonic qi would be refined bit by bit. When the demonic artifact was fully refined, then it could be reused completely.

Also, this sealing weapon had another use. It could effectively trick the enemy. If one was against a person with an inferior-grade artifact, then one might not treat the enemy seriously. However, what if that inferior-grade artifact suddenly turns out to be an advanced-grade weapon in the middle of a fight? This would surely change the tides of battle.

Zhao Hai didn’t hear about these sealing artifacts from the Heart Defending Clan, instead he got it from Lu Wei’s remnant soul. In the past, Lu Wei suffered a loss from sealing artifacts. Because of this, the impression of the artifacts on him was very deep. And due to this memory, Zhao Hai was able to know about them.

Zhao Hai intended to throw his staff and then saying that it was a sealing artifact in order to fool Tiande. Sure enough, upon hearing this, Tiande’s expression immediately changed.

If Zhao Hai really took out a sealing artifact, then that would truly be scary. Making a single sealing artifact wasn’t easy. Even in the Cultivation Realm, only elder-level characters would make these artifacts and hand them over for their younger descendants. This way, these younger generations would have life-saving methods when exploring the outside world.

It can be said that sealing artifacts weren’t simple items. And because he knew this, Tiande couldn’t help but be afraid.

At this moment, Zhao Hai murmured, “Transform, suppress!”

Just as Zhao Hai’s voice fell, the floating magic staff suddenly emitted massive amounts of red lights. Then the staff broke down and became a huge red cauldron. This cauldron immediately flew into the air and opened its mouth to cover Tiande. The cauldron moved too fast, even if Tiande wanted to defend using his flying sword, it was already too late. After a spark from the flying weapon, Tiande was swallowed up.

A spatial rift appeared before Tiande was thrown into the Space. However, Zhao Hai didn’t immediately follow. Instead, he quickly flew towards Holy Bone City and entered the small room on the ceiling. After having Cai’er record the transmission formation, Zhao Hai went on to completely destroy it.

Only after destroying the formation did Zhao Hai begin to relax. Zhao Hai knew that the Underworld was now his.

The reason why Zhao Hai didn’t reveal the truth while fighting Tiande was because he didn’t want to ruin the impression that he had a master in the Cultivation realm. He couldn’t risk everything over a simple mishap. Therefore, Zhao Hai didn’t showcase the strength of his staff too much. He acted every move he made, making sure that there would be no flaw.

Although Zhao Hai knew that the people from the Cultivation Realm got their news through that beast skin, he still didn’t dare to be negligent. The means of the Cultivation Realm were endless, and the people behind Tiande weren’t simple. In this situation, Zhao Hai would have to be careful. He was afraid that Tiande’s memories would be sent back to the Cultivation Realm. If that was the case, then it would be best to tell Tiande nothing. If people discover Zhao Hai’s secrets, then instead of causing trouble for Lu Wei, Zhao Hai would gain another powerful enemy!

Zhao Hai had always been a careful person. He would rather miss an opportunity than go too far. To be honest, this kind of temperament would never take anybody to great heights. It was only because of the Space that Zhao Hai was able to reach his current state.

After taking care of Holy Bone City’s matters, Zhao Hai returned to the Space. Upon entering, Zhao Hai saw that Laura and the others were still happily playing their game. Looking at their enthusiasm, Zhao Hai didn’t know whether he should laugh or cry.

However, Zhao Hai smiled in the end. Seeing Laura and the others like this made him relieved. As long as they were happy, then he was happy.

Zhao Hai didn’t disturb them, instead he returned to his own room and called Tiande over. Tiande had been sent to the Space’s warehouse, so now that he was summoned by Zhao Hai, the Space immediately issued a prompt, “Hostile being detected. Subduing, successfully subdued. Strange communication link detected on the Undead’s body, interrupting link. Link has been interrupted.” Then there were no other prompts.

But what made Zhao Hai’s heart jump was the bit at the end. Did the Space just discover a hidden communication link inside Tiande? After having thought of this, Zhao Hai quickly turned to Tiande and asked, “Tiande, could you directly contact the Cultivation Realm? Were you able to relay what just happened to them?”

Tiande shook his head and replied, “Replying to the Young Master. I cannot. If I want to contact the Cultivation Realm, then I would  have to write on the beast skin.”

Zhao Hai knit his brows and said, “That what was that unusual communication link about?”

Tiande immediately replied, “Young Master, that link was installed the moment my body has been refined. That link would activate the moment I die. After my spiritual imprint gets erased, the people from the Cultivation Realm would immediately see the scenes one hour before I died. It has been integrated into my body, there’s no way for me to remove it.”

Zhao Hai nodded, he finally understood. This communication link was the same as things he read back on Earth. There would be bombs that would be connected to a person’s heart. Once the heart stops beating, then the bomb would explode. Tiande had the same thing, once his spiritual force dissipates, then the communication link would immediately activate.

But as the matter stands, Zhao Hai could feel relief. As long as Tiande wasn’t passing information over to the Cultivation Realm in real time, then everything was fine. Otherwise, Zhao Hai wouldn’t know what to do when the people from the Cultivation Realm found his flaws.

Zhao Hai let out a long breath. Then he turned to Tiande and asked, “Tiande, which influence from the Cultivation Realm do you belong to?”

Tiande nodded and answered, “Young Master, I belong to one of the five biggest trading companies in the Cultivation realm, the Myriad Treasures Pavilion. In the past, the pavilion obtained some coordinates. After finally deciding to try looking for it, an Elder managed to see the Underworld. And after seeing the special properties of the plane, they immediately thought of sending someone to collect yin attribute materials for them. And thus I was sent over.”

Chapter 1065: Tiande’s Past Life

Zhao Hai nodded before asking once more, “How do you know all of this?”

When Tiande heard Zhao Hai’s question, the dried up skin on his face twitched unconsciously. Then he sighed and said, “Replying to the Young Master. I wasn’t born a zombie back in the Cultivation Realm. I was a disciple of an orthodox sect, a sword sect. It was only later on that I was refined into a zombie.”

Zhao Hai’s brow couldn’t help but go up. He looked at Tiande and said, “Continue.”

Tiande nodded, “Although my sword sect isn’t a strong influence in the Cultivation Realm, it was still a medium-grade sect, it is still quite powerful. I was deemed as a talent in the sect. At age 20, I reached body tempering. At age 21, I successfully entered qi condensation. There were a lot of people in the sect that called me a rare talent.” After he said that, Tiande’s eyes turn red as he recalled his life.

Killing intent can be seen on Tiande’s eyes as he continued to recall, his voice became colder and colder, “But I didn’t expect that my outstanding talent would actually draw me into a fatal disaster. An Elder of our sect had a sole grandson that was practically a waste. Ying Ran ate precious medicinal pills while he was growing up. But despite this, he only had the same strength as me when he reached the age of 20. If I consumed those pills instead, then I would have already been a foundation establishment expert. It was because of this fact that Ying Ran became jealous of me. In the end, he used his grandfather’s influence to issue a mission that would kill me in the end. At that time, I wasn’t aware of the real goal of the mission. It was already too late when I found out that I was supposed to deal with a famous Nascent Soul demonic expert. Ghost Hand Merchant, Jia Dingtian!”

Tiande gave out a sigh before continuing, “Although this Jia Dingtian is already at a Nascent Soul stage, he still kept with his ruthlessness. Moreover, he was an assassin in the Cultivation Realm. He would accept cash in return for his service. He also had a formidable demonic art, Living Corpse Refining Technique.”

Upon hearing this, Zhao Hai’s heart couldn’t help but turn cold. Judging by its name, the Living Corpse Refining Technique should be a sinister method. But Zhao Hai didn’t disturb Tiande as he continued, “As its name suggests, the Living Corpse Refining Technique refines a living person’s body. Not only would the corpse retain its soul, it would also have all of its memories, even some emotions. The process of refinement was very painful. Moreover, you can feel it all the time!”

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but feel cold. He doesn’t know the exact process of refining, but he can be certain that retaining a person’s memories and emotions wouldn’t be an easy process. It might even be multiple times more painful than being burned alive.

Tiande went on, “When I was captured by Ghost Hand Merchant Jia Dingtian, he used his technique in order to refine my living body. While in the process, he told me that the sect’s elder was the one who wanted me killed. However, the Elder didn’t give the instruction to turn me into a living corpse. Instead, it was the Elder’s Grandson who wanted me refined.”

After speaking up to here, Tiande let out a long breath and then said, “After being refined into a living corpse, I was no longer able to progress in my cultivation. I was at Qi Condensation stage before I was refined. Low-ranked living corpses like me had little to no use in the Cultivation Realm. But this time, the Myriad Treasures Pavillion actually needed low-level corpses. Because of this, Jia Dingtian sold me to the Pavillion.”

Tiande let out another long breath, “The Myriad Treasures Pavillion refined me once again. Moreover, from what I could hear, their secret technique involves separating my soul and my body. Then they would deliver my body to the Underworld first before attaching my soul to a inferior-grade artifact and then sending it second. The artifact would be attracted to my body by using my soul. Before long, my soul and body were reunited. This is how I ended up living in the Underworld.”

Zhao Hai didn’t expect Tiande to go through all these twists and turns. He immediately asked, “Once you arrived in the Underworld, aren’t you able to separate from the pavilion’s control?”

Tiande shook his head, “I cannot. While the Myriad Treasures Pavillion refined me, they gave heavy emphasis on restricting my soul. If I dared to break their control, then that restriction would activate, dissipating my soul, killing me instantly.”

Zhao Hai knit his brows, “If what I heard was right, then could the pavilion send countless people like you in the Underworld?”

Tiande shook his head, “I’m afraid it would be impossible. After all the years I spent here, I discovered that the Underworld was changing bit by bit. Even in the past it would still be very hard. If I hadn’t arranged the transmission formation right after I arrived in the Underworld, then I might have completely lost contact with the Cultivation Realm. The Yin Wind Ghost Emperor should be aware of these changes as well since it looks like he could no longer send energy to his incarnation. After seeing his incarnation restricting itself inside the Temple, I knew that there must be a problem.”

Zhao Hai began to relax. To be honest, the things that Tiande spoke about gave Zhao Hai a scare. He looked up to the people in the Cultivation Realm, eager to see them. But after hearing Tiande, he knew that the Cultivation Realm was much more dangerous than he expected. The capabilities of the Cultivators seem to be much more ruthless than he thought.

Regarding the changes that Tiande said, Zhao Hai could affirm that it was because of the Giant Heart. All this time, the Giant Heart had been working hard to defend itself. Because of this, the Underworld went through changes year after year. It seems like the results were remarkable, even Tiande was able to sense that the Underworld was different from before.

However, Zhao Hai was still curious, so he asked Tiande, “How are you able to sense that the Underworld was different?”

Tiande replied, “Replying to the Young Master. As time went by, I began to feel that the Cultivation Realm’s control over me had decreased. Moreover, aside from the transmission formation, they lost all their means to give me commands. When I first came to the Underworld, they were still able to use their Divine Sense to control me. But now it has become impossible.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he said, “I’ve already destroyed that transmission formation. The link you have to the Cultivation Realm has also been erased. You don’t need to worry about it anymore.”

Tiande gave Zhao Hai a bow, “Tiande thanks the Young Master. If not for the Young Master, then I might not be able to see this day.”

Zhao Hai waved his hand as he inquired once more, “Didn’t you say that your memories had been preserved? So do you still remember the cultivation methods of your sect?”

Tiande immediately replied, “Young Master can rest assured, I remember them all.”

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but feel happy, “Good, then you should stay with Cai’er and recall every cultivation method you have. Write down what you know about the Cultivation Realm as well.”

Tiande complied before following Cai’er. Zhao Hai stood up and walked out of his room. Before long, he arrived in the living room. Laura and the others were still playing. They had nothing else to do, so they decided to play with the Undead.

The Undead were under Lizzy and Megan’s control. If they wanted the Undead to attack, then they would attack; and if they wanted them to defend, then the Undead would defend. Because of this, they had a jolly time controlling the Undead army.

The reason why they weren’t catching Undead like before was because the Space’ Undead had already reached an astonishing 50 billion. It was already a lot, there was no need to be frantic in taking in more.

Zhao Hai looked at the monitor and saw that here weren’t a lot of Neutral Alliance Undead left. He smiled before saying, “Alright, you can stop playing around, clean them all up.”

When Laura and the others heard this, they turned their heads. They were too immersed in their game that they failed to notice that Zhao Hai had come back. Now that Zhao Hai suddenly spoke, they couldn’t help but be surprised.

Laura hastily stood up and said, “Brother Hai, you’re back? When did you return?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “I returned a while ago. But after seeing you having fun, I decided not to disturb you. I just finished talking with Tiande, I didn’t expect that you would still be playing. Alright, it’s time to tidy up. You can play later, the Underworld already belongs to us.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Laura and the others looked at each other and cheered. They had waited for this day for a long time, now they finally achieved their goal.

The Underworld was different compared to the other places. Places like the Ark Continent could have their laws destroyed. Once its laws were destroyed, then it would become like an unguarded city. On the other hand, the Underworld had a special environment that didn’t allow beings that weren’t Undead. At the same time, the Giant Heart was here, changing the plane bit by bit. There was no arguing that the Underworld was the best place to be their base.

Naturally, nobody else would want to make the Underworld their base, even the people from the Cultivation Realm. If someone stays in the Underworld for too long, they would eventually succumb to the plane’s death energy. If they don’t turn into Undead immediately, then they would turn into a deranged demon before dying.

And in addition to the Dark Mist, it would also be impossible for them to cultivate here. Therefore, this was a plane that nobody really wanted to be in.

The reason the Yin Wind Ghost Emperor came to the Underworld was because he wanted to gather subordinates while also gaining faith power.

However, after the transformations caused by the Giant heart, the Yin Wind Ghost Emperor could no longer gather subordinates, he could only collect faith power.

And now that the Dark Temple has been ruined, faith power could no longer be collected. Also, it would now be impossible for the Ghost Emperor to go back to the Underworld. It can be said that the Underworld was now in Zhao Hai’s hands.

While it was useless and harmful to others, this didn’t matter to Zhao Hai. He has the Space, therefore he can take the Underworld as his back garden. Not only could it provide Zhao Hai with ores, special plants, and endless subordinates, it could also provide faith power in the future. These were all things that the people from the Cultivation Realm wanted. And now it was in Zhao Hai’s hands.

Laura and the others were also clear about the Underworld’s importance. Because of this, they were happy after hearing the news.

Zhao Hai looked at their expressions and smiled, “Alright, now go finish everything up.” Lizzy and Megan nodded before commanding the army to end the fight.

Not too long after that, the Neutral Alliance fell.

After the Undead were cleaned up, Zhao Hai waved his hand and called Addison in. Addison had a look of joy as he faced Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai looked at Addison’s expression and smiled, “Addison, now that the Underworld is ours, I want to hear your opinion. You have two choices. First choice is to enter the Hell Space. You should be very clear that practicing in the Hell Space is much more effective than here in the Underworld. Your other choice is staying in the Underworld, helping me manage the place, becoming the Lord of the Underworld. Besides me, all the other Undead would listen to you. This isn’t relaxed work and it might affect your cultivation.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Addison couldn’t help but chuckle. Then he turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Young Master, you can forget about the first option. I will stay here in the Underworld to manage it. If I’m here, then I would bring better benefits to you. Although it might seem like I chose this because of your preferences, but I am really willing to manage the Underworld. Even if I spend my entire life doing so, I would still be willing. This is because the Young Master has given us Undead an identity, treating us as our own race. For Young Master’s sake, I will do everything.”

Zhao Hai looked at Addison, he smiled faintly and said, “Alright, Addison, I understand your decision. You can stay here in the Underworld. But you can rest assured, after I ascend to the Cultivation Realm, I will certainly seek cultivation methods for you to use. When the time comes, you can practice here in the Underworld. If you manage to get stronger, I can pick you up at any time.”

Addison’s eyes shone. He stood up and gave Zhao Hai a bow, “Thank you, Young Master. Rest assured, I will properly manage the Underworld.”

Zhao Hai laughed. He patted Addison’s shoulder and said, “Alright, you go settle things in the Underworld. After all, this is now your domain.”

Chapter 1066: The Space’s New Discipline: Magic Branding

Zhao Hai calmly stood on his blood lotus. In front of him was a rich and solid continent. Growing on the land were various strange grasses, shining amidst the rays of the sun.

But if one carefully looked into the land, one would see remnants of destroyed buildings beneath the lush vegetation.

This continent was none other than one of the Divine Realm’s 13 continents, the Central Continent. It was the land Zhao Hai attacked in the past.

The Central Continent was left unmanaged for a long time. After destroying the continent, Zhao Hai left zero people here. Even if the Foreign Races ruled the entire Divine Realm, they would still find it hard to send people here. And since the Foreign Races were at war with the O’Neal family, it was even more pointless for them to send people to this continent.

Zhao Hai came to the Divine Realm because he wanted to see the situation here. It has been two years since he had unified the Underworld. In those two years, the development of the Space went as usual. And since he had scoured almost all of the lands he went to, the Space didn’t level up, it was still level 120.

The Space’s development was very good. There were even Experts that emerged from the Ark Continent and the Goblins. These were out of Zhao Hai’s expectations. This was especially true for the Goblins. The physique of the Goblins was unsuitable for practice. But despite this, the Goblins found their own means to cultivate. And this method gave Zhao Hai a great surprise.

The Goblins knew about their strengths as well as their weaknesses. Their near extermination had dug deep into their minds. Because of this, there were a lot of Goblins that went all out both in researching magic formations and in cultivation.

However, one has to know that the Goblin race’s innate skill in cultivation wasn’t much. Although they could exchange for manuals from the churches that Zhao Hai built, their initial progress was very slow.

Zhao Hai wanted to urge the Goblins to stop cultivating and instead focus on researching magic formations. However, he decided to give up on this idea. He wouldn’t go in the way of the Goblin race’s learning. So he stationed a few more instructors into the Goblin Academy. These instructors were members from the other races that could teach the Goblins about martial arts and magic.

Zhao Hai didn’t expect too much from this arrangement, he was clearly aware of the Goblin race’s capabilities. He was like a giant patiently teaching a dwarf how to play basketball, despite knowing that the dwarf would never be good at it.

However, Zhao Hai didn’t expect that among the instructors that were sent, one of them would be a Demon that dealt with potions. This instructor cooperated with the Goblins and made a new method that Zhao Hai had never heard of.

This method combines potion-making and magic formations. The Demons and the Goblins gave this method a name, Magic Branding.

This so-called magic branding method was actually very simple. Plants would be refined into special potions, then using a needle, the potion would be branded on the body of a Goblin. This branding couldn’t just be done freely. One had to find the body’s meridians before inscribing a magic formation for it to take effect. And in the end, this effect was extraordinary.

As long as a Goblin was branded in their meridians, then no matter martial arts or magic, their practice speed would be doubled while the effort needed was halved. They became no worse than the other races. It was an exceptionally good invention.

Naturally, after he came to know about this, Zhao Hai didn’t become stingy. He immediately rewarded that Demon instructor as well as the Goblins. Moreover, he complied their findings into books and distributed them to the other Academies. This way, not only would they gain rewards, their fame would also increase.

Of course, magical branding wasn’t so easily studied. First, one would need expertise when it comes to potions. One would also need large amounts of high-grade medicinal ingredients. Second, one would have to know magic formations. Mistakes during branding should also be avoided otherwise everything would turn to waste. Finally, one should also have knowledge about the body’s meridians. These distinct methods weren’t gained from the Ark Continent nor the Divine Realm. These were derived from the Cultivation Realm’s methods. All these things put together made it possible for magic branding to exist.

Zhao Hai was very appreciative about this creation. This magical branding gave him a realization. Currently, the magical brands used ordinary magic formations. If the formations used were from the Cultivation Realm, then what would its effect? Its might should be even greater.

Just like the Space, the Underworld was developing normally. And just like Tiande said, because of the Giant Heart, the plane was slowly transforming. At this point, the Cultivation Realm’s experts shouldn’t be able to find its coordinates.

In the past, the Giant Heart didn’t dare to transform the plane too quickly. First because it was afraid of being found out. And second, because it didn’t have much strength.

But after so many years of progress, things were now different. Now, the Cultivation Realm’s influence had been cut off, and the strength of the Giant Heart has increased. Because of this, the transformation of the Underworld increased. In just two years, the Cultivation Realm should have already lost track of the Underworld; which was absolutely good news for Zhao Hai.

As long as the Cultivation Realm couldn’t find the Underworld, then the Underworld was safe. With one less worry, Zhao Hai’s heart began to lighten up.

Unlike the Underworld and the Space, the Divine Realm wasn’t doing too well. Ever since the Dwarves had moved out, the Beastmen and the Elves continued their war with the O’Neal family. Although the war turned into small skirmishes later on, the battles didn’t stop all these years.

Moreover, the Foreign Races had underestimated the O’Neal family. The magic armors were not to be trifled with. Their fighting strength was formidable and they were all extremely quick. As long as there was a war tank supplying them with energy, their fighting strength wouldn’t fall. Because of this, the Foreign Races had been at a disadvantage during the small encounters.

Zhao Hai cared about the war in the Divine Realm. After all, he was the one who started it. He wanted to see who would win between the two sides.

But after two years of observation, Zhao Hai finally couldn’t wait. Although the two sides remained fighting, the scale of the battles were very small. The overall status of the war was left unchanged, there wasn’t too much development.

Zhao Hai wasn’t satisfied with this result. Although Zhao Hai had some misgivings against the Beastmen and the Elves, if they asked for a chance to enter the Space, he would still give it. In Zhao Hai’s mind , when the O’Neal family greatly injures the Beastmen and the Elves, there would be a good chance for the two races to enter the Space.

But now, the Foreign Races and the O’Neal Family seem to be in a stalemate. In this case, the Beastmen and the Elves wouldn’t enter the Space.

Just like the Divine Realm’s stagnant situation, there was also not much development in the Atlanta Plane. If there was, then it would be Zhao Hai’s factory. After two years, the factory had turned into a large-scale factory, capturing business from established forces.

This was a very good outcome. One must know that these established forces had Noble backgrounds. Being able to do business with them wasn’t an easy matter.

And with this, Zhao Hai was able to see Bluewell’s capabilities. Bluewell had great talent in management. In just a short two years, he was able to expand the factory’s operation to this degree. It was truly astonishing.

Naturally, the one with the greatest harvest these two years was Zhao Hai. Because of his Dao Lotus, Gold Core, Spirit Incarnation, and the Yin Yang Myriad Stellar Transformation art, he was still making fast progress despite doing nothing. At this point, Zhao Hai’s strength had reached the peak of the art’s first layer. He was on the cusp of breaking through.

Zhao Hai started to feel the laws of the Divine Realm repelling him once more. Zhao Hai knew that he was close to ascending.

It needed to be said that Zhao Hai wasn’t being repelled in the Underworld. After all, his heart was once one with the Underworld’s Giant Heart. In this case, it was impossible to repel him. However, Zhao Hai knew that he could not stay in the Underworld for a long time otherwise he might induce some changes to the plane’s laws. His continued presence in the Underworld might form a connection with the Cultivation Realm. If this happens, then his back garden would once again be in danger.

Zhao Hai wasn’t generous enough to share his family’s properties to others. Because of this, Zhao Hai left the Underworld despite not being repelled.

At this point, Zhao Hai had a certain understanding of the laws of the Heavens and the Earth. Normally, the laws were unchangeable. In a plane, a mountain, a rock, a sea, or a small blade of grass might induce some changes, but this change was very minimal. There wouldn’t be much of an impact.

However, when a super strong expert appears, then the laws of the plane would be greatly affected.

Any plane had its own unique laws. Even if there was something that can control a plane’s laws, the laws would still stick to its core.

Chapter 1067: Strange Laws of the Atlanta Plane

People from the Cultivation Realm couldn’t truly control a plane. Rather they had something that was either related to a plane or something that can communicate with it. This way, they can send a trace of their spirit into the plane and collect faith power.

But not all Cultivators need to send their own incarnation in order to collect faith power. Some of them could have the residents of that plane worship them like a god. In turn, this would produce faith power. The only thing they needed to do was to find means to collect it.

This was a very easy matter. Generally, Cultivators who reach a small plane could easily become a god-like existence due to their overwhelming strength. Even if they only send an incarnation, they could still dominate the plane.

Now that the Underworld has been transformed, even the Yin Wind Ghost Emperor couldn’t find the plane. The Underworld has been changed by the Giant Heart from being a stationary plane to a moving one. Because of this, the Underworld’s original coordinates could no longer be used. Things that could link to the Underworld had been rendered useless as well.

Also, Zhao Hai discovered that the spatial rift connecting the Underworld and the Ark Continent was being patched up by the Giant Heart. He believed that before long, the spatial rift would completely vanish.

The reason for all of this was because the Giant Heart wanted to protect itself. Although the spatial rift to the Ark Continent benefits the Underworld, it could also be used as a passage to enter the plane. How could the Giant Heart allow such a thing? Therefore, it began to fix the rift little by little.

Zhao Hai didn’t oppose this decision. Conversely, he agreed to the Giant Heart’s action. The Underworld was now his domain, it would be good if nobody else enters it.

And no matter what changes happen to the Underworld, it wouldn’t affect Zhao Hai. His heart has been inherited from the Giant Heart. And there was also a map of the Underworld in the Space. It was impossible for Zhao Hai to lose contact with the Underworld.

But Zhao Hai wasn’t in the mood to take care of the Underworld right now. With Addison managing the plane, he didn’t need to worry. And although the Giant Heart couldn’t actively attack, Zhao Hai knew that as long as it was willing, it could use the entire Underworld’s laws. It can be said that the core of the Underworld’s laws was the Giant Heart. Nothing else had a stronger control over the Underworld.

The reason why the Giant Heart accepted Zhao Hai was because he wasn’t subjected to the Underworld’s laws. It can be said that Zhao Hai was beyond the five elements and even the planes. And with Zhao Hai’s strength, there was no reason for the Giant Heart to drive him away.

At this point, Zhao Hai’s most important task was to plan his ascension. Naturally, the Underworld wasn’t a good choice. Not to say about the possibility of ascending now that the Underworld has been cut off from the Cultivation Realm, if he could ascend, then the Underworld would once again be connected to the Cultivation Realm. With this new connection, both the Yin Wind Ghost Emperor and the Myriad Treasures Pavilion would naturally want to grab this fat piece of meat back.

As for the Ark Continent, Divine Realm, and the Demon Realm, these three planes belong to the same group of planes. Ascending here was equivalent to sending Zhao Hai to Lu Wei’s mouth. Zhao Hai naturally wouldn’t want this.

Although Zhao Hai had thrown filthy water over to Lu Wei, what can two years do? It might seem like a long time for Zhao Hai, but in the Cultivation realm, two years happen in a blink of an eye. Zhao Hai didn’t believe that Lu Wei would be killed by the Yin Wind Ghost Emperor and the Myriad Treasures Pavilion in just two years. He wasn’t even sure if Lu Wei would be found in just two years, much less killed.

Therefore, the Divine Realm, Ark Continent, and the Demon Realm were excluded from the selection. In the end, the last choice for Zhao Hai was the Atlanta Plane.

Although the Atlanta Plane had been interlinked with the Ark Continent, Zhao Hai can almost affirm that the Atlanta Plane was the same as the Underworld, besides the sentient Giant heart. The Giant Heart was aware of its being, so it did its best to close the connection. As for the Atlanta Plane, it seems like this wasn’t the case.

Zhao Hai also discovered that whether it was the Divine Realm, the Ark Continent, or the Atlanta Plane, even if their laws changed, these changes were methodical, like a computer program. It would change according to the rules, there was little to no deviation.

The Giant Heart was different. Being the core of the Underworld’s laws, it wasn’t like a computer, it had sentience. In other words, it was close to being human, making the Underworld different than the other planes.

Zhao Hai also discovered something strange with the Atlanta Plane’s laws. Take the Magic Armor Continent as an example. If someone from the continent wanted to ascend, then they would have to use a magic armor in order to do so. Other methods were useless.

At the same time, the repulsion force of the Atlanta Plane was different. In the other planes, Zhao Hai felt their repulsion as though it was an angry mob, punching and kicking him all over. It was as though they were adamant to kick him out.

But in the Atlanta Plane, the feeling was not the same. The repulsion here made one feel as though they had entered an uncomfortable place, making them leave as soon as possible. The contrast between the two repulsions could be categorized as passive and active. Two different concepts. Just like the difference between being thrown into prison and wanting to go to prison. The outcome was the same but the process was different.

This was what Zhao Hai was stressed about. If he was in the Divine Realm, he would know when he would be ascending. As long as his strength has accumulated to a certain degree, then the plane would immediately force him to ascend.

As for the Atlanta Plane, as soon as he entered, he would immediately feel annoyed. He would always have this nagging feeling that he didn’t want to be here. But even so, the plane still didn’t exert any strength to force him out. This made Zhao Hai extremely puzzled.

Because of this, Zhao Hai was left not knowing what to do. This was the reason why he was stressed out. If it was before, then he can wait a while and look at the result. But now it can no longer be done. Zhao Hai calculated that he only had a couple of months left before his energy reaches the threshold. When this time comes, he would need to ascend. In other words, he only had a few months left to Understand the Atlanta Plane’s laws.

Several months wasn’t short, but it wasn’t long either. Moreover, with Zhao Hai wanting to figure out the plane’s laws, these months would even feel shorter.

Figuring out the laws was something that even those in the Cultivation Realm couldn’t understand. Finishing his goal within only a few months would be very difficult for Zhao Hai.

Not knowing what to do and being in a dilemma, Zhao Hai decided to take a walk. Unconsciously he arrived in the Central Continent.

The Central Continent was left with zero management, causing it to become a paradise for magic beasts. One could see various beasts wandering around the once prestigious Connecting Heaven Palace.

Upon seeing this, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but sigh. Although all of this was caused by him, he still couldn’t help but lament.

Humanity seems to be born with two conflicting abilities, creation and destruction. On one hand, Humans can make brilliant civilizations. And on the other, one can see Humans destroying similar civilizations. They were like the treacherous heavens. With the constant creation and destruction, one would wonder how the Humans would develop in the end.

Without knowing, Zhao Hai’s mind wandered to his cultivation method, the Yin Yang Myriad Stellar Transformations art. From the moment he obtained this manual, every time he practiced, Zhao Hai always felt that something was missing.

Zhao Hai was completely lost about this in the past. But after seeing the stretch of ruins, Zhao Hai’s eyes were suddenly opened. During his cultivation sessions, he failed to look at the universe, the stars, and the yin-yang pair.

These things were the major components of the Yin Yang Myriad Transformations Art. In the past, Zhao Hai only practiced the art according to what was depicted inside. Although the art’s effects were manifolds more than ordinary cultivation methods, Zhao Hai wasn’t able to grasp the true meaning of the cultivation method. One could say that Zhao Hai’s knowledge of the art was just superficial.

Zhao Hai stood in place as though he was frozen. He was completely immersed in this new revelation, completely isolating himself from the outside world. One must know that doing this was extremely dangerous. Now that the Central Continent was teeming with magic beasts, one could attack Zhao Hai at any time.

However, something unusually strange happened. Even if they were beside the unmoving Zhao Hai, the beasts seem to see nor sense nothing. It was peculiar.

Chapter 1068: Role-play

Meanwhile, Laura and the others were quite worried inside the Space. Zhao Hai just stood motionless in a completely wrong place. And there was also no indication that he would do it, which was very abnormal.

Cai’er was aware about Zhao Hai’s situation, but she wasn’t anxious. She knew that Zhao Hai wasn’t in any real danger, he was just comprehending something.

After looking at the worry on Laura and the others’ faces, Cai’er immediately said, “There’s no need to worry. The Young Master is just comprehending something, so there’s no real danger. And if we take the Young Master to the Space at this time, we would be cutting him off from his current mental state. This is more dangerous than just leaving him there.”

Upon hearing Cai’er, Laura and the others immediately gave out a sigh. But Lizzy looked at the screen before turning to Cai’er and saying, “Cai’er, have some Undead protect Brother Hai. There are a lot of magic beasts around him, he may be attacked.”

Cai’er just smiled as she replied, “Sister Lizzy, there’s no need to worry. If I guessed correctly, then the Young Master is currently comprehending his cultivation method. Young Master’s cultivation method is very unusual, and when he is cultivating, his body would merge with the surrounding environment. These magic beasts would just see the Young Master as though he is part of the scenery. If we send the Undead, then the magic beasts might attack them instead. If that happens, then we would be breaking the Young Master’s concentration.”

Lizzy quickly nodded. However, Megan seems to be angry as she said, “Does Brother Hai really need to scare us every time he comprehends something? Hmph. Elder Sisters, I guess we should teach Brother Hai a lesson when he comes back.”

When Laura heard Megan say this, she couldn’t help but tease her, “Alright, then let’s teach him a lesson. And the first to do that will be Sister Megan!”

Upon hearing Laura, Lizzy and the others immediately chuckled. Meanwhile, Megan’s face went completely red. She threw menacing look at Laura and said, “Sister Laura, you actually dared to ridicule me?” After she said that, she went on to throw herself towards Laura.

Laura squealed before running away. Lizzy and the others joined in on the fun before long, causing a mess in the villa. Zhao Hai was fully immersed in his comprehension, who knows when he would be done.

Currently, the ever changing universe and the stars kept flashing inside Zhao Hai’s mind, displaying the essence on yin-yang. The universe was made up of the yin and the yang. If there was yang in the world, then yin would surely be present.

At the same time, the yin and the yang components of the five elements comprised a myriad of things in the universe. It was both a simple and a very complicated process, but this process went according to the universal laws.

Similar to the depiction of the yin-yang fish, the yin has yang, and yang has yin. It was an endless cycle that permeated all things in the universe.

Zhao Hai didn’t know for how long he spent inside this profound state before he suddenly woke up. Upon turning sober, Zhao Hai discovered that his cultivation of the Yin-yang Myriad Stellar Transformations art had grown deeper. Moreover, he noticed that his command of his body had become much more smooth and natural.

Zhao Hai let out a long breath. To be frank, he was somewhat afraid of what just happened. If he kept with that state for a long time, then its possible for his strength to quickly reach the peak. If that happens, then Zhao Hai would have to prematurely ascend.

He looked all around him and saw that there were still a lot of magic beasts. However, it seems like these beasts weren’t afraid of him or maybe they simply didn’t think of him as an enemy. There were even some magic beasts who only gave Zhao Hai one glance before resuming to handle their own matters. There wasn’t even a point of hostility in their gazes.

Zhao Hai looked at these magic beasts and smiled. Then his figure vanished as he entered the Space. But as he entered the Space, Zhao Hai’s brows couldn’t help but wrinkle. He was still worried about his ascension.

He had decided on the Atlanta Plane, but the plane had very unusual laws. This caused Zhao Hai to feel his head ache.

While Zhao Hai was thinking, he entered the villa. But upon entering, he was immediately met with fierce expression coming from Laura and the others. Zhao Hai couldn’t help but feel puzzled at the sight.

He pretended to feel guilty as he asked, “My lovely wives, what did I do wrong?”

Laura and the others looked at Zhao Hai’s reaction and couldn’t help but smile. However, they still went according to what they planned. Megan stood up and said, “Big Brother Hai, you might not know, but you gave us a scare when you suddenly blanked out like that. So how would you like to be punished?”

Zhao Hai stared, then he immediately replied, “This. Right, that’s right. How do you want to punish me?”

Megan gave out a snort before saying, “Come with us.” Then she turned around and walked to the villa’s interior. Upon seeing where Megan was heading, Zhao Hai’s eyes couldn’t help but light up. Megan seems to be heading towards the villa’s basement, to where the hot spring was.

Laura and the others also pretended as though they were escorting a criminal. Zhao Hai couldn’t help but chuckle inside as he saw their conduct. He saw that Laura and the others just wanted him to relax, so he just cooperated.

………………………………………………………….

After several hours of this role-playing, Zhao Hai and the others relaxed on the hot spring. Laura looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, are you still worried about ascending?”

Zhao Hai sighed and said, “The Atlanta Plane’s laws are just too strange. I know that people who want to ascend would need to use the ascension magic armor or else they wouldn’t be able to succeed. But even if I was given an ascension magic armor, I still feel like it would be difficult for me to ascend. It was as though I don’t like to ascend there. I really don’t know why.”

Megan frowned as she asked, “What do we do? Big Brother Hai, will you really ascend in the Divine Realm? We don’t know where we’ll end up, but if we go straight into Lu Wei’s hands, then wouldn’t we be like sheep walking straight into a tiger’s mouth?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “If we ascend in the Divine Realm, then its possible that we would be chased by Lu Wei. Although preserving our lives wouldn’t be a problem, I still prefer to do it in the Atlanta Plane. It is much safer to ascend there.”

This time, it was Lizzy who frowned, “How about we have Bluewell gather news about ascension magic armors? We can try this out first. Elder Brother Hai, what do you think?”

Zhao Hai nodded, but he forced a smile as he said, “The issue with your idea is that we don’t have the time. After that period of comprehension, I calculated that with the rate of increase in my energy level, I only have two months before I would need to ascend. Otherwise, I would have to hide inside the Space. And I doubt Bluewell would get something in just two months.”

Megan made another suggestion, “Brother Hai, what about directly stealing the magic armor? We know that the strongest in the Magic Armor Continent is physically weaker than the God-ranks in the Divine Realm. With our current strength, it would be very easy to flatten the Magic Armor Continent.”

Zhao Hai smiled bitterly and said, “Forget it. If we really go and steal an ascension magic armor while killing a lot of people, then we might offend the Atlanta Plane’s controller. Then if we ascend, then we might be chased down. This is also the reason why I haven’t made any moves in the Atlanta Plane.”

Laura seems to have realize something, “So this is why Brother Hai has been polite to the Atlanta Plane’s residents. It seems like we can’t just snatch the magic armor or else we would be in trouble. But if this is the case, then I’m afraid ascending in the Atlanta Plane would be hard.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he said, “If there’s really no other way, then once I am going to ascend, I’ll try forcing my way in the Atlanta Plane. Let’s see how the plane’s laws handle me then.”

Meg, who hasn’t spoken all this time, opened her mouth and said, “Young Master, why don’t you head to the Warrior Continent or the Mage Continent?”

Zhao Hai replied, “It’s still the Atlanta Plane, what’s the difference?”

Meg gave a smile and said, “Young Master, the Atlanta Plane is divided into three continents. If the Magic Armor Continent uses an ascension magic armor to ascend, then shouldn’t the Warrior and Mage Continents have their own methods? Moreover, the Warrior Continent and the Mage continent doesn’t have a good relationship with the Magic Armor Continent. I’m almost certain that people from the two continents don’t use ascension magic armors to ascend. So if they don’t, what method do they use?”

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but stare as he heard Meg. To be honest, he completely forgot about this point. He thought that the Atlanta Plane’s laws would be uniform all throughout.

Now that Meg reminded him, Zhao Hai began to think it through. Right, the Atlanta Plane doesn’t only have the Magic Armor Continent, there’s also the Warrior and Mage Continents. These two continents use the same system as the Ark Continent and the Divine Realm, the martial and the magic system.

Moreover, ascension was considered to be the most noble goal that a practitioner could accomplish. If the people from the Warrior and Mage Continent couldn’t ascend while the people from the Magic Armor Continent could, then what was the point of studying martial arts and magic? If the two Continents could ascend, then they surely wouldn’t use ascension magic armors. If that was the case, then Zhao Hai’s issue might be solved.

Zhao Hai laughed as he rose from the hot spring and hugged Meg before flying in the air. Laura and the others couldn’t help but laugh. They knew very well that Zhao Hai was very glad at Meg’s reminder.

After some time, the group walked out of the Hot Spring. They headed to the living room before opening up a map of the Magic Armor Continent.

As he looked at the Magic Armor Continent, Zhao Hai’s tone fell, “Who would’ve expected that I would forget about the other two continents.”

Laura nodded and said, “Brother Hai, do you want to head there now?”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he turned to Cai’er and said, “Cai’er, show us the map of the entire Atlanta Plane. Let’s see which the two continents we should go first.”

Caie’r nodded before she opened a map on the monitor. This map wasn’t the same map that was made from the blood ghost staff’s explorations. Instead, it was just a common map bought from the Magic Armor Continent. After scanning the map, it was then saved inside the Space. Because of this, the map wasn’t 3D like the ones before. It can only be read as thought it was a normal map.

After seeing this map, Zhao Hai didn’t immediately set out to see the two continents. Instead, he looked at the basic information about the locations and topography inside the two continents. This way, he would have a rough idea on where to visit.

Zhao Hai carefully scanned through the map. From the map, he could clearly see the distribution between the three continents. The three continents formed a triangle on the map. The other two continents wasn’t much smaller than the Magic Armor Continent. Northeast to the Magic Armor Continent was the Warrior Continent, and on the southeast side was the Mage Continent. The distance between the three wasn’t that much. There were also small islands dotted around the three landmasses.

Zhao Hai tried to imagine what it would look like if these three continents were combined. From the legends, it seems like these three continents were once one huge supercontinent.

Looking at the three continents, Zhao Hai said, “We’ll go to the Warrior Continent first to take a look. If it had the same laws as the Divine Realm, then we wouldn’t need to worry anymore.”

Laura nodded and said, “Two months should be enough for us to put the Warrior and Mage Continent on the Space’s map. As long as their laws are suitable for ascension, then Brother Hai can just go to either continent in order to ascend.

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “We should also find a good place to ascend. I reckon the disturbance caused by the ascension wouldn’t be small. It would be great if we can find a desolate area. But let’s put that aside for later. We still don’t know if the laws of the two continents would be favorable to us. If it was, then it wouldn’t be too late to find an appropriate place.”

Chapter 1069: Maximum Benefit to Ascending

A blood red needle was flying through the sky. The needle was very fast as it flew through the air. It was almost unnoticeable, leaving only a very thin line along its path. Most people might even just think that it was an illusion.

Of course, at this point, nobody would be able to see this needle since it was flying above an ocean. The seas of the Atlanta Plane were very dangerous. Besides appropriate times, people going across these areas would be killed.

The residents of the Atlanta Plane were very peculiar. Although the Magic Armor Continent, Warrior Continent, and Mage Continent were hostile to one another, their people still trade with each other. But since the three continents were enemies, trading was still quite difficult.

In the beginning, there were some big companies that traded between the three continents. These traders would bring numerous guards in order to defend against the assault coming from the enemies.

But before long, people from the three continents decided that trading this way brought more peril than benefits. The number of merchants who did business with the three continents decreased, causing a lack of commodities between the three landmasses.

Naturally, this lack of commodity didn’t mean that the people would find it hard to live. Instead, this was a shortage of rare materials in each continent. In turn, this made it difficult for them to progress in their civilization.

After they discovered this situation, the three continents reached an agreement. Each year, they would allocate a couple of months specifically for trade. In these months, people from the three continents could freely exchange goods without the fear of being attacked. Anyone who dared attack these merchants would receive collective retaliation from the three continents.

But besides these months of peace, the seas would become a battlefield the rest of the months. People from the Atlanta Plane treat the seas as a smelting trial. They would either go search for ores or try to temper their cultivation.

Hidden in this body of water were formidable Warriors and Mages. Naturally, on the side of the Magic Armor Continent, there were also powerful magic armor pilots present. These people were doing their best to kill the people on the other two continents.

They kill people not just for the sake of slaughter. These people do this mainly because they would receive bounties every time they kill an enemy. Once they return to their clans, they would be handsomely rewarded. Because of this, there were countless amounts of people who would come to this region every year.

Because of this, Zhao Hai wasn’t too anxious to go outside. He knew that the moment he came out, he would be attacked immediately. Therefore, he just sent the blood needle instead of himself.

Besides this blood needle, Zhao Hai also released other blood needles. These needles were divided into two groups, one heading to the Warrior Continent while the others would head to the Mage Continent. Zhao Hai wanted to see the situation with the two continents as soon as possible.

Zhao Hai’s action produced excellent results. At this moment, Zhao Hai had already mapped some areas, showing hidden Warriors, Mages, and Magic Armors. Naturally, they were being monitored by the Space.

This action also went according to Zhao Hai’s current situation. Every minute he stays inside the Space, his cultivation would be accelerated. If he kept being inside, then he would ascend one month later. And even if he didn’t practice, his body would be full in less than two months. Because of this, Zhao Hai had no other choice but to hurry.

It didn’t take more than five days before the blood needles entered the Warrior and Mage Continents. The two continents have distinct architectural and fashion styles. In the Warrior Continent, one would be able to see people wearing warrior clothing everywhere. There would also be weapons hung on the backs of these people at all times. Even some commoner families would have weapon frames somewhere in their houses, holding a weapon of sorts. At the same time, despite being commoners, each household still had a set of dumbbells, sandbags, and exercise materials in their homes. In the Warrior Continent, these things were deemed to be essential to their lifestyles. Even the poverty stricken folks weren’t exempted from this custom.

As for the Mage Continent, in almost every city, one would be able to see a magic tower. These magic towers were places where the mages live.

Actually, in both the Ark Continent and the Divine Realm, magic towers were things from ancient times. These things had long since been out of fashion. Of all the places Zhao Hai had been to, besides the Mage Continent, only the Underworld had magic towers.

The towers that protect each city in the Underworld, where high-ranked Undead live in, were actually magic towers. In the Ark Continent, magic towers didn’t exist anymore. And even if there were, they were mostly used as a decoration or as a historical ruin.

However, these seemingly ancient magic towers were actually present in almost all cities in the Mage Continent. And most importantly, through the Space, Zhao Hai was able to see that around these magic towers were the liveliest places in the city.

What made Zhao Hai even more surprised was the fact that, in the Mage Continent, two to three people out of ten were wearing mage’s robes. The proportion of mages to common people was quite high.

In the Ark Continent, if a Mage could emerge every thousand people, then that was already seen as a good ratio. But here, in ten people, two or three Mages could be seen. It would be very hard for people to accept this statistic.

This wouldn’t be strange if it came to Warriors. After all, most people could practice martial arts. Even if one didn’t practice too deeply, they could still become a common Warrior. But as for Mages, one needed innate skill to dabble in the elements. But even if this was the case, the Mage Continent seem to have a lot more talents.

Even Zhao Hai, with his talents and capabilities, couldn’t help but be speechless when he saw this. In the end, he could only let out a helpless sigh.

If he had the time, he would certainly do a thorough investigation on these two Continents. He might even go and buy some land in these two continents to play around from time to time.

But it was a pity that Zhao Hai was about to ascend, he didn’t have time to play around in these two continents. And as long as he ascends, he would no longer have this opportunity.

Although the needles had arrived at the two continents, Zhao Hai didn’t immediately exit the Space. Instead, he would wait until the terrain of the continents were fully mapped inside the Space. This took five days to be finished. Unknowingly, Zhao Hai had already spent ten days inside the Space. If he continued to stay inside the Space for a month, then he would immediately ascend.

After finally mapping the two continents, Zhao Hai let out a long breath as he stood up. It was already night, but he still wanted to take a look.

Laura saw Zhao Hai stand and immediately said, “Brother Hai, it’s already dark. How about you go outside tomorrow?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “I’ll just go out and feel the laws. Otherwise, I wouldn’t be able to sleep.”

When she heard Zhao Hai, Laura knew that she couldn’t stop him, so she said, “Alright, but Brother Hai needs to be careful. If the laws are just like in the Magic Armor Continent, then you need to come back. We’ll just snatch an ascension magic armor so that you can ascend.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Rest assured, I will be careful.” After he said that, his clothes changed into warrior clothing and his staff shifted into a greatsword.

After seeing Zhao Hai’s change in attire, Laura and the other knew that Zhao Hai was planning to visit the Warrior Continent. In the Warrior Continent, people with Zhao Hai’s attire could be seen everywhere, nobody would suspect him of anything. Additionally, with Zhao Hai’s strength, nobody in the Warrior Continent would be able to defeat him. The only thing that can threaten him were the laws.

Zhao Hai gave Laura and the others a glance before he smiled and vanished. The next moment, he was already in the Warrior Continent. Upon appearing, Zhao Hai immediately felt the laws pressuring him, it was even stronger than the pressure he felt in the Divine Realm.

But even if this was the case, Zhao Hai was still ecstatic. This was because the laws in this continent was different than the Magic Armor Continent. In the Magic Armor Continent, the laws made Zhao Hai feel sick. But here, the laws were pressuring him, the same as the pressure back in the Divine Realm. In other words, Zhao Hai can choose to ascend here.

Zhao Hai carried his greatsword and arrived at a tavern in the city. He listened to the Warriors boasting about their accomplishments. Although these were just mere boasting, Zhao Hai could still find obtain useful information.

However, Zhao Hai only stayed at the city for one hour before he returned to the Space. After finding out that he can ascend in the Warrior Continent, Zhao Hai decided to take a look at the Mage Continent. If he could ascend in the Mage Continent, then he would have another choice.

Zhao Hai turned into a Mage before teleporting to the Mage Continent. Just like the Warrior Continent, Zhao Hai was able to ascend here. With this matter taken care of, Zhao Hai began to relax. With the Mage and Warrior Continent present, he didn’t need to worry about ascension anymore.

However, he was left with deciding on where to ascend. He needed to understand the two continents before making a decision.

Although Zhao Hai didn’t know where he’ll end up upon ascending, he still needed to consider where he would ascend. He would analyze their laws and find out where he would benefit the most from ascending.

Chapter 1070: Sweeping the Central Bookstore

Shangwu City was a fairly famous city in the Warrior Continent. The city was built according to ancient architecture. It had a 300 feet high city wall that was ten feet thick. Moreover, the walls weren’t constructed using ordinary materials. It was being reinforced with the unique black iron ore of the Warrior Continent.

This black iron ore was a common ore in the Warrior Continent. Black iron can be extracted from this ore. However, black iron wasn’t as popular in the Warrior Continent as the other metals. This was because it only had one redeeming quality, it was very heavy!

Black iron refined from black iron ore was ten times heavier compared to ordinary iron. But despite this, black iron wasn’t stronger than ordinary iron. It can be said that it was a weak metal. In the Warrior Continent, black iron was only used to add weight to a weapon.

However, the qualities of black iron ore and black iron were different. Black iron ore can be said to be one of the hardest materials in the continent. When not refined into black iron, the hardness of the ore was no less than steel and iron. It was only after it was refined into black iron did the hardness change. It was one of the mysteries in the Warrior Continent.

This black iron ore was the best material to be made into a city’s wall. There were even weapons that had black iron ore added to them.

At this time, a young man carrying a red greatsword on his back was seen heading towards the city. The man looked very ordinary. His clothes were also the most common warrior clothing, his greatsword was the only unique thing about him.

Naturally, this person was Zhao Hai. The city’s guard only looked at Zhao Hai and didn’t make any action. In the Warrior Continent, it was very common to bring your weapon along. Here, it would be very strange if you didn’t have a weapon on you.

Zhao Hai looked at Shangwu City’s walls and his eyes couldn’t help but sparkle The Space didn’t have this kind of ore, he needs to get one for the Space. This was what Zhao Hai was thinking about as he entered the city.

Upon entering, Zhao Hai looked for a restaurant first and ordered several small dishes. He poured himself some wine and drank alone, nobody paid any attention to him. However, Zhao Hai’s ears were listening to the conversations around him.

The reason Zhao Hai entered Shangwu city was to acquire information. He also needed to collect some of the continent’s martial arts manuals.

Upon listening to the drivel coming from the surrounding Warriors, Zhao Hai knew that staying here any longer was useless. However, he was able to get some tidbits here and there. For example, manuals were common in the continent. Additionally, there were bookstores in each city. One could see basic training manuals from these bookstores. As for the more profound methods, one needed to acquire them from dojos or from some powerful families.

These powerful families and dojos were the most important groups in the Warrior Continent. In the continent, there weren’t such things as kingdoms. Each city were either managed by a powerful family or a dojo. The army defending the cities were subjects of these two groups.

As the name suggests, powerful families were great clans in the Warrior Continent. These great clans had their own unique martial skills. These unique skills shouldn’t be underestimated. It was said that each of these unique skills were very formidable.

As for the dojos, they were institutes for practicing martial arts. They were just like schools where Warriors learn martial arts. In each city, it didn’t matter if they were commoners or members of influential clans, all of them would study inside a dojo. Because of this, dojos had become rooted into the society.

Getting to know about these information was already quite good, so Zhao Hai paid the restaurant before leaving and heading towards a bookstore. There were a lot of bookstores in the city. However, the bookstore with the most complete collection of martial arts related books was the Central Bookstore. Naturally, Zhao Hai didn’t delay and headed towards this bookstore.

Shangwu City’s central bookstore was very popular. It was the highest building in the city. The building was divided into ten floors. The first five floors was where one could buy and sell basic martial arts manuals.

As for the sixth-eighth floor, this was where Warriors can acquire the rarer manuals. One could also sell unique manuals in these floors. As long as the bookstore’s attendants find the book good, then they would give a very good price for it.

And as for the ninth and tenth level, this was where people could only borrow books. However, not anyone could borrow books here, and not anyone could go up these floors. There were barriers guarding these floors. One needed to break these barriers if they wanted to enter.

Zhao Hai arrived at the central bookstore. Upon seeing the huge structure, he couldn’t help but feel nostalgic. This place was truly huge, they wouldn’t lose to some large-scale malls back on Earth.

Zhao Hai calmed himself down before entering the bookstore. When he went in, he couldn’t help but gawk. The first floor of this bookstore was full of ten meter tall shelves. There were rows upon rows of bookshelves. These shelves went from floor to ceiling, making one feel that they were propping the entire floor up.

Up and down these shelves were warriors choosing or reading books. The place looked extremely busy.

After sweeping a glance at this floor, Zhao Hai didn’t stop and continued going upstairs. He continued up until the eight floor without any problems. Naturally, he was met with the barrier to the ninth floor. However, how could this barrier stop Zhao Hai? He was able to swiftly enter the ninth floor.

There weren’t a lot of people on the ninth floor. Moreover, this floor was different. There weren’t as many bookshelves here compared to the other floors. In between bookshelves, there would be areas to rest and read.

Zhao Hai explored the ninth floor. He also had Cai’er control a blood needle to fly from shelf to shelf, recording the name of the books. When Zhao Hai got the book he wanted to read, he proceeded to the resting area to read.

The books that Zhao Hai wanted to read were introductions to high-level martial arts. Besides these, there were also records of miscellaneous stuff about the Warrior Continent. Such books were rarely seen in the Warrior Continent.

The reason Zhao Hai chose to read these high-level manuals was because he wanted to understand the martial skills of the continent. As for the records of miscellaneous events, he wanted to see if there were any information about someone ascending.

Zhao Hai wasn’t only reading, he was also releasing blood needles in order to scan all the books inside. Cai’er would then sort them out and divided them into categories. After all, the Warrior continent was a holy place for Warriors. Zhao Hai wanted to see to what degree their martial arts had reached.

After staying for a while on the ninth floor and waiting for the needles to finish their scan, Zhao Hai proceeded to enter the tenth floor.

He needed to head to the tenth floor personally. These two floors had barriers that would definitely detect the blood needles. If he had the needles fly to the tenth floor themselves, then it might produce an unwanted result.

Zhao Hai only stayed at the tenth floor for a short time. After scanning each book, he proceeded to leave the bookstore. Shangwu City was a huge city, there were a lot of people who entered here every year. Because of this, nobody would pay special attention to Zhao Hai. And even if the powerful families take note of him, by the time they receive information, Zhao Hai would already be inside the Space.

In the central bookstores of every city, local families would have informants planted inside. As long as someone had the qualifications to enter the ninth and tenth floor, these informants would immediately send word back to their families. One had to know that people who pass the barriers to the ninth and tenth floor were considered experts. Seeing an unknown expert entering the city, it was natural for these people to pay attention.

Zhao Hai was unaware about these. The time he spent on the bookstore was very short. While these people were still looking for more information about him, he was already inside the Space.

After returning, Zhao Hai immediately looked for Cai’er and asked, “Cai’er, how many books did we get? And what kind of books were they?”

Cai’er quickly replied, “We have various books numbering more than 10 thousand. There were about ten thousand books on martial arts while the miscellaneous books numbered a thousand.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Good, then please reorganize these books for me. If there are low-level manuals mixed in, deal with it accordingly. If you see useful books, then make copies of it and send them to the Academies. But focus on high-level manuals and miscellaneous information. See if they have anything we need.”

Cai’er nodded before she left to process the books. As Zhao Hai sat down, Meg gave Zhao Hai a cup of herbal tea before saying, “Young Master, will you go to the Mage Continent tomorrow? Or would you take us out to play around?”

Zhao Hai forced a smile and said, “I’ll get more books tomorrow. I don’t have time left to play around. You can go out and play yourselves. I want to use the remaining days to look for books about ascending.”

Laura, who was on the side, said, “Brother Hai, there’s no need to waste too much time on these matters. Just abduct a high-level warrior and turn them into Undead. You do the same at the Mage Continent. This would make things quicker.”

Zhao Hai just bitterly smiled, “It’s okay. I just want to ascend, I don’t want to kill people. I need to look for information about ascending in the Mage and Warrior Continent. This way, I can make a perfect decision as to where to ascend.”

Chapter 1071: The Bright Sword Severs The Emotions, Finally Ascending!

Zhao Hai was currently standing on a desert island. This island was quite a distance away from the Mage Continent. Moreover, it was in a location where ship routes never pass through. One could only see stone on weeds on the island. Describing it using a proverb, it was an island where birds wouldn’t even defecate in.

This island was the place Zhao Hai chose to ascend in. Although it was far from the Mage Continent, it was still considered to be part of the continent. Not only was it far from the Mage Continent, it was also very far from the Warrior and the Magic Armor Continent. It was fitting to call it a desert island.

With no use as a supply point nor could it be exploited for its resources, the island was naturally unoccupied by humans.

After collecting books from both the Mage and Warrior continent, Zhao Hai used the rest of the time to look for a place to ascend in.

Ever since Zhao Hai discovered that the laws of the Magic Armor Continent and the Mage Continent were different, he knew that he was now left with the decision on where to ascend. He also knew that ascending on a different place would also send you to a different place in the Cultivation Realm. And in the end, Zhao Hai chose to ascend under the Mage Continent’s laws.

The reason Zhao Hao chose the Mage continent was because Mages were still less numerous than Warriors. Mages need talent to cultivate whereas Warriors had easier requirements. Because of this, there were fewer Mages compared to Warriors.

The less of a thing there was, the more precious it was. Although Zhao Hai doesn’t know the status of Mages in the Cultivation Realm, in his opinion, Mages were still more valuable than Warriors.

Additionally, he was always dressed in his robe and staff. And from the past few days, Zhao Hai came to understand the level of magic in the Mage Continent. Although the magic in the Mage Continent was more beautiful compared to the boring magic of the Underworld’s researchers, it was actually weaker. And with his knowledge of the Undead researchers’ magic, the magic level of the Mage continent was nothing to him.

As he stood on the desert island’s shore, Zhao Hai quietly gazed at the tumbling waves. His heart was a bit melancholic. Although he had been in the Atlanta Plane for some time, he was still aware that the plane was connected to the Ark Continent. With the Continent being his birth place, he felt sad that he would be leaving it probably forever.

Zhao Hai took in the scent of the sea’s gentle breeze. As he breathed in, he also felt that he only had two days before the energy inside his body reaches a critical point. When that time comes, then as long as he remains here, he would ascend.

Zhao Hai sighed before he sat down cross-legged. He was concentrating on his Myriad Stellar Transformations Yin-Yang Art. To be honest, besides that time in the Central Continent, Zhao Hai rarely practiced this cultivation method. He just let the method run its course.

Zhao Hai looks like he was just standing there, but in fact he was analyzing his own self. He discovered that he was actually a timid person. It was a deliberate decision for him to not practice the art. He wanted to delay his ascension as much as possible, and stay here for a long time.

There were two reasons for him to do this. First was because he came to love this place. And the second reason was because he was afraid!

He was afraid of the new environment. He was afraid of facing a formidable Cultivator. Perhaps he might not realize this, but it was what his subconscious wanted. It was because of this that he didn’t practice the Myriad Stellar Transformations Yin-Yang Art.

After discovering his own true nature, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but inwardly shout in shame. No wonder people said that the only person who might not know you would be you. This seems to be the case for him.

If he wasn’t about to ascend and tried to clear his mind, then he wouldn’t have realized this point. But fortunately, this realization didn’t come too late. Zhao Hai immediately used his divine sense to form a sword in order to sever this fear.

In the past, Zhao Hai heard the phrase, “the bright sword that severs the emotions”, but he couldn’t understand its meaning. But at this moment, he finally understood those words. When the mind reaches a complete phase, it can feel one’s seven emotions and six desires. One would then be able to distinguish each of these and gain complete understanding. It was because of this that Zhao Hai, with no hesitation, used his divine sense as a sword in order to sever the fear in his heart.

Besides this fear, Zhao Hai also used his divine sense to sever any other negative emotion. This didn’t mean that he wouldn’t have a negative mood from now on. Emotions take root deep into one’s heart. Even if you wanted to prevent it from coming out, you couldn’t. Zhao Hai just temporarily cut these emotions off, they would come back later on.

The reason Zhao Hai did this was because he wanted to welcome his ascension in his best state. As his ascension gets closer and closer, he began to feel some things. These feelings made it known to him that having too much emotion during his ascent wouldn’t be good. Ascension still carried some danger. If one cannot maintain their peak state, then their ascension might very well fail.

Natives from the Mage Continent who failed in their ascensions died. Even Zhao Hai might be seriously injured if this happens. Zhao Hai wasn’t hoping for this to happen to him.

After Zhao Hai severed his emotions, he immediately felt an unprecedented sense of clarity. This clarity didn’t come from the neatness of his body. Instead, it was a feeling that came from inside.

Not only did Zhao Hai feel comfortable. He also felt that his mind became much more insightful. The rocky parts of the Myriad Stellar Transformations Yin-Yang Art seem to be easily broken through.

The bright sword that severs the emotions was truly worth its reputation!

A whirlpool began to slowly form around Zhao Hai. This energy whirlpool got bigger and bigger until it turned into a small tornado and then into a giant tornado. In the end, it became like a black hole that wantonly absorbed all of the energy around him.

And in the center of this maelstrom of energy was a calm and steady Zhao Hai. He didn’t feel anything other than the repulsion of the plane getting stronger and stronger. This tremendous pressure seems to be bent on expelling his from this plane.

Then all of a sudden, dark clouds began to gather on top of Zhao Hai. The clouds began to clump up as it slowly shone with lightning. These lightning snaked through the clouds as if they were ready to strike down at any time.

Zhao Hai also felt the dark clouds forming, causing him to stop his cultivation. He stood up and looked at the clouds right on top of him. He was aware that this was his tribulation before he ascends.

Zhao Hai didn’t dare to ignore these clouds, he quickly held his blood ghost staff. This staff went through a lot of transformations in Zhao Hai’s hands. At this point, it was a very attractive piece of work. The staff had a blood red body and on it were symbols of the constellations. It looked both attractive and mysterious. The entire staff was about three meters. The body itself was 2.4 meters long, with the constellations hovering 20 centimeters away from the staff. The rest of the 60 centimeters were taken up by the blood red lotus. The lotus had seven cores and was divided into 18 layers. At the end of each lotus flap was a small red ring that held bells that swayed gently with the breeze, emitting a delightful ringing sound.

Zhao Hai’s original staff was just a meter long. At that size, it was still very convenient to hold on to. With the lotus on top of it, the staff became bulky to hold. Because of this Zhao Hai normally had the staff head become a skull.

But this long staff was actually something that Laura and the others designed. Zhao Hai also agreed to the three-meter long design. For a Mage, this staff wasn’t short nor was it very long.

There was a lot of Mages who use staffs longer than three meters. There were even some who held staffs that were four meters or longer. These were used to arrange formations in order to resist the enemy.

However, after Laura and the others showed him their design, Zhao Hai felt that the staff looked more like what Buddhist Monks use. Also, this staff wasn’t only used as a staff, the giant lotus can also be regarded as a weapon. Upon seeing the staff, Zhao Hai thought about a weapon he saw back on Earth, the spiked mace!

Naturally, Zhao Hai’s magic staff was much more attractive than spiked maces. Zhao Hai took his staff and looked up as the sky turned darker and darker.

He knew that there was no way to avoid this tribulation, it was a requirement to all those who wanted to ascend. If he hid inside the Space, then this dark cloud would vanish, only to reappear when Zhao Hai went out once more.

Zhao Hair revolved his gold core, providing massive amounts of energy to his body. At the same time, his dao lotus revolved gently. With each revolution, the energy in the gold core became more and more compressed. With the help of the dao lotus’ mysterious energy paths, Zhao Hai can oppose any enemy he would come across.

Zhao Hai stood in place, his magic staff on his hand. The wind from the whirlpool disturbed his hair. But despite this, his eyes were stuck on the dark clouds overhead. He was waiting for the tribulation to come down.

Laura and the others were also inside the Space, looking at the dark clouds. They were worried for Zhao Hai, they also knew that this was a tribulation that he couldn’t avoid.

Not only Laura and the others, Karen, Green, and the other members of the Buda Clan were also looking at the situation outside. They stopped what they were doing in order to observe the spectacle.

After accumulating to a certain degree, the dark clouds began to rumble. And along with a very loud thunder, a lightning bolt crashed down on Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai looked at the lightning bolt and coldly snorted before he waved his magic staff. A yellowish light went out of the staff. As it went out of the staff, the yellow light began to absorb energy. Before long, a yellow hammer appeared in the air as it opposed the incoming lightning bolt.

The yellow hammer that the staff projected out gave people a very heavy and strong feeling. The hammer shone in the air as it welcomed the approaching lightning.

Boom! A loud sound was heard as smoke and fire began to erupt overhead. After the collision vanished, the lightning bolt nor the hammer can be seen.

However, this wasn’t the end. After the first collision, another lightning bolt came down. This time, Zhao Hai’s staff issued a purple light as it formed a huge shield. This shield looked incomparably sturdy. As the lightning hit the shield, it seems as though the earth was about to break.

Despite the strength of the lightning, Zhao Hai’s huge shield miraculously survived. Then Zhao Hai emitted, blue, green, purple and golden lights from his staff. These lights formed a huge stick that sunk 100 meters deep into the desert island.

Just as this giant stick was formed, the third lightning bolt went down. The shield immediately dispersed. However, the lightning was attracted to the giant stick. Before long, the lightning dispersed.

Right after the third lightning went down, the fourth followed soon after. Since Zhao Hai didn’t have time to cast magic, he transformed his staff into a large glaive as he hacked through the lightning bolt.

The dark clouds seem to contain infinite amounts of energy. As Zhao Hai dispersed the fourth lightning, the fifth immediately crashed down, not giving Zhao Hai any time to prepare. But this time, Zhao Hai already crystallized his body. Although the lightning bolt hit Zhao Hai’s body, he still kept standing. The staff quickly formed into a shield as he blocked the incoming lightning.

And just as the shield has been formed, the sixth lightning came down. The shield shivered gently, but it didn’t sustain any damage. Then the seventh strike came, then the eight, and then the ninth. Each strike as strong as the previous one. However, the blood red shield protected Zhao Hai through them all. It only shivered slightly with each strike.

After the ninth lightning strike, the dark clouds began to disperse. Then Zhao Hai turned his blood ghost staff into its original appearance. Once the dark clouds have dispersed, a ten meter tall, three meter wide spatial rift appeared in the sky. The rift let out a sucking force that pulled Zhao Hai in. Zhao Hai’s present strength couldn’t resist this pulling force, so he could only let go and let himself be absorbed.

After Zhao Hai entered the rift, the desert island went back to its desolate state. But this time, Zhao Hai can no longer be seen!

Chapter 1072: Machines!

After a dazzling white light, Zhao Hai opened his eyes slowly. He stared at four directions only to see that he was inside a room. Moreover, this room had people inside!

This room was quite big, having a floor area of more than a thousand square meters. It also had a ten meter high ceiling. The floor was made out of the same bright silvery material.

In this room, whether it was the walls or the ceiling, they were all made out of metals. On these metals were magic formations, each as mysterious as the others. These formations were layered on top of each other, adding on to their mystery. Those who were dabbling in magic formations would surely go blank upon seeing this scene, this was how wonderful the formations were.

This ten thousand square meter room was almost empty. Besides the people standing inside, there weren’t anything else.

Zhao Hai inspected the people with him. All of these people were wearing Mage’s robes. Their robes seems to be made out of ancient standards, covering their entire bodies. Besides these people were their magic staffs. Zhao Hai hadn’t seen staffs like these before. These staffs were all made out of metal.

While Zhao Hai was observing these people, they suddenly took a step forward. Zhao Hai waved his hand, taking his blood ghost staff out in preparation of defending against these people.

But at the same time, Zhao Hai also noted that the energy here was much stronger compared to the Atlanta Plane. It can be said that the laws of the Atlanta Plane and even the Underworld couldn’t compare to this place. Zhao Hai also noticed that the pressure on him had completely vanished. This feeling of being unrestrained was something that he hadn’t felt in a very long time.

Zhao Hai observed the five other Mages inside this room. When he swept them using his spiritual force, he suddenly discovered that these Mages didn’t emit any energy, they didn’t even emit any signs of life. This made Zhao Hai stare.

At this moment, the five Mages arrived in front of Zhao Hai. When they came close to him, Zhao Hai discovered that these people had number plates on their bodies. And even more surprising was the fact that these numbers are in Arabic Numerals.

The Mage with the number plate of ‘1’ opened its mouth and said, “Greetings, ascended Mage. Welcome to the Machine Field. Please come with us.”

The voice that went out of the Mage’s mouth sounded female. It actually sounded very gentle. However, Zhao Hai wasn’t attracted to this voice. This was because the voice sounded synthetic, artificial.

It was at this point that Zhao Hai can affirm. These Mages weren’t people, they were robots!

Although he was able to see this, Zhao Hai still made a polite response, “Thank you.” After he said that, he followed the robots.

What made Zhao Hai feel even stranger was the fact that there were no doors nor windows in this room, it was just like a metallic cube. He really wanted to know how they were supposed to leave.

This was also the time that Zhao Hai discovered the reason why the room was bright despite the lack of windows nor doors. This was because on the walls of the room, as well as the floor, were sources of white light. The light was very gentle, it wasn’t overly dazzling.

Zhao Hai arrived at a wall alongside the five robots. This section of wall wasn’t any different than the other sections. However, Robot Mage Number 1 placed her hand on the wall and pressed a few magical symbols. After that, the symbols shone as a door opened right in front. This door appeared very quickly, Zhao Hai wasn’t even able to catch how it opened.

The door wasn’t that big, it could only accommodate two people walking side by side. After opening the door, Robot Mage Number 1 turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Respected Mage, please.”

Zhao Hai nodded before walking through the door. Upon coming out the other side, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but pause. What entered was another room, albeit smaller than the previous one.

This room wasn’t big, only about 100 square meters in floor area. The walls of this room seems to be made out of stone. On its ceiling was a very ancient lamp. This lamp comprised of iron chains as well as discs. It looked very sturdy as it held fluorescent stones that lit the place up.

The floor was covered with a layer of carpet that was very comfortable to step on. What attracted Zhao Hai’s attention the most were the five bookshelves. Each bookshelf was stocked up with books. However, the books looked like they haven’t been touched for a long time.

Behind a table on one corner of the room was a person. The person was flat on the table and seemed to be asleep.

Zhao Hai could feel a formidable strength coming out of this person. It was a level of strength that he hadn’t met before. Even at his present level, if he was against this person, he can see himself lose.

The five Robot Mages brought Zhao Hai to the table before Robot Mage Number 1 opened her mouth and said, “Mister, a Mage has ascended to the Machine Field. Please register his presence.”

The person groaned before slowly sitting straight. Then he stretched his body before saying, “Really, I couldn’t even sleep for a while…” Then after sobering up, the person looked at Zhao Hai and smiled before asking, “Name, plane of origin, and profession?” Zhao Hai looked at the person’s appearance. He couldn’t help but frown inside, but he still replied, “This one is Zhao Hai, from the Atlanta Plane, an all-element Mage.”

While he was giving his answer, Zhao Hai was also sizing the person up. This person seems to be a Mage. His build wasn’t small. He had white beard that contrasted with his black mage robe. The man was knitting his eyebrows, his hair and beard were completely unkempt. He didn’t look that handsome.

The old man wrote with his quill as he listened to Zhao Hai’s answer. But when he heard that Zhao Hai was an all-element Mage, his quill stopped. Then he looked straight at Zhao Hai as he frowned and said, “You say that you’re an all-element Mage?”

Zhao Hai was actually attracted to the old man’s quill. Zhao Hai discovered that the old man’s quill pen wasn’t a normal pen. Instead of having ink on its tip, the quill pen actually emitted beautiful, dazzling light.

At the same time, although the table looked like it was made out of ordinary wood, it actually had a small film on top of it. As the light fell on this film, the words that were written began to levitate.

Upon hearing the old Mage’s question, Zhao Hai recovered, then he nodded and said, “Yes, this one is an all-element Mage.”

The Old Mage’s two eyes shone, he smiled and said, “Alright, very good. Show me a spell or two.” Zhao Hai stared, then he looked around before turning back to the Old Man, “Right now?” The Old Man looked at Zhao Hai’s reaction and smiled, “Yes, right now. But don’t use too much magic.”

Zhao Hai nodded. He didn’t reject the request, he knew that this was some sort of test. He waved left his hand, summoning a tornado on his hand. As though like dancing elves, the tornado danced on his hand, drilling through his fingers as though it was a playful child..

This wasn’t the end, Zhao Hai waved his right hand, summoning a little fireball. This fireball also rolled about his hand. Then Zhao Hai threw the fireball over to his left hand. The fireball and the tornado met and proceeded to chase each other.

After that, Zhao Hai waved his right hand once more, summoning a ball of water. Then after tossing the ball of water to his left hand, Zhao Hai summoned a piece of stone, then a black and white mass. After summoning the six elements, Zhao Hai had them revolve around his body. They looked like six naughty children gathering around their father.

After showing this, Zhao Hai knew that he had shown his capabilities. He gave a snort as the elements vanished. Then he looked at the Old Mage and said, “Mister, is that enough?”

The Old Mage looked at Zhao Hai with shining eyes as he nodded again and again, saying, “Good, very good.” He said that while writing a few more lines on the table. After some time, he placed the quill down and then took out a piece of paper from the side. Taking a look at the contents of the paper, the Old Man nodded before handing it over to Zhao Hai, “Take this and follow them. Take a break for today. Someone will come and pick you up tomorrow morning. He will take you to a place, there you will know everything you need to know.” Zhao Hai looked at the paper and read its contents. The writing was in traditional chinese, but Zhao Hai could see that the contents of the paper were related to him. It had his name, the plane he came from, the fact that he was an all-element Mage, and then some appraisals about him.

The Old Man really wasn’t stingy in appraising Zhao Hai. Above the information that Zhao Hai was an all-element Mage, the Old Man also added that he had reached a high-level of control and it was suggested that he should undergo training.

Upon seeing this, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but force a smile. He was an apex Expert in the Atlanta Plane. But in here, it seems like he needed training. He didn’t know whether he should laugh or cry.

However, Zhao Hai didn’t dare to show that he was dissatisfied. This was because he felt that the Old Mage’s strength was no weaker than him, and might even be more powerful. If that Old Man saw him looking dissatisfied, then he might teach him a lesson. With no information about where he was, Zhao Hai naturally wouldn’t mess anything up.

Chapter 1073: Room 2046

The Old Man looked at Zhao Hai staring at the paper and smiled, “Young Man, go and take a rest. You just ascended to Machine Field. I know that you are the strongest person at your plane. But here, you’re just an early ascendant. Go, go and rest. Someone will fetch you tomorrow to take you to a place with all the answers you seek.”

When he heard the Old Mage, Zhao Hai immediately stopped reading the paper. Then he gave the Old Man a respectful bow and said, “Yes, thank you for the advice.” Then Zhao Hai turned around and followed the five Robot Mages.

After seeing Zhao Hai leave, the Old Mage murmured, “He’s a special one. A Mage that isn’t arrogant. He will surely make waves in the future.” Once he said that, the Old Mage yawned once more before leaning on the table and saying, “I hope those guys can train him properly.” His voice got quieter and quieter as he finally fell asleep.

Zhao Hai followed the Robot Mages and left the room. While they were walking up a level, Zhao Hai tried to use his spiritual force to scan the surroundings. Then he discovered that the building was made out of special materials that completely isolated spiritual force.

Upon knowing about this, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but be more careful. His spiritual force was very formidable, it was many times better than ordinary Mages. But even so, he still cannot penetrate anything inside this place.

Not to mention the Old Mage’s strength, nor the materials used to make this building that weren’t in the Atlanta Plane, the five Robot Mages alone made Zhao Hai curious about this place called the Machine Field.

But what made Zhao Hai curious the most was the fact that he didn’t ascend in the Cultivation Realm, but instead in this Machine Field. Also, he hadn’t heard about this place before, did Lu Wei’s remnant soul lie? That’s impossible. At that time, the soul has been subdued by the Space, it couldn’t have lied. It might be because he ascended in the Atlanta Plane.

After he thought about this, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but feel regret. If he knew that he would ascend to this place, then he might not have chosen the Mage Continent. Instead, he would just choose to ascend in the Divine Realm. After all, he still had some understanding with regards to the Cultivation Realm. As for this Machine Field, he was completely clueless.

But after some thought, Zhao Hai removed the negative thoughts from his mind and instead rejoiced. Looking at what just happened, it seems like the Machine Field was used to receiving ascenders. Moreover, they already had a set of procedures in welcoming newcomers. This was noteworthy. This meant that this plane’s strength was much higher than the Mage Continent. It shouldn’t be any weaker than the Cultivation Realm.

While Zhao Hai was thinking about these things, the five Robot Mages stopped in front of a room before Number 1 turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, please go in and take a rest. We shall be waiting outside. You can call us if you need anything.” Zhao Hai recovered, then after he gave the Robot Mages his gratitude, he turned around and pushed the door open. But upon seeing the door plate, Zhao Hai couldnt’ help but stare. There were four numbers printed in arabic numerals, 2046!

When he saw these four numbers, Zhao Hai didn’t know whether to laugh or cry. It seems like he was number 2046. Who knows if this room was different compared to the others.

He gently shook his head and then entered the room. Zhao Hai also knew that this was just a coincidence, it shouldn’t be related to Earth.

It was an ordinary room. It was divided into two parts, a small living room and the bedroom. In between the living room and the bedroom was a door. Zhao Hai opened it and saw that it was the bathroom.

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but faintly smile. He didn’t mind the room anymore as he walked to his bedroom. The bedroom was also very ordinary, there wasn’t anything special inside. It had a cabinet, a bed, and a lamp. After looking through the room, Zhao Hai sat down and began to contact Cai’er using his mind.

And after hearing Cai’er’s reply, Zhao Hai began to feel relieved. Then he used his mind to talk, “Cai’er, I won’t be able to enter the Space in the meantime. I’m afraid this room is under surveillance. Let’s wait for a while as I gain more understanding about this plane. Tell everyone that there’s no need to worry.” Cai’er gave her approval. After the small conversation, Zhao Hao stopped their communication. Then he began to sit cross-legged as he rested. What Zhao Hai didn’t know was the fact that he was right. This room was monitored. Not entering the Space was the right decision.

The moment Zhao Hai entered room 2046, his actions were immediately noted down. Moreover, his presence in this room began to shake the Machine Field.

Zhao Hai just came to the Machine Field so he didn’t know. The Machine Field was quite good in looking after ascenders from the lower realms. This was because everyone knew that the concentration of energy in both realms were very different. If someone was able to ascend from a lower realm, then this meant that they were rare talents. Such people needed to be trained well and they might emerge as powerful Experts later on.

Naturally, this went according to how diligent the ascender was. After all, back in their lower realms, these ascenders were powerful experts. But upon reaching the Machine Realm, they were demoted into ordinary people. Some people couldn’t bear this change of status and would live a life of degeneracy and vanishing from the eyes of the people. There would also be people who treated the Machine Field as an amusement park, not having the heart to progress in their cultivation. With this mindset, it was impossible for them to become strong.

The place where Zhao Hai was currently in was an area specifically made to receive ascenders. There were quite a lot of planes that the Machine Field was in control of. And almost every year, an ascender would come from the lower realms. However, only a handful of these ascenders would truly prove themselves as talented, the others, for some reason, became just ordinary people.

But among the rooms used to receive ascenders, there was one room the Machine Field deemed very special. And it was room 2046!

Besides the reception tower as well as the first level staff room, the second to eleventh layers were places for ascenders to occupy. There were 100 rooms in each level. Above the eleventh floor were rooms for the staff to rest in.

There weren’t necessarily 100 people in the Machine Field’s Ascender Reception Area. Moreover, some of them would live here for just one night and then leave the day after. Because of this, these 100 rooms were generally empty. The staff responsible for registering the ascenders was also in charge of where to put them. Naturally, the assignment of the rooms wasn’t random.

One’s room went according to the ascender’s recorded aptitude. The higher your talent, the higher the floor you’ll be assigned to. And the lower one’s floor assignment was, the lower their talent would be. And Zhao Hai was in the second level, so he should be on one of the worst rooms. However, room 2046 was an exception.

Among the ascender reception staff, room 2046 held a very special status. Naturally, room 2046 was just an ordinary room in the beginning. But one day, it changed when a Mage from a lower realm ascended. This Mage was referred to have a low aptitude, and that he had no future. Because of this, he was assigned to room 2046. But who would’ve expected that the Mage would create a miracle, becoming a famous expert in the Machine Field. In his old age, the Mage decided to settle down in the Ascender Reception Tower. And from that moment on, each ascender that the Mage had his eyes on would be sent to room 2046. And after that, every ascender that took residence in room 2046 became strong experts. This Mage would continually assign ascenders to room 2046, and almost without fail, those ascenders would become strong experts. As this information got passed around, the Machine Field began to have an unwritten rule, every ascender living in room 2046 was favored to be a strong expert later on.

Because of this, people would pay attention whenever an ascender gets assigned to room 2046. But Zhao Hai was unaware of this. He thought that it was the Robot Mages’ decision to assign him to room 2046.

At this moment, Zhao Hai’s image was passed around to all influences in the Machine Realm. Before long, all of these powers began to note Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai continued to practice inside his room. However, he felt a little strange. He was very sensitive when it came to energy. Because of this, he knew very clearly that the amount of energy inside this metal room shouldn’t be that rich. Although the laws here were the same, the energy density had actually undergone a huge change.

Even if he was puzzled, Zhao Hai recalled the Old Mage saying that someone would take him to a place tomorrow. There, all of his questions would be answered. Because of this, Zhao Hai didn’t dwell on this matter for long.

Since he was in a new place, he needed to be low-key. Therefore, Zhao Hai planned to show as little as possible. But he didn’t know that the Old Mage fancied his talent and placed him in room 2046.

If Zhao Hai knew about what the Old Mage did, then he wouldn’t know whether to laugh or cry. Fortunately, he was careful and didn’t enter the Space. Otherwise, his secret might place him into huge trouble.

Zhao Hai didn’t know that his information was already on the desks of the Machine Field’s various powers. When these huge influences saw that Zhao Hai was a Mage that can use all of the elements, they immediately took note of him.

Back in the Divine Realm, Zhao Hai transformed his energy to shift between battle qi and magic. However, due to the Mage Continent’s laws, this transformation between energies and elements was impossible. Zhao Hai didn’t know about this because he spent too little time in the Mage Continent.

Chapter 1074: Ascender Academy

The laws of the heavens and the earth have always been a mystery! Each place had their own distinct law. Take the Mage Continent for example, they had laws that only permit the use of magic energy. Besides magic energy, they couldn’t use anything else. But even if they could other energies, they wouldn’t be able to use too much of it. Because of this, nobody in the Mage Continent cultivated both martial arts and magic. And in the end, they would never reach the peak strength of an individual, not to even say ascending. This was the same case with the Warrior Continent and the Magic Armor Continent. The reason why Zhao Hai was repelled by the laws was because his body was full of both battle qi and magic.

When he ascended to the Machine Field, Zhao Hai was still able to use all kinds of energy. Normally, when the Old Mage asked someone from the Mage Continent to show their spells, they would certainly use the element they were proficient in. But since Zhao Hai didn’t know about this, he revealed that he was a Mage that could use all of the elements.

Zhao Hai might not know about the Mage Continent’s state, but the people from the Machine Field did. Therefore, when they heard that Zhao Hai was an all-element Mage, they were shocked.

It needed more than aptitude to ascend while also being an all-element Mage. Needless to say, the people from the Machine Field paid very close attention to Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai didn’t know any of these, so he just sat there the entire evening, cultivating. He knew that even if he was an expert in the Atlanta Plane, but in the Machine Field, he was only someone with some talent. If he wanted to live a better life here, then he needed to be competent.

Zhao Hai’s actions actually earned the praise of the people observing him. There were some ascenders who still had the mindset that they were very strong. Because of this, their bodies exuded arrogance and would eventually be idle. People like Zhao Hai who still cultivated after ascending were in the minority.

Even those who became strong afterwards were still arrogant when they ascended. On their first night, they couldn’t sit still like Zhao Hai and practice the entire night.

The more he was like this, the more it showed that Zhao Hai was different. Those who’ve seen Zhao Hai’s conduct felt that he was even more worthy of their attention.

To a person who was absorbed in their cultivation, one night was nothing. Zhao Hai only thought that he was circulating his Myriad Stellar Transformations Yin-Yang a few times before he heard a knock coming from outside his room.

Zhao Hai stopped cultivating as he said, “Come in.”

The door opened before a person wearing mage robes entered. This person’s mage robes were unlike the ones worn by the Robot Mages. This person’s robes were very fashionable and didn’t cover his entire body.

Zhao Hai stared, he looked at the person and asked, “You are?”

The person smiled faintly at Zhao Hai and said, “Are you Mister Zhao Hai who ascended from the Atlanta Plane yesterday? Hello, I’m here to pick you up.”

Zhao Hai quickly replied, “I’m Zhao Hai. Hello. May I know where you’re taking me?”

The Mage smiled and said, “All ascenders from the lower realms needs to study in the Machine Field’s Ascender Academy for one year. And after a test, you will then be provided with an official citizenship. I’m here to lead you to the academy.”

Upon hearing the Mage, Zhao Hai immediately nodded and said, “Alright, I’ll have to trouble you.”

The person smiled and said, “Not a problem. Since this is a place for you to temporarily take a rest, you’ll only get to eat after arriving at the Academy” Then he made a gesture to lead Zhao Hai.

After expressing his gratitude, Zhao Hai proceeded to walk shoulder to shoulder with the Mage. Zhao Hai no longer saw the five Robot Mage as he walked together with the Mage. Since Zhao Hai lived on the second floor, they were able to head outside very quickly.

Zhao Hai was met with shock upon reaching outside. What he saw was something that could only be seen in science fiction movie scenes. There were tall buildings, each one easily reaching 100 floors. On the skies were flying vehicles just like the one from the movies. On some corners and sides of buildings were huge screens showing advertisements.

Upon seeing Zhao Hai’s reaction, the person smiled and said, “You’ll slowly get used to it. Come, let’s get going.” As he said that, the person gestured Zhao Hai towards a car not far away. This car was just like other automobiles, but this one didn’t have wheels, instead it had something that looked like propellers. It looked like a vehicle meant for aquatic use.

Zhao Hai didn’t ask anything and just lowered his head in order to enter the vehicle. While the other person was entering the car, Zhao Hai took the opportunity to look at the place he came from. It was a tall tower, but in this large concrete jungle filled with tall buildings, it was on the shorter side. It only had about 20 floors, and even if looked shorter than it was, it would be 30 floors at most.

The entire tower was made out of a type of azure stone. It looked ancient, just like how the others magic towers were made. There were no windows on this tower, exactly like some magic towers. Zhao Hai couldn’t help but be stunned. He didn’t expect a building such as this to exist in this place.

The person saw Zhao Hai’s reaction as he smiled faintly and said, “Does it seem strange that the ascender tower looks incompatible with the surrounding buildings?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “It looks out of place.”

The person smiled and said, “This is the oldest building in the entire Magic City. And the building was also intentionally built to look like this.”

Zhao Hai looked at the man with a puzzled expression. The man just smiled and said, “You’re from the lower realms. Don’t you think that it would be better to live in buildings like these?” Then he gestured towards the nearby tall buildings.

Then he turned his head to the front of the car and said, “Ascender Academy.” The vehicle silently started. It was a smooth start that Zhao Hai wasn’t even able to notice that the vehicle was already running.

However, Zhao Hai shook his head and replied to the earlier question, “To be honest, I felt uncomfortable in that building when I arrived.”

The person smiled and said, “It is for this reason that we didn’t replicate its appearance. Also, the appearance of the building has a function. The building has magic formations that suppresses spiritual qi.”

Zhao Hai immediately asked, “Spiritual Qi?”

The person looked at Zhao Hai and smiled, “Right, Spiritual Qi. In the Machine Field, we don’t study what you call magic energy. Instead, we have spiritual qi. Don’t think that Spiritual Qi is weak based on your experience yesterday. That was because the building has formations that suppresses spiritual qi. Actually, the spiritual qi in the Machine Field is a hundred times more than what you experienced before. But newly ascended people like you might not be able to adjust to the abrupt change in concentration, causing you to turn insane. You need time to adapt, so the tower suppresses the spiritual qi in the surroundings. In the course of one year, the Ascender Academy will gradually train you to adapt to the normal amount of spiritual qi. Once you get used to the normal level of spiritual qi and pass the assessment, then you will become an official citizen of Machine Field.”

While the person was saying that, the car was speeding through the air. Although the car was very fast, the speed can’t actually be felt inside. It just felt like they were just sitting in a room.

By the time the person stopped speaking, the car stopped in front of a lot. This lot was quite big, complementing the huge 100-story or more building in front of it. Above the large building were four characters that read ‘Ascender Academy’.

After the car stopped, the vehicle door automatically opened as electronic voice was heard, “Ascender Academy, please disembark.”

The person turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Let’s head out.” Zhao Hai nodded and exited the car along with the Mage.

Just as they stood on the ground, it suddenly moved forward. Zhao Hai stared at the ground for a moment and didn’t care about it anymore.

The person looked at Zhao Hai and smiled, “You reacted quite well. I received someone who fell over the moment it moved.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Actually, my Atlanta Plane is quite developed. Although we don’t have moving platforms, we have elevators. I think the principle between the two is quite similar.”

The man turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Really? The Atlanta Plane has elevators? You aren’t lying?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Of course its true. You might now know, but the Atlanta Plane is divided into three continents, the Mage Continent, Warrior Continent, and the Magic Armor Continent. The Mage Continent and the Warrior Continent didn’t have elevators, but the Magic Armor Continent did. Oh right, those Mages that received me yesterday, they looked like magic armors from the Magic Armor Continent. They aren’t really people are they?”

Zhao Hai deliberately inserted the last part in order to probe for information. The person didn’t suspect anything as he said, “Of course they’re not people. They’re robots that are made to look like people. They’re just machines. So those magic armors, what do they look like?”

Zhao Hai replied, “Magic armors are metal giants several meters tall. People can enter this giant and operate it from the inside. In addition to fighting, magic armors can also fly. They’re strength is quite formidable. Moreover, there’s also an ascension magic armor. I hear that high-level pilots use them in order to ascend. Do they ascend here?”

The person nodded and said, “It’s possible that they ascended here. But the place where you’re from didn’t have any ascenders for a long time. I had this job for 20 years, and I haven’t heard of someone ascending from your plane.”

Zhao Hai just gave a smile, “The rate of ascension in the Atlanta Plane is very slow. There has been so many years since somebody ascended.”

The man gave a nod, “That’s normal. There are some planes that won’t have ascenders for several hundred years. It’s not a big deal.”

The two arrived at the large building as they chatted. There was a huge screen before the large building. Shown on that screen were information related to the Ascender Academy. The entire building was called the Ascender Mage Academy. This was because this building was for training Mage Ascenders.

The person looked at Zhao Hai who was reading the screen and smiled, “There’s no need to read everything. You’ll know all about that as you spend time here. Let’s go and have you registered first. Then after you settle down at the dormitory, you can have your meal.”

Zhao Hai nodded and entered the building. Inside was a very big hall, it wasn’t any smaller than the hall Zhao Hai ascended to.

Inside this hall were people in Mage robes busily walking in and out. Several of these people saw Zhao Hai arrive and then whispered among each other.

Since Zhao Hai’s ears were very sensitive, he was able to hear their words, “This one’s new. Who knows where he came from.”

Another said, “Who cares where he came from? He may be a genius back there, but here everyone is equal.”

At this time, Zhao Hai arrived at the innermost part of the hall. There was a door that had three characters that read “Registration Office”. The man pushed the door open and entered. Zhao Hai quickly followed behind.

The room wasn’t very big, only about 20 or so square meters. The inside looked simple. It only had a table, a chair, and a robot.

This one looked like a very simple robot. It had a round head and its face was half-covered with a screen. It had a silvery body and two arms that showed plates and gears. The robot’s left hand was a rectangular box while the other was equipped with a pen.

Zhao Hai looked at this and understood why the person didn’t even bother to knock. So the one inside the room wasn’t a person.

The man wasn’t polite as he arrived in front of the robot and then turned to Zhao Hai, “Give me the piece of paper that you received yesterday.” Zhao Hai took the paper that was given to him by the Old Mage and then handed it over to the person.

After the Mage received the piece of paper, he placed it on the table. The robot’s screen turned bright before writing something on the paper with its pen. After that, the robot’s rectangular box whirred two times before a card was spat out.

Chapter 1075: A Bag of Coins For A Secret

The man took the card from the robot before handing it over to Zhao Hai, then he said, “This is your ID card. For one year, you would only be able to live inside the Ascender Academy. But you can use this card both in and out of the academy. You will have your own separate room to store your items. This ID card also functions as a bank card. Do you know what a bank is?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Of course, we have banks in the Atlanta Plane. We also use our ID cards as bank cards back there.”

The man nodded and said, “It seems like I need to know more about the Atlanta Plane. I didn’t expect your civilization to be advanced. This card has 10,000 machine coins. You can use this to buy things. Naturally, the dormitory and the canteen won’t cost any money. But there’s also a restaurant on the premises. If you want to eat good food, then you can go to the restaurant to eat. But you need to spend money if you want to do that. Although 10,000 isn’t a lot, it should be enough for you to live with for an entire year. You also need to pay attention to the tests every month. The content of these tests vary, and there’s also tests that relate to the military. If you pass these tests, you will gain money as reward. If you fail them, then your money will be deducted as punishment. Do you understand?”

Zhao Hai nodded. Not only did the Machine Field welcome the ascenders, they took great pains in order to construct this academy. They also made sure to have the ascender get used to spiritual qi. At the same time, the academy was built like a small city to make the ascenders familiar with the lifestyle of the Machine Field. And to top it all off, they even gave 10,000 machine coins. They were truly generous.

The man looked at Zhao Hai’s expression and couldn’t help but ask, “Aren’t you shocked? I’ve seen ascenders before who reacted strongly to the one-year stay inside the academy. They said that we’re putting them under arrest.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Mister can rest assured, I’m very satisfied with this arrangement. Right, how can I know where I’ll be staying? Going to eat? Or where to head to class?”

As soon as the man heard Zhao Hai, he immediately replied, “There’s no need to worry about that. After obtaining this card, you will also be given a Robot Butler. You can even take this robot with you after you leave the academy. If you need anything, you can just ask the butler to assist you.”

After he said that, the door opened and a robot entered. This robot wasn’t as advanced as the Mage Robots from the ascender tower. This robot looked like a metal shell with a head and two eyes. While it walked over, one could hear the gears moving. One could see at first glance that it wasn’t a good product.

The man looked at the robot and said, “This is you Robot Butler. If you don’t want this one, you can just go to the school’s store to buy another one. Robot Butlers are quite cheap, you can buy several of them using your 10,000 coins. You can also exchange your lower realm items in the shop in exchange for coins. And since your lower realm coins don’t circulate here, you can go to the school’s bank and have them exchanged. Rest assured, the exchange rate is very fair. At the very least, you won’t eat a huge loss. Alright, I’ve already accomplished what I need to do. If you have any questions, you can just tell them to this robot. Programmed into this robot are common questions that ascenders ask.”

Zhao Hai nodded before he gave a bow and said, “Thanks for the hard work. Right, from the beginning I failed to ask for your name. I’ve been disrespectful. Please accept this small gift.” Then Zhao Hai turned his hand to retrieve a small sack. This cloth bag wasn’t that big, but the thing inside felt quite heavy.

The man was also a good judge of the items. After seeing Zhao Hai’s cloth sack, he knew that it was a bag of coins. To be honest, he didn’t expect Zhao Hai to give him a bag of coins.

The man worked in this job for more than 20 years and had met quite a number of ascenders. These ascenders were too arrogant to give him gifts. When they saw him, they all treated him as though he were a servant. Although he took this job because he didn’t have the talent to progress, he still felt uncomfortable with being looked down upon. Zhao Hai was the first person in 20 years that gave him any gifts.

The man actually didn’t take the coins and just bowed and said, “I thank Mister Zhao Hai. I’m called Gu Mingyue. Mister Zhao Hai, I’ve been a receptionist for more than 20 years, and this is the first time that someone has given me gifts. However, I simply cannot accept your generosity. You need these gold coins. This academy is built just like a small city. In order to get settled here, you would need money. You also need to save up some money for the future.”

Zhao Hai laughed and said, “There’s no need for Mister to worry about me. I’m a Mage, I could easily study magic for a whole year without going out. I also don’t like to walk around, so I don’t need that much money. Please take it.” Then he took Gu Mingyue’s hand and placed the bag on it.

Gu Mingyue looked at Zhao Hai and felt his heart move. He looked outside the room before turning to the Robot Butler, saying, “You go wait for us outside.” The Robot Butler didn’t move and just turned to Zhao Hai, obviously treating him as its master. It would only listen to Zhao Hai’s instructions.

After seeing Gu Mingyue’s expression, Zhao Hai knew that the man had something to say. So he immediately turned to the robot and said, “You go outside and wait.” The robot immediately bowed towards Zhao Hai and said, “Yes, Master.” Then it proceeded to leave the room.

Once the robot had left the room, Gu Mingyue immediately looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Mister Zhao Hai, you need to be alert if you intend to use this robot. It isn’t just a Robot Butler, it is also used to observe a person. If you use him, make sure to have him modified by a special robot shop inside the school and remove the surveillance device. There are a lot of robot shops inside the academy, but there are special ones that don’t care about the academy’s power and influence. If you also want to buy robots, buy them from those special stores, they can guarantee the quality of your robot.” Zhao Hai blinked upon hearing this. Then he said, “Alright, I will pay attention. Thank you for the warning Mister Gu. If you need anything from me in the future, then don’t hesitate to approach me. I’ll do what I can to help.”

Gu Mingyue bowed and said, “Thank you, Mister Zhao Hai. I will take my leave first.” Then he turned around and left.

After seeing Gu Mingyue being honest, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile. He understood that Gu Mingyue was a low-level character here in the Machine Field. And it would be close to impossible for him to advance further in life. Because of this, he could only be a receptionist here. Moreover, he did so for already 20 years.

Because of their status in life, these low-level characters wouldn’t enter the eyes of most ascenders. But Zhao Hai knew that these kinds of people had their own methods and means in order to survive. If you make connections with them, then you would certainly gain unexpected benefits later on.

Now that Zhao Hai arrived at a completely new place, his way forward was essentially dark. In this case, it wouldn’t be bad to have a few friends while keeping a low profile. If he were plunged into cunning plots and ruses, who would save his life?

Take today’s matter for example, a bag of gold coins was nothing to Zhao Hai. But to Gu Mingyue, it might actually represent something, even changing his state in life. Most importantly, Gu Mingyue saw Zhao Hai’s respect in that bag of gold coins.

And because of this, Gu Mingyue was able to tell Zhao Hai such a relevant information. Otherwise, Zhao Hai wouldn’t have known about the surveillance device inside the robot.

This information was very important to Zhao Hai. His biggest secret was the Farm. If a heaven defying thing such as the Farm was made known to these people, then they would certainly use all kinds of means in order to take it from him.

Gu Mingyue told Zhao Hai that the spiritual qi in the Machine Field was a hundred times more than the lower realms. With such a concentration of energy, the Machine Field certainly had much more powerful experts than the Underworld.

Zhao Hai also came to know that the laws of a plane had a direct relationship with the plane’s density of spiritual qi. Since the Ark Continent’s spiritual qi was inferior to the Divine Realm, it could only produce experts up to 9th rank. God-ranks would need to ascend not only because of the laws, but also because of the spiritual qi.

If God-ranks stay in the Ark Continent for a long time, then they would absorb massive amounts of the Ark Continent’s spiritual qi. This would affect the continent’s development. Since the density of the spiritual qi was low, the Ark Continent’s laws wouldn’t permit the constant presence of God-ranks inside the plane.

The laws and the density of spiritual qi were part of the universe. Naturally, they complement each other. The laws of the Ark Continent’s have been forcibly changed, and even if it was connected to the Divine Realm, it still couldn’t replenish the spiritual qi being lost. Because of this, the Ark Continent opened more spatial cracks in order to supplement its need of spiritual qi.

Although the energy of the Underworld was dark energy, it was still a type of spiritual qi. Since the spiritual qi of the Underworld was superior than the Divine Realm, the strongest experts born there would naturally be stronger than the ones in the Divine Realm.

And now, the spiritual qi of the Machine Realm was supposedly 100 times more than the Atlanta Plane. According to estimation, the strongest experts here should be at least 100 times stronger than the peak experts in the Atlanta Plane. Faced with such experts, even Zhao Hai was certain that he wouldn’t be able to make a struggle.

Zhao Hai recalled his arrogance back in the Underworld, where he could just flatten a city with ease. But now he was clear that he couldn’t afford such arrogance.

Chapter 1076: The Massive World of Cultivation!

When Zhao Hai left the registration office, the Robot Butler clunkily went to greet him. Seeing the mechanical being approaching him, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but admit that this robot was very ugly. And with Gu Mingyue’s reminder, he knew that he wouldn’t be keeping this robot by his side.

However, he wouldn’t replace this robot immediately, it would be too suspicious if he did so. Also, it wouldn’t be too late to exchange this robot later on. And the robot wouldn’t be following him at night, so he can just go to the Space then.

Zhao Hai wasn’t polite as he told the butler, “I’ll be calling you Tinkle from now on, and you’ll call me Young Master. Understood?”

The Robot Butler bowed and said, “Tinkle understands. Young Master can rest assured.”

Zhao Hai nodded before he said, “Tinkle, take me to see my room.”

Tinkle complied before leading Zhao Hai to the side. Zhao Hai was now able to see that there were several elevators. Moreover, the numbers on top of these elevators reached three digits.

To be honest, the level of technology in the Machine Field had exceeded Zhao Hai’s imagination. At the same time, their level of magic formations was also beyond his expectations.

Whether it was an elevator or a speeding car, all of these things had traces of magic formations in them. These magic formations weren’t just ornaments, they really had a purpose. This caused Zhao Hai to be surprised.

Developing technology and magic formations to this degree wasn’t an easy feat. While he thought of this, Zhao Hai and Tinkle entered into the elevator. As Tinkle pressed a few buttons, Zhao Hai noticed that alongside numbers, there were also guides on the panel. For example, on the button with ‘12’ in it, the word ‘store’ was printed out. And on floor 14, ‘restaurant’ could be read.

Zhao Hai looked at the elevator panel and saw that there were 110 floors altogether. Ten of which were used as classrooms, another ten were for dormitories, and five for the library. There were even some floors allocated as practice grounds, which made Zhao Hai somewhat confused.

But after recalling what Gu Mingyue said that the academy built like a small city, Zhao Hai began to understand. This practice ground wasn’t actually outdoors, it was just built inside the building. This way, they really had no way of going outside for a year.

Zhao Hai didn’t need to find the dormitory floor, Tinkle already took care of it. After the elevator doors opened, Tinkle led Zhao Hai out.

Zhao Hai was quite curious about the elevator. He felt that the elevator was much faster than he expected. Upon heading out of the elevator, they were met with an illustration showing the different blocks present in the floor. There was the calming block, clear block, silent block, and common block, a total of four regions.

Zhao Hai looked at the characters of the four regions and couldn’t help but murmur, “Clear and calming? Interesting.”

Seeing Zhao Hai stop, Tinkle stopped as well. Zhao Hai turned to Tinkle and said, “Tinkle, which block do we live in?”

Tinkle quickly answered, “Young Master, we live in the clear block. Please follow me.” Zhao Hai nodded as Tinkle led him in. Tinkle turned corners about seven or eight times. Zhao Hai didn’t expect this place to be huge, there might be dozens of rooms on this floor alone.

Tinkle brought Zhao Hai to a room that had the number ‘13’ on it. Then he turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Young Master, we’re here. You can open the door using your ID card.”

Zhao Hai nodded and took his ID card out before inserting it on a hole beside the door. A ‘ding’ was heard before the door opened for Zhao Hai and Tinkle to enter.

Zhao Hai took a deep breath before entering his room. He inspected the place and estimated it to be about 50 square meters. But this was already pretty good. After entering the door, he was met with the small living room. On the living room was a set of sofas and a television. The living room and the bedroom wasn’t partitioned by walls, instead a shelf was used to divide the two. On the shelf were a few decorations such as figurines of cars and other things.

The bedroom was also simple. Besides the bed, closet, and a cabinet, there were no other things inside. Next to the living room was another room. Upon entering, Zhao Hai saw a set of sanitary items inside. It seems like this was the bathroom. There was also another room right next to the living room. Zhao Hai looked in and there was a chair and a table as well as some shelves with books on them. It was the study.

Although his living quarters was quite small, it was fully equipped. This place was really well-made.

After his simple exploration, TInkle introduced Zhao Hai to the facilities built into the room. There weren’t really a lot of advanced things in this room aside from a computer connected to a wide network. For someone who used the internet a lot in his past life, this computer was already good for Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai explored the room a few times before he returned to the study and scanned through some books. Sure enough, these books had relatively simple contents. Most of them were about the Machine Field. Naturally, the books were specially prepared for ascenders from the lower realms. It was also possible to know about these by using the computer. But since most of the ascenders didn’t know how to use computers, they could only place the books here.

Since this room was present, Zhao Hai wasn’t too anxious about understanding the Machine Field. He could just read them anytime. What he needed to do now was to gain an understanding of the academy.

Zhao Hai turned to Tinkle and said, “Tinkle, lead to me to explore the classrooms, then we’ll head to the cafeteria.” Tinkle complied and brought Zhao Hai out of the room. Locking the door was very simple, it only took a press of a button in order to lock it. Moreover, the button identified the room’s owner by fingerprint. This way, other people wouldn’t be able to lock the room’s owner in his own room.

Tinkle proceeded to bring Zhao Hai to explore the classrooms. Upon seeing the rooms, Zhao Hai knew that they were different. The classrooms that ascenders entered in were pre-arranged. Inside each classroom was an instructor that would teach you. Then after a while, you would be tested. If you pass the test, you would proceed to another classroom. But that classroom didn’t have a living instructor inside, instead you would be taught by a robot.

Zhao Hai didn’t oppose to this arrangement. After that, Tinkle brough Zhao Hai to the cafeteria. Actually, the cafeteria wasn’t too far from the classrooms. This way, it was convenient for the students coming from their classes. Robots were specially assigned in this cafeteria in order to serve the students. The meals here were free but were fixed. In other words, if you don’t like the food, then you would have no choice but to eat it.

After visiting these places, Zhao Hai returned to his room. The stores as well as the other places could be delayed and visited at another time. After all, one couldn’t just understand everything in one go. The technology level of this place was more developed compared to earth. He needed to digest everything first.

When Tinkle and Zhao Hai returned to their room, Zhao Hai went to the bathroom and took a good bath. He also noticed a set of night clothes that was hung inside the cabinet. He changed into these night clothes before throwing his own clothes into the automatic washing machine. Tinkle can take care of these things, Zhao Hai didn’t need to do anything else.

Zhao Hai proceeded to the study, stopping himself from touching the computer. After arriving at the bookshelf, he took out a book introducing the Machine Field.

Zhao Hai slowly and calmly turned the pages of the book. However, deep inside, his heart wasn’t calm. This book didn’t only introduce basic things about the Machine Field, there were other things as well. He also understood how he came to ascend in this realm.

Mentioned in this book was the relationship between the Machine Field and Lu Wei’s Cultivation Realm. The two were like the Mage Continent and the Magic Armor Continent of the Atlanta Plane.

However, the distance between the Machine Field and the Cultivation Realm wasn’t just an ocean, but a huge span of void!

There were more than 1,200 planets that can be inhabited in the Machine Field. But there were a lot more planets in the Cultivation Realm, about 10 thousand. Also, the two places weren’t peaceful, they were hostile to each other.

The reason the Machine Realm was called as such was because it was not only an advanced Mechanical Civilization, it was also very adept in magic formations.

Back in the Underworld, Zhao Hai discovered that magic formations and the Cultivation Realm’s Arrays were completely different systems. Zhao Hai thought that after reaching a very deep realm in magic formations, one would arrive at magic arrays. But afterwards he discovered his mistake. Magic formations and arrays work with two completely different laws. In the Machine Field, magic formations were developed to an extreme level. Arrays used in the Cultivation World were completely different from these magic formations.

It can be said that the Machine Field was supported by two major systems, the mechanical system as well as the magic formation system. This was the reason why it was called the Machine Field.

Besides the Machine Field and the Cultivation Realm, there was also the Devil Realm, Spirit Realm, Monster Realm, Elven Realm, and the other smaller groups. They were the influences in this world. Moreover, these realms weren’t spread out in one plane. This plane was composed of countless big and small planes connected to each other by transmission formations.

After reading the book, Zhao Hai began to understand that these groups of small and big planes composed this extremely huge entity. It can be said that they composed the very massive World of Cultivation!

Chapter 1077: A Splendid World

Zhao Hai’s mind was completely glued to the book. Under the book’s guidance, the enormous World of Cultivation slowly unraveled before Zhao Hai’s mind.

It was an incomparably mysterious world. Moreover, it was different than the novels that Zhao Hai had read before. Back then, people from the Cultivation Realm would be riding their swords as they flew in all directions. But this wasn’t the case here, the technology of this world was very developed. People could still ride their flying swords, of course, but if they want to hurry then they would be using something else. They would either use transmission formations or some vehicles.

The World of Cultivation was also very dangerous. Even powerful cultivators would find themselves in danger at any time. If they fly using their swords all the time, then they would need to keep providing energy. If their enemy knew about what they were doing and then used a transmission formation ahead of time, then the cultivator would be fighting with a deficit in energy. The end result of this wouldn’t be good for the cultivator. Therefore, cultivators who wanted to hurry along would just use cars and other transportation vehicles rather than waste their energy in flying by themselves.

It was just like how a normal human would ride buses when going long distances. Who in their right mind would jog from city to city? The same principle applies in the World of Cultivation.

But Zhao Hai also understood that the level of technology between places differ. It can be said that the science and technology in this world wasn’t purely mechanical. Instead, technology would be the base and then other aspects would be added to it.

Take the Machine Field for example, their mechanical technology was unified with magic formations, creating a unique civilization. But the mechanical technology in the Machine Realm was only a partial part of their civilization, magic formations was also added to it.

On the other hand, in the Cultivation Realm, cultivators give cultivation priority. Because of this, their usage of technology was entirely different.

While the Machine Field had fast cars, mechs, and battleships, the Cultivation Realm was still left with the cultivators themselves equipped with magic artifacts.

But currently speaking, the Cultivation Realm’s civilization was much better than the Machine Field. Although the Machine Field had powerful battleships, these battleships still fall short compared to the Cultivation Realm’s magic artifacts.

Besides the Machine Field and the Cultivation Realm, there was still the Devil Realm, Monster Realm, Spirit Realm, and the Elven Realm!

The entire World of Cultivation was mainly composed of these six powers. They were situated at the middle of the world, becoming its central powers.

There were other powers in the World of Cultivation as well, but these weren’t as huge and as powerful as the Cultivation Realm and the others. However, these powers still held influence in their respective territories. And with the central powers being hostile to each other, they were able to survive up to now.

Although these six central powers were in a hostile relationship, this didn’t mean that they didn’t communicate with each other. There were transmission formations connecting their territories. At this time, the six were cautious about fighting lest they risk the lives of the innocent. Because of this, on the surface, the six powers were maintaining peace.

Although peace was needed to maintain trade, this didn’t mean that small skirmishes had stopped.

Naturally, these small battles were left unrecorded. However, Zhao Hai had experienced quite a lot of things, so from reading the book, he knew that these battles were constantly happening.

After reading, Zhao Hai understood that the Ark Continent belonged to the Divine Realm that was controlled by the Cultivation Realm. Meanwhile, the Atlanta Plane was under the Machine Field’s control. Although the place he ascended was different, he still ascended into a common major plane, the World of Cultivation.

In addition to Zhao Hai’s fast reading speed, the introductory book was also quite short. So in just a breath of time, Zhao Hai was done. After reading the book, Zhao Hai let out a long breath before his eyes lit up with sparkling light.

He didn’t expect to end up in such a splendid world. This world had battles between battleships and immortal cultivators. And battles between monsters and men was somewhat common. Compared to this huge World of Cultivation, the Ark Continent, Atlanta Plane, Divine Realm, and the Underworld just couldn’t catch up.

Zhao Hai let out another breath as he returned to his usual mood. Then he turned to Tinkle and said, “Tinkle, what’s my schedule for tomorrow?”

Tinkle nodded and said, “Young Master, you have a class tomorrow at room 1. There, you will receive basic ascender briefing.”

Zhao Hai gave a nod, then he said, “Can I go to the cafeteria to eat now?”

Tinkle replied, “You can, Young Master. As long as you present your ID Card, the cafeteria will prepare a meal for you to eat.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Good, then let’s eat. Right, Tinkle, what energy do you need? Do you need to consume anything?”

Tinkle said, “Young Master, this Tinkle doesn’t need to eat anything. I could just charge myself every evening. There’s no need for you to worry.”

Zhao Hao nodded. To be honest, he didn’t expect Tinkle to sustain itself by charging. He expected the robot to have a huge battery, allowing him to maintain its function for many years. Who would’ve thought that the Robot Butler would charge itself every night.

Zhao Hai proceeded to wear his Mage Robe. Naturally, this robe was a transformed version of Zhao Hai’s battle suit. Of course, he wouldn’t transform his clothes under anyone’s gaze, or else people will start to suspect.

Although Gu Mingyue didn’t say much, Zhao Hai was able to hear a lot of things from his words. A lot of ascenders from the lower realms use spatial equipment, so the academy shouldn’t be suspicious about him having one. But if he had two or more things that shouldn’t be in a lower realm, then the academy might not let him off easily.

Upon wearing his Mage Robe, Zhao Hai went out of his room along with Tinkle. As the two were walking, Zhao Hai turned to Tinkle and said, “Tinkle, how long will one charge last? Once I leave the academy and explore the world, wouldn’t it be troublesome if you just suddenly lose power?”

Tinkle replied, “Young Master, I’m a Robot Butler, so it’s impossible for me to be far from home. If Young Master brings me along inside a car, then I can charge using the vehicle. If Young Master wants to take me to a place with no electricity, then you might as well leave me behind. I can maintain two days of work with one charge. I also have a spare battery inside my body, allowing me to work for a total of five days. I will be completely drained after five days.”

Zhao Hai nodded, it seems like Tinkle was just a normal home robot. With this information, it seems like robots were inferior to Undead.

When he thought about this, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but pause. Then he tapped his head. He forgot that he revealed that he was an all-element mage yesterday. This means that nobody would suspect him if he had an Undead helping him with his matters.

After thinking about this, Zhao Hai immediately turned to Tinkle and said, “Tinkle, I’m an All-element Mage. Will the Academy allow me to summon my Undead?”

Tinkle quickly replied, “It is allowed, but you can’t summon a lot. Common ascenders can summon at most five Undead to work for them.”

Zhao Hai nodded, the actually didn’t expect the Academy to permit this action. But after hearing the answer, he suddenly thought about another matter, Faith power.

Using Undead meant using Dark Energy as well. If the Machine Field was like the Divine Realm, then they might suppress Dark Mages. That wouldn’t be good.

However, this matter wasn’t something that Tinkle could answer. Zhao Hai could just delay this matter and find the right time to ask the instructor tomorrow.

The two entered the elevator and before long they arrived at the cafeteria. The academy’s cafeteria was very huge. The academy’s classrooms occupied ten floors, and there was a cafeteria on each floor. Since Zhao Hai was having his classes on the first floor, he could only go to the first floor cafeteria.

The first floor was where the most recent ascenders go to. They were all Mages, but since they came from different places, they each have their own differences.

Just like Zhao Hai who ascended while still young, there were also talents from other planes that ascended at an early age. Naturally, there were also less talented people who ascended late into their lives. One could see a person’s talent from this point. After all, one cannot hide their age.

Each floor’s cafeteria could accommodate 200 people at the same time. But from the day the academy was established, the cafeteria had never been full. Aside from those wise old men, there were young ascenders that were used to the life in their previous plane where each of their needs were being fulfilled. And since meals in the cafeteria were just ordinary, how could these people eat it? Because of this, those young ascenders would exchange their lower realm coins for machine coins. After that, they would go to the restaurant and have their meals there.

When Zhao Hai and Tinkle entered the first floor cafeteria, they saw several people already inside. These people were in Mage Robes. Most of them were quite old, with white beards and hair.

These Old Mages quietly ate their ordinary meals. Their quiet attitude made the cafeteria quite a spiritless place.

Looking at these Old Mages, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but sigh inside. He can understand the mood of these Old Mages. They took great pains cultivating their entire life in order to ascend and be treated as deities. But after they ascended, they actually discovered that they weren’t treated as deities. Instead, they arrived at an advanced society that didn’t look at them as anything special. Faced with this situation, the attack on their spirits would surely be enormous.

Zhao Hai also noted Robot Butlers beside these Old Mages. Moreover, their robots had the same model as Tinkle. There were only a few advanced looking Robot Butlers.

Although these Old Mages were quietly eating, they were still aware of their surroundings. Seeing newcomers coming in, they couldn’t help but look at the entrance. Upon doing so, they couldn’t help but stare. They didn’t expect a young man like Zhao Hai to come to the cafeteria. Moreover, this was someone they haven’t seen before.

However, they quickly changed their mind after they understood. This was definitely a new ascender. After that, they didn’t care about Zhao Hai anymore as they proceeded to face their food.

Zhao Hai understood the moods of these Old Mages. These Old Mage discovered that they didn’t ascend to a holy place. Moreover, they were old, so improving their strength would be very difficult. Because of this, they didn’t spend their money extravagantly. Instead, they saved their money so that when they leave the academy, they could use this money in order to live their remaining years in happiness.

Zhao Hai lightly sighed when he thought about these Old Mages. Moreover, he didn’t think that these Old Mages were not talented. After all, they were still able to ascend, this meant that they had potential. Moreover, after living in the Lower Realms for many years, they surely had a lot of accumulated wisdom. And sometimes, wisdom was the most precious thing one could have.

Zhao Hai never looked down on these old people. As he stood at the cafeteria’s entrance, he looked around the cafeteria before greeting the Old Mages close by, “Hello, I’m Zhao Hai. I just ascended here from the Atlanta Plane. I hope you can take care of me from now on.”

The Old Mages didn’t expect Zhao Hai to take the initiative to talk to them. Moreover, he was so polite. One must know that the other young ascenders would just arrogantly look at them before snorting. It was as though they had grown eyes on their foreheads. And now, there was this unfamiliar young man being polite to them.

After seeing that the Old Mages weren’t replying, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile faintly as he added, “Everyone here is an ascender from the lower realms. It can be said that we came from the same place. The only thing different between us is our age. Other than that, we are the same group. I hope that we can help each other. After all, the Machine Field is a very strange place for us.”

The Old Mages stared at Zhao Hai. It took a while before someone spoke out. After some time, an Old Mage stood up and courteously bowed, “I’ve seen Mister Zhao Hai. This one is Dins from the Ole Plane.”

Chapter 1078: Ashley Clan

Being ascenders from the lower realms, these people certainly weren’t simple characters. And for these Old Mages to ascend, it only meant that they were somewhat geniuses among their people. It was only a pity that they were already old when they ascended. This caused their future development to be filled with challenges.

But at the same time, these Old Mages were people who achieved the peak of their realms. And it was impossible for their hands to not be stained with blood. Because of this, their mental states would surely be very solid.

It was only because they had ascended to the Machine Field that these Old Mages began to feel temporarily dejected. In the future, they would just casually find a place and live a countryside lifestyle.

Zhao Hai’s words were a faint proposal for an alliance. These Old Mages were wizened individuals. Therefore, they were able to read Zhao Hai’s intention from his words.

All of them came from the lower realms. Although they had been received well after ascending to the Machine Field, this didn’t mean that they would be treated well in the future. Perhaps the people from the Machine Field would treat them as cannon fodder in future battles. These Old Mages didn’t have Zhao Hai’s Space. Because of this, they had no means to decline arrangements from the Machine Realm. In this case, it’s quite possible for them to meet miserable ends.

But if they unite, then the situation would be different. Of course. their alliance doesn’t have the means to contend against the entire Machine Field, but if they band together, they wouldn’t be abused in the future. There were gangs who lived long lives because of this principle.

These Old Mages were still outstanding individuals, they were only demoralized at this time because of their status as well as the fact that they were plunged into a strange world. Upon hearing Zhao Hai’s words, these Old Mages immediately introduced themselves. But in the entire cafetaria, there were only 15 Old Mages present.

After the Old Mages introduced themselves, Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Grandmasters, this young one has just ascended, so I basically know nothing. I’m just like you. I hope that we can mutually support each other in the future.”

These Mages naturally complied as they smiled. Zhao Hai promptly went to the robots in order to get his meal before gathering together with the old men.

The food wasn’t phenomenal and there wasn’t any liquor. Additionally, the  room that was built for 200 people was only occupied by a few people, making it very desolate. But despite this, the spiritless atmosphere of the room had vanished.

Zhao Hai knew that with Tinkle present, this matter would certainly be known to many people. However, he wasn’t worried because there were only a dozen or so people. It was impossible for them to threaten the Machine Field. He was also doing this in order to catch the attention of the major forces.

Zhao Hai believed that no matter where, a force that wants to grow and develop would always need a lot of talents. And it was quite appropriate to say that Zhao Hai was such a talent.

And what just happened was indeed like what Zhao Hai thought. What Zhao Hai did today has been noted by the various powers from the Machine Field. Those who didn’t get a video would get a printed report.

And a Dark Mage Clan, the Ashley Clan, was one of them. The Ashley Clan was quite famous in the Machine Field. And Clans of Dark Mages were quite unique.

In the World of Cultivation, the six influence weren’t only hostile to each other. Besides the six, there were also enemies that they needed to defend against. These were some malicious ghosts produced by extreme lands or powerful magic beats.

Up until now, nobody could explain exactly how malicious ghosts came into being. Some said that they were souls of people who had grievances when they died. Upon death, their souls slowly absorbed resentment before forming into malicious ghosts. This theory was also deemed as the closest one to the truth. Aside from these resentful souls, special conditions also needed to be met. It was just like in the Underworld where dark energy was strong, eventually producing Undead.

These malicious ghosts or powerful magic beasts pose threats to the Machine Field as well. In order to live peacefully, these enemies needed to be dealt with. Normally, this work would be managed by Mages or Warriors. Therefore, Mages and Warriors would take care of it in the Machine Realm.

There were plenty of churches in the Machine Field. Naturally, churches didn’t only belong to light element Mages. Each Mage group had their own church. In addition to this, there were also aristocratic families with Mage or Warrior lineage. These families had their own unique magic or martial skill. After developing for many years, they were able to slowly influence the realm.

However, there were only three powers that really held major influence in the Machine Field. The first power was the Church Alliance. This alliance was composed of Mages. The high-ranks of the Alliance were almost made out of Mages. Their main objective was to train and take in Mages. In the Magic Field, the Church Alliance doesn’t only composed of various churches. They also take in other Mage groups into their fold.

The second power was the Martial Arts Assembly. Similar to the Church Alliance, the Assembly was composed of Warriors. They opened this assembly in order to take in Warriors who ascended in the Machine Realm. Naturally, Warrior Clans would become members of this assembly.

The third power was the Machine Field Army. It can be said that the Machine Field Army was the largest force in the realm. Since it was an army, it had battleships, mechs, Mages, and Warriors among their members. They were the most powerful fighting force in the Machine Field.

If the Machine Field was the country, then the Machine Field Army would be the country’s regular troops. Meanwhile, the Church Alliance and the Martial Arts Assembly would be forces that were recognized by the government. These two powers had complicated relations to the government, but they had certain influence in the overall governance of the realm.

The Church Alliance and the Martial Arts also had their own battleships and mech battalion. However, their quantity and quality was lower compared to the Machine Field Army. And in the Machine Field Army, the strongest divisions were the battleships and the mechs, never the Warrior and Mage divisions.

The Ashley Clan was one of the members of the Church Alliance. They were a famous Dark Mage Clan, and they had 100 members working inside the Alliance.

One shouldn’t underestimate these 100 people. One must know that the Machine Field only had a bit more than 1,000 administrative positions in the government. These positions would be divided by the three major powers. The Ashley Clan holding 100 of these positions meant that they had terrifying strength.

The place where Zhao Hai was at now was the Ashey Clan’s domain. In the Machine Realm, there were also a lot of places where ascenders end up. Zhao Hai was just someone who happen to ascend in the Ashley Clan’s domain.

Since the Ashely Clan was a Mage Clan, naturally they had a special fondness regarding Mages. This was especially true for Mage ascendants. The Ashley Clan attached great importance to people from the lower realms because the Ashley Clan’s founding patriarch was an ascender himself.

Zhao Hai’s actions have been sent to the Ashley Clan’s external hall manager. This manager was also a Dark Mage. He sat there with his black robe. But unlike most thin Dark Mages, this manager was fat. He was 1.9m tall and should be about 300jin(150kg). He had brown hair and silver gray eyes. But he didn’t have the honest and simple look of a conventional fatty. Instead, his face looked ferocious, not something a good person would have at all.

Currently on the manager’s table was a recording of Zhao Hai’s actions. A middle-aged person stood in front of him. This person had a normal nose and was also wearing a mage robe. However, aside from his eyes and his robes, there was nothing noteworthy about the man.

This person was respectfully standing opposite the fat manager. One wouldn’t want to take a heavy breath with the atmosphere inside the room.

Zhao Hai didn’t do a lot of things in the two days that he had been here. Moreover, the recording didn’t show everything that Zhao Hai did. All the irrelevant parts were cut out, only the valuable recordings were kept in.

As soon as the video had finished playing, the fat manager looked up at the middle-aged man and said, “This one is interesting. He didn’t have any arrogance despite being an ascender. Moreover, he’s quite good at communication. He’s also talented.”

The middle-aged person bowed and said, “He is. This Zhao Hai has been assigned to room 2046. He also gave the receptionist a gift as thanks. Then he united the Old Mages into an alliance. We could see his talent in these actions. Because of that, I recommend him to Manager. Manager, our Bone Symbol Camp has slowly lagged behind our other battalions. We should attract more talents to this clamp.”

The fat manager nodded before he sighed and said, “Our Bone Symbol Camp is the first battalion of the external hall. But it is precisely because of this status that they always get the most dangerous missions. Additionally, our Bone Symbol Camp could only be replenished if there are deaths. This caused the Bone Symbol Camp to hold too few ascenders. I hope this Zhao Hai can be a gift to the camp.”

Despite his ugly and ferocious face, the manager’s voice was actually peaceful. It made people have a favorable impression of him. One couldn’t even associate his voice with his face.

Chapter 1079: The Fat Manager’s Attention

As soon as the middle-aged man heard the fat manager, he also couldn’t help but sigh, “Manager, this is because your heart is just too soft. If you let our members get eliminated, then the Bone Symbol Camp wouldn’t decline.”

The middle-aged man knew the fat manager’s temperament fully well. One shouldn’t look at the manager’s ugly and ferocious face. Contrary to what he looks like, the fat manager was actually a tenderhearted person. Moreover, he was friendly to all of his subordinates. It was also because of this that the middle-aged man dared to talk like this to the manager.

The fat manager looked at the middle-aged man’s eyes and sighed, “Tao Wang, you don’t understand. Our Ashley family is one of the top forces in the Church Alliance, this also means that the pressure on us is huge.There are a lot of talents and we aren’t really sure who and what abilities they have. Because of this, there are some talents in the family that wouldn’t be able to play to their own strength. If they did, then they would provide huge help for the family.”

“At this point, the family only looks for people who can fight. No matter who it is, as long as they are taken in, they would be sent to the outer hall in order to undergo a smelting trial inside the camps. A lot of people die during this time because they aren’t good at fighting. Talented people dying an undeserved death is truly a waste.”

“This is especially true for the lower realm ascenders. All of them are surely geniuses of their generation. And when they arrive in the Machine Field, they are treated with great importance. The ones most attracted to this attention are the young men. They ascended from the lower realms at a young age, so each one of them are arrogant. But there would only be a few of them who would integrate with the Machine Field and fully mature. And as for those older ascendants, they aren’t looked at with the same level of importance. Nobody wanted them. But they are also from the lower realms, so their talents are pretty good as well. Additionally, they have practiced for a long time, so they are experienced when it comes to fights. If we give them enough time, then their achievements would be higher than those young ascenders. It is just a pity that nobody sees this point right now.”

“This method of elimination might truly unearth talents, but the yields are too low. I remember someone mentioning this saying before, ‘a silly servant is useful, but a good servant is rare.’ But not many people remember this saying. All of them are just anxious in looking for benefits. They aren’t thinking far into the future!”

Despite his looks, the fat manager considers this matter differently compared to the other people. His word indicated how tenderhearted he was. He was much better compared to those who just look at weak people as prey.

Tao Wang looked at the fat manager and said, “Manager, so what do we do about Zhao Hai now?”

The fat manager thought about it for a moment before he said, “We won’t monitor him too much. Look for an opportunity to remove his robot’s internal surveillance system. We should get on good terms with a person like that. In order to avoid any mishaps in the future, we’ll stop spying on him. Let’s just observe his character from now on.”

Tao Wang nodded, “Alright, Manager can rest assured. I know what to do.”

The fat manager nodded, “Go, make sure to observe Zhao Hai’s actions. If there are other people who come in contact with Zhao Hai, don’t be polite to them. Make sure that they don’t get control over our ascendants.”

Tao Wang nodded. Then he said, “Manager, what if Zhao Hai is challenged inside the school? There are those who’ve almost done one year. Those guys have entered other camps. I’m afraid they would be instigated to challenge Zhao Hai.”

The fat manager sighed, “Looking at his actions, I reckon Zhao Hai isn’t a simple character. If he is unable to survive a challenge like that, then he wouldn’t be a huge help even if he enters our camp. And don’t forget that challenges in the academy only goes through if the challenged party accepts. We can see Zhao Hai’s character from this point. Right, also look for opportunities to recruit those old mages from the advanced classes.”

Tao Wang nodded before he turned around and leaving. The fat manager opened the video once more, after looking at Zhao Hai for some time, he muttered, “He’s really a talented person. I hope that he’ll become a blessing to my Bone Symbol Camp.”

Even if the other forces were aware of Zhao Hai, they couldn’t do anything. After all, this was the Ashley Family’s domain. The Ashely family wasn’t a group that could be underestimated. Although they weren’t a top force in the Machine Field, the power they held wasn’t small. Just for a single ascender, offending a force like the Ashley Family wasn’t worth it at all. Additionally, each influence had their own training academies. They had no shortage of geniuses like Zhao Hai.

However, the other camps of the Ashley family don’t have the same mindset. The Bone Symbol Camp might be powerful in the past, but now it was in decline. And now that there was a talent appearing in the Bone Symbol Camp’s area, how could these people let him off? These people would certainly make a move.

Although Zhao Hai knew that he would be getting attention, he was unaware of how big the focus on him was. In his mind, he was just an ordinary ascendant. How could he cause waves in the Machine Field?

But how could Zhao Hai know that he was already attracting attention the moment he entered room 2046? The matters he did from them on were brought into the attention of many powers.

After eating his meal with the Old Mages, Zhao Hai returned to his room. Then he entered the study and had Tinkle teach him how to use the computer.

The computer here was much more advanced than the ones on Earth. Although the computer itself was also placed on top of the table. But when it was used, it would retract into the table, allowing the use of the entire table as a workspace. One could directly use their hand in order to explore the computer. There were voice commands as well.

Naturally, this computer was better than the one Zhao Hai used before. And in order to improve the user experience, the table can also be moved up, allowing the user to stand up. It was manufactured in order to provide convenience to its users.

Zhao Hai didn’t feel strange as he used the computer. Although there were a lot of changes on it, the core principle was still the same. It didn’t take long before Zhao Hai was confident in using it.

Before long, Zhao Hai was using the computer. After that, he entered a few websites and read news from there.

There was no need to say whether Zhao Hai was able to understand the interface of these news sites. Zhao Hai absorbed news about the Machine Field nonstop. It was only until late at night that he began to sleep. But with his current level, there simply was no need for him to sleep. He just rested because of habit. It didn’t take long before Tinkle woke him up.

Zhao Hai arranged for Tinkle to wake him up every 7 o’clock in the morning. After he woke up, Zhao Hai would clean himself before sitting in the study and drinking two cups of tea. Then after reading for a while, he would proceed to the cafeteria to have a meal. After his breakfast, he would then go towards the classroom.

Zhao Hai already asked Tinkle and knew that there was no time limit in the cafeteria. You can eat whenever you want. Even if you ate at ten, the robots would still serve the same meal to you.

He was already done with scouring the net for news. So after he washed up, Zhao Hai sat in the study room and drank tea while reading a book. There were a lot of books inside the study. Some of these books were introductions about the six powers, some were history books, and there were also books about ascending to the Machine Field. Understanding these things was very important for Zhao Hai.

At about 8 o’clock, Zhao Hai put his book down and then went to the first classroom floor cafeteria alongside Tinkle. The Old Mages were also eating inside. Ever since meeting Zhao Hai yesterday, the Old Mages began to look into their own situations. In addition to their advantage in age compared to the young ones, they were also aware of their advantage in wisdom. At the same time, they also recognized that they too were peak experts in their own generations. They were demoralized in the past because they had just arrived at a strange place that wasn’t in their expectations. Now that they looked into themselves, they began to feel better. Their relationship with each other had improved as well.

In the past, when they woke up in the morning, they would just hole up in their rooms reading. Then they would go to the cafeteria to silently eat their meals before heading to class. Most of the time, they wouldn’t talk to one another.

But today was different. The cafeteria had become a small meeting place. These old people were now chatting as they ate their food. Even those who finished eating stayed around as they drank tea.

This tea was also one of the academy’s free services. Everyone in the room had their pipes, releasing smoke from their nose as they took sips from their teacup. It was just a pity that there was no liquor.

After seeing Zhao Hai arrive, the old men immediately offered him a seat. Zhao Hai returned their greetings before sitting down. Tinkle would get his meal from the kitchen so there was no need to worry about that.

After Zhao Hai sat down, Dins looked at him and said, “Little Hai, have you used the computer yet?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “I’ve used it. That thing is really convenient. It’s more convenient than books. If you want to look something up, you can do it immediately.”

Dins laughed and said, “It’s indeed good. Right, how was your first night?”

Zhao Hai replied, “I forgot the time, so I rested very late.”

The other Old Mages laughed. They knew what Zhao Hai was talking about, they experienced it themselves. One of the Old Mages named Barlett looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, you need to control yourself. Otherwise, you would easily get addicted.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Rest assured, I know. I can control myself.”

Berlett nodded, then he added, “Since it’s your first day, you will have someone provide you with independent counselling. You only have the entire morning as class, you can rest in the afternoon. Since that is the case, how about everyone exchange for some machine coins so that we can go to the restaurant? It’s been a while since I’ve drank some liquor.”

Chapter 1080: Rune Study

Although Barlett was old, his character was very straightforward. His stature was tall and strong. If he didn’t have his Mage Robe, then people might think that he was a Warrior.

The other Mages agreed with Barlett’s proposal. When they were in the lower realms, they were figures at the top of countless people. And ever since they ascended, they were very depressed. Now that the negative feeling has been eliminated, its time for them to go out and explore the other luxuries of the academy.

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Good, I also want to go outside and take a look. But I think there’s no need for everybody to take your gold coins out since I have a lot more than you. How about I treat you all ?”

When the old Mages heard Zhao Hai, they couldn’t help but stare. Dins turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, it looks like you aren’t bluffing. Just how much gold coins did you bring? Don’t you use bank cards or something like that?”

These old Mages were naturally rich people back in the lower realm. But they use bank cards, causing them to only bring a small amount of gold coins. Most of their wealth were in bank cards or things that were similar.

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Of course we also have banks. But I’m used to carrying a lot of gold coins with me. Naturally, this also includes silver and copper coins. I’m not only a Mage, I’m also a Merchant.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, the Old Mages laughed. Then Dins said, “I didn’t expect this youngster to be rich and powerful. Good, good. Then today is your treat. When the time comes, you better not ask us to contribute for the bill.”

Zhao Hai laughed as well as he said, “Rest assured, I’ll take care of it. I’ll go to the classroom first. After class, we’ll share a meal together.”

Dins and the others nodded. Then the group stood up and proceeded to their own classrooms. Since it was Zhao Hai’s first day, he would be going to a special room where an instructor would personally meet him.

Zhao Hai had Tinkle guide him to his classroom. There was no need to take care of their eating utensils, the cafeteria’s robots would deal with them.

Unlike its title, Zhao Hai’s classroom wasn’t anything special. It only had an electronic sign saying Room 2. But Zhao Hai didn’t care. In any case, with Tinkle with him, he would not worry about which classroom to go every day.

Upon entering Room 2, Zhao Hai saw that the inside was very spacious. Too spacious in fact that there wasn’t anything inside, even furniture.

Zhao Hai gawked. He saw the other classrooms yesterday, and all of them had furniture inside.

At this time, Tinkle suddenly said, “One set of furniture!” Just as his voice fell, a set of furniture emerged from the floor.

Zhao Hai stared, he didn’t expect it to be like this. He smiled faintly and said, “Alright, that’s convenient.” Then he proceeded to sit on the chair.

Not long after Zhao Hai took a seat, footsteps were heard from outside. Before long, the classroom’s door opened as a female Mage entered.

The female Mage looked young and had blonde hair. Although she looked old-fashioned, her black Mage robe was unable to hide her slender body.

Zhao Hai stared at the woman. He didn’t expect the teacher to be a beautiful woman, moreover she was a Dark Mage!

Zhao Hai hastily stood up. The beautiful woman sized Zhao Hai up before saying, “You are Zhao Hai?”

Zhao Hai bowed his head and said, “I am, are you my instructor?”

The female Mage nodded and said, “My name is Margaret, a Dark Mage. I will be your instructor for the rest of the year. You can look for me at any time.”

Zhao Hai stared, then he said, “Instructor Margaret, didn’t they say that the instructor would only be available for one month?”

Margaret looked at Zhao Hai and said, “No, I’m your instructor for the entire year. However, I will only teach you personally the first month. After that, robots will take over. But I’m still your instructor. If you have any difficulties, you can ask me directly.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “So that’s how it is. I’m sorry for troubling you.”

Margaret shook her head and said, “There’s no need to be polite. What I’m going to teach you aren’t things like the differences between the lower realm and the machine field. Those things can be found by asking the robots or using the computer. You can learn those at your leisure, so there’s no need to waste time on it. What I’ll be teaching you is the magic of the machine field. Our magic isn’t the same as the lower realms. Although the magic of the lower realms is formidable, they still fall short compared to the magic we use here. In the machine field, our magic is built upon the research of our seniors. After years of study, our magic formations, summoning magic, alchemy, and other disciplines have been fused together in order to form a new system of magic. If you want to survive here, then you need to learn our magic.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Alright.” Zhao Hai thought that he would be guided about how to live life in the machine field. Who would’ve thought that he would be instructed in magic?

What Zhao Hai didn’t know was the fact that Margaret wasn’t a common instructor. Moreover, Dins and the others didn’t have an instructor as special as her. It was only because Zhao Hai had potential that the academy specifically assigned a good instructor to train him.

In fact, in the academy, most instructors work part-time. There were only a few instructors present here due to the academy having very few students.

Margaret was one of these part-time instructors. However, she wasn’t just any other part-timer. She was from the Ashley Clan, sent by the Bone Symbol Camp in order to examine Zhao Hai ahead of time. And in addition, she was also here in order to tell people that the Bone Symbol Camp already had Zhao Hai in their sights. If anyone wanted to get in touch with Zhao Hai, then they would have to go through the camp.

Dins and the others didn’t have the same treatment. Their teachers were common part-timers. After teaching them for one month, these instructors would leave and would no longer manage them. And if other powers contact them, the Bone Symbol Camp wouldn’t get in the way.

The Bone Symbol Camp controlling an ascension point didn’t mean that they would recruit every ascender. This just meant that the Bone Symbol Camp had priority in choosing the ascenders they want. After they get their pick, the others would be free to choose their own.

Naturally, their pick could also be poached. If the other party was influential, then they could rob the ascender. After poaching a candidate, these people would then have their picking rights revoked.

Margaret looked at Zhao Hai, then she nodded and continued, “Lower realm magic generally involves incantations and hand gestures in order to cast the spell. If they want to make their spells more powerful, then Mages might use wands or staffs to do so. But this type of magic is limited. This is because they largely depend on the user’s spiritual force. How much spiritual qi can you use by only replying on your spiritual force? Only a small amount. Because of this, the might of the spells is small. This situation might be great in the lower realms since the energy present there is small.”

“However, this wouldn’t do well in the Machine Field. The density of spiritual qi here is at least a hundred times more than the lower realms. If you use the same method here, then that would be like using a small bowl in order to take water from a river. You’re wasting time as well as your source of water.”

“Because of this, seniors from the Machine Field studied through the years in order to invent the present magic system of the Machine Field, Magic Theory. It’s a system that unites magic and magic formations. Its might is very formidable.’

Margaret looked at Zhao Hai and saw that his expression was quite pensive. She couldn’t help but stare for a moment. Most people would be confused upon hearing such a theory. However, Zhao Hai seems to understand. This gave Margaret a surprise.

Margaret said, “Can you understand what I just said?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “I can understand some of it. Back in the Atlanta Plane, learning magic is basically cultivating spiritual force. Then we would use incantations and gestures in order to concentrate our spiritual force and communicate with the world’s energy. Then we use this energy in order to cast our spells. However, I’ve always thought that this method isn’t very convenient. A person’s mental strength is limited while there is a lot of energy available for use. Using your own spiritual force to come in contact with this vast amount of energy is very inefficient. I thought that maybe we can use magic formations in order to strengthen our spiritual force so that we can control more energy. It’s just that I haven’t grasped how to do it yet.”

Margaret’s eyes shone as he heard Zhao Hai. Then she said, “Correct, very good. The method you are thinking about is very hard to grasp. Because of this, our seniors studied for several hundred years. Their research slowly lead us to the creation of Magic Theory. It uses magic formations and spiritual force in order to communicate with spiritual qi, allowing our spells to gain more power.”

Zhao Hai gave a nod. Then Margaret added, “In order to study Magic Theory, you need to first learn about magic formations. Zhao Hai, have you studied magic formations before?”

Zhao Ha nodded, “I’ve dabbled in it. However, I didn’t give it priority. Because of that, I’m only able to learn simple formations.”

Margaret nodded, “After many years of development, the Machine Field already formed sets of theories regarding magic formations. It might look difficult at first, but it’s actually very simple. If you want to learn magic formations, then you would need to learn its basic framework as well as the runes. As long as you become familiar with these two, you can learn magic formations in a short time.”

Zhao Hai gawked for a moment before his eyes shone as he said, “Instructor, so you mean that you already broke down magic formations into frameworks and runes? Do you know what each rune signify?”

Margaret nodded, “Right. After years of study, the Machine Field managed to slowly break down every rune that can be used. In fact, the uses of these runes are fixed. The only thing that differentiates them are in where they are used. Putting it in an analogy, if a rune is a stroke, then magic formations are characters composed of these strokes. Although the strokes are fixed, using them in different characters meant that they had different meanings. This is the core of magic formation study.”

Zhao Hai’s eyes remained sparkling. He wasn’t able to think about this point. Magic formations play a huge role inside the Space.

Margaret looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Making magic formations using runes is only a fundamental skill in our magic system. Later on, you would need to make sets of magic formations in order to form a huge formation net. This net will produce more powerful results than individual magic formations. If magic formations are characters, then formation nets are words. As for what these words mean, then it would depend on the characters used to make them.”

Zhao Hai kept nodding. Looking at Zhao Hai’s reaction, Margaret couldn’t help but give a gentle nod. Then she knocked on the wall opposite Zhao Hai. The wall quickly turned into a screen. The screen was all white with nothing else on it.

Margaret’s hand swiped at the wall, making a row of runes appeared. Zhao Hai wasn’t ignorant about these symbols. This was because he saw them in magic formations. They were the most common symbols he had seen.

Margaret turned back to Zhao Hai and said, “One of the most difficult parts of magic formation study are runes. Currently, there have been as many as a hundred thousand symbols found. Moreover, as studies go further, more and more symbols would emerge. It would be impossible for a single person to remember more than 100 thousand runes. Because of this, most Mages would specialize on which department they would study runes in.”

Zhao Hai interjected, “Runes are also divided into different departments?”

Margaret nodded, then she said, “Correct. They are divided into nine types, metal, wood, water, fire, earth, light, dark, wind, and space. These nine departments comprised runes in our current system.”

Zhao Hai stared, he didn’t expect runes to be divided into nine departments. Moreover, the first departments refer to the five elements. Are runes somewhat related to the five elements?[1]

As he thought about this, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but frown as he said, “Instructor, is there metal element magic here? Why does the metal element have runes?”

* * *

The five elements refer to the Wu Xing(https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Wu_Xing)

Chapter 1081: Shops

Zhao Hai had a metal element divergent ability. However, he had no way to integrate this kind of ability into his own attacking system. He can use both martial arts and magic, but he can’t use his metal element in them. So as soon as he heard Margaret saying that runes were divided into nine major departments, of which the five elements were part of, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but ask.

Margaret looked at Zhao Hai. She also knew that the lower realms generally had no metal element magic. Because of this, she knew how to answer Zhao Hai’s question, “Correct,there is metal element magic here. Unlike the lack of metal element magic in the lower realms, the Machine Field was able to develop metal element magic by studying the Cultivation Realm’s five element energy.”

Zhao Hai nodded, it seems like the Machine Realm’s Magic Theory had absorbed some aspects of the cultivation realm’s spells. Then they slowly evolved their methods in order to arrive at their current state.

Actually, it can be said that in the World of Cultivation, most cultivation methods have aspects that tie them back to the Cultivation Realm. Take the Machine Field, for example, their two strongest means of attack were through battleships and magical mechas.

It was needless to say that battleships came up through studying the Cultivation Realm’s crafting techniques. After being baptized with magic formations, it became a weapon. But even if its might was formidable, it needed to be mentioned that it still fell short compared to the Cultivation Realm’s magic artifacts.

As for magical mechas, to put it bluntly, they were enlarged version of the Cultivation Realm’s golem techniques. And naturally, it wasn’t as good as the Cultivation Realm’s golem techniques. Golem techniques allow control over multiple golems. Moreover, when a golem was destroyed, the damage to the controller was limited. As for magical mechas, they are a combination between golem techniques as well as the Cultivation Realm’s armor refining techniques. Although its might wasn’t small, each pilot can only control one mecha. And when a mecha gets destroyed, the pilot would certainly die.

The machine field’s Magic Theory was also conceived with the same principle. It was partly based on the Cultivation Realm’s five elements. As for how they managed to extract that aspect, nobody knows.

Although Zhao Hai managed to figure these out, he didn’t say anything. Instead he just nodded. Margaret saw Zhao Hai’s understanding and then asked, “I heard that you’re an all-element Mage. Which rune department do you want to study?”

There was no need for Zhao Hai to think as he immediately answered, “Instructor, I want to study runes of the dark element. It would be best if they are related to summons.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Margaret’s eyes couldn’t help but shine. She was someone from the Ashley family, a heritage of Dark Mages. Naturally, she hoped that Zhao Hai would study dark element runes.

However, Zhao Hai has to decide which department he would study in. Even if Zhao Hai wanted to learn runes from other elements, the Ashley family would still take him in. The Ashely Family were a group of Dark Mages, but they would still recruit Mages from other departments. Otherwise, it would be impossible for the family to grow. It was only because the core members of the family were Dark Mages that they were titled as a Dark Mage family.

Margaret took a deep breath in order to calm her mood. Then she said, “Actually, if you want to progress with Magic Theory, you would need to learn all runes. It’s just unfortunate that there are too many runes in existence. Only a few could achieve such an endeavor. Magic formations with one element aren’t too strong. But if you fuse runes from two departments, their might would increase a lot. It’s not just a simple matter of adding one and one.”

Zhao Hai gave a nod. Then Margaret continued, “You certainly are familiar with dark element summoning magic. But in the Machine Field, in order to display its biggest strength, you would need to study dark element runes as well as space element runes. I’ll teach you dark element runes first. Then after a few days, we’ll tackle runes of the space element. Dark element summoning magic focuses mainly on dark element runes while space runes act as auxiliary.” Zhao Hao nodded once more. Margaret began to draw a symbol on the wall. Each stroke of the rune were clearly stated. The interpretation of the rune was also well detailed.

Although Zhao Hai just looked like he was listening, he was actually informing Cai’er to record everything. Not a single character should be missed. This was very important for their future.

Although he had Cai’er record the runes, this didn’t mean that Zhao Hai couldn’t understand them. Each rune might look simple, but a single change would have an impact on the rune. It was clear that the Machine Field’s understanding of these runes was beyond his imagination. The emergence of these runes was truly priceless in the use of magic formations.

The people inside Zhao Hai’s Space were also researching magic formations. However, compared to the Machine Field, they were still too far off. The people from the Machine Field researched for who knows how many years before coming up with Magic Theory. But in order to be an expert in this system, one needed to cross a certain threshold, studying magic runes. The reason why there were a lot of runes was because people would create new runes. Because of this, the number of runes wasn’t fixed. One could also study magic formations itself. However, it would be better if you created your own formation that suited your style. And in the process, creating a new rune was much easier than creating your own magic formation.

As he listened to Margaret’s lecture, Zhao Hai nodded. Creating new runes was just like inventing something new, nothing very special. However, creating a new magic formation was different. It was just like the difference between creating a new word and creating a new sentence.

What made Zhao Hai happy were Margaret’s words telling him that the runes could be found on the computer. This was absolutely good news for Zhao Hai.

Others might not remember all of the runes, but he can. He has the Space to do it for him. This was equal to Zhao Hai having the computing power of a computer.

Average people might remember all of the runes, however they would find it hard to use the most appropriate ones when necessary. It was just like how a person who knows how to write might not know how to write an article.

Although Zhao hai had learned a lot of runes, the time he spent doing so was actually a lot. It took about two hours for Margaret to introduce the runes. Margaret concluded the class at around 11 o’clock.

Zhao Hai expressed his gratitude before walking out of the classroom and heading towards the cafeteria. All this time, runes had occupied his head. He was itching to obtain those runes.

However, he also knew that he shouldn’t be too anxious about this matter. After waiting in the cafeteria for some time, Dins and the others arrived. Zhao Hai stood up as he was warmly greeted by the Old Mages.

Although Zhao Hai was young, these Old Mages were experienced in human interactions, so they didn’t dare to underestimate Zhao Hai. If not for Zhao Hai, they might still be depressed.

Zhao Hai hastily returned their greeting. After exchanging courtesies, Zhao Hai looked at Dins and the others and said, “Everyone. Why are you still on this floor? Couldn’t you request a transfer?”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Dins and the others couldn’t help but turn red. Each one of them had been dejected until recently. Because of this, they didn’t have the motivation to transfer floors. Moreover, they ascended earlier than Zhao Hai, so they shouldn’t be present on the first floor. When they heard Zhao Hai, they couldn’t help but feel embarrassed.

Zhao Hao looked at their reactions and knew what they were thinking. He didn’t laugh at them. They were in a poor condition, so laughing at their state was useless. Zhao Hai just gave a friendly chuckle as he said, “Tinkle, lead us to the store to have a look. Right, let’s look for a bank first.”

Tinkle replied, “Yes, Young Master. The shops and the bank are on the first floor of the academy. Please follow me.” Zhao Hai nodded and then turned to Dins and the others, “Today’s my treat. We’ll explore the shops to look. I’ll buy you anything you want. Sigh, it’s a pity I wasn’t able to go shopping with beautiful women. Instead, what I get is a group of old men. It’s unfair!” As soon as they heard Zhao Hai, Dins and the others felt their hearts warm up. But after a moment of staring, the group began to burst into laughter.

Dins looked at Zhao Hai and said, “You smelly brat. It’s your fortune to have us accompany you. What are you being sad about. Let’s go!” Zhao Hai chuckled before shaking his head. Then along with the smiling old men, Zhao Hai walked out of the cafeteria.

While the group was chatting, they quickly arrived at the elevator. This time, they rode one of the bigger elevators as they headed to the first floor.

When the elevators opened up, Zhao Hai saw two beautiful women in professional attire standing in the front. They were smiling as they said to the group, “Welcome, everyone!”

Zhao Hao nodded before inspecting the scenery ahead. Before him was a very large market with a lot of people inside. A large part of these people were staff. The staff weren’t wearing mage robes. Those who were wearing mage robes were ascenders who were buying stuff with their robots.

Zhao Hai didn’t bother the two women for long as he led the old men towards the market. This was also the first time for the old men, all of them couldn’t help but be absorbed by the atmosphere.

As the group were walking along, Zhao Ha inspected the shops. All of the things that Mages generally used were here. Some of the items offered were even beyond what Zhao Hai expected.

Chapter 1082: Crazy Dog

Magic in the lower realms and the Machine Field were completely different. Things in the lower realms weren’t necessarily useful in the Machine Field. Because of this, upon seeing all of these Mage equipment, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but frown.

The place was full of Mage equipment, from staffs, robes, potions, and even mage manuals. However, these things weren’t in line with what Zhao Hai learned about Magic Theory.

Magic Theory was very mystical, but its power stemmed from magic formations. Using the lower realm’s magic staff was definitely the wrong thing to do.

Because he knew about this, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but feel strange. Why would these shops display items that lower realm Mages use?

However, Zhao Hai was quick to understand why. When the old Mages saw these items, they were immediately excited. They quickly went to the shops and looked through the items displayed.

Looking at the expressions of these Old Mages, Zhao Hai understood that they had yet to understand the essence of Magic Theory. Because of this, they were still willing to buy these lower realm items in order to increase their strength.

In the lower realms, these people were the peak characters of their generation. Potions and staffs were useless to them. With their strength, nobody in the lower realms would dare fight them. Because of this, they didn’t have suitable items when they ascended.

But in the Machine Field, the importance of potions and magic staffs became apparent to them. Therefore, they wanted to buy some potions or a staff in order to increase their strength.

On the other hand, Zhao Hai was certain that these items would be useless. Magic Theory and ordinary magic were different. Later on when they learn more useful cultivation methods, they would find that these lower realm items that they thought to be useful were in fact very weak.

Zhao Hai arrived by Dins’ side as he smiled faintly and said, “You want to buy these things?”

Dins turned to Zhao Hai and forced a smile as he replied, “I was shortsighted before coming here in the Machine Field. I thought that unparalleled existences like me didn’t need any means to preserve my life.”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “Believe me, you don’t want to buy them. These things won’t help you progress in Magic Theory. The magic we studied and Magic Theory are completely different. At our current state, these things are useless. We should go to other shops and see if we can find special tools used by Mages in the Machine Field.”

Zhao Hai didn’t lower his voice not because he wasn’t afraid of offending people, he just didn’t see any staff around. On the other hand, the staff standing close by couldn’t help but look at him with shock.

Just like Zhao Hai said, the items sold here were useless for Machine Field Mages. The only reason these items were sold here was because ascenders had yet to have deep understanding about Magic Theory. If they did, then not only wouldn’t they buy these items, they would buy life preserving items instead.

Although this was the first time that the staff has seen Zhao Hai, she was actually very clear about people of the Bone Symbol Camp. This was Zhao Hai’s first day attending class. Having this deep understanding of Magic Theory on his first day was simply too astonishing.

Just before the staff could say anything, a cold snort was suddenly heard nearby. Then an arrogant sounding voice said, “If you couldn’t afford it, just say you couldn’t afford it. Do you really think that you have a deep understanding of Magic Theory?”

Zhao Hai and the others stared before all of them turned their heads to look at a young Mage standing close by. This young Mage seems to be between 20 to 30 years old. On his side was a robot butler. This butler was more advanced compared to Tinkle. Although this robot looked the same, one couldn’t hear any sound when it walked around. Moreover, it was more pleasing to look at than Tinkle as it resembled a person a little bit more.

The young Mage’s figure was symmetrical. He had a very white face, blonde hair, and a magnificent mage robe. Compared to the charming young man, Zhao Hai looked like a commoner. The arrogance on the young Mage’s face was akin to an emperor looking at a beggar.

Zhao Hai looked at the young man and frowned before asking, “Does Mister know us?”

The young man coldly snorted as he turned his head to Dins and the others and said, “Useless old bastards. Even if you managed to ascend, what can you really do? Right, why aren’t you hiding inside your rooms like you used to?”

Zhao Hai turned his head and looked at Dins and the others. The expression on the old men’s faces weren’t looking good. Zhao Hai turned his head back to the young man and said, “Mister, if you like these things, then why don’t you buy more? Or can it be that you lack money as well? Do you want me to buy you something too?”

As soon as they heard Zhao Hai, Dins and the others couldn’t help but gawk. And then each one of them laughed. They knew that it was impossible for Zhao Hai to treat this person. He was just teasing him.

When he heard Zhao Hai, the young man’s face paled, he retorted, “It’s useless to save your face. If you can’t afford it, then don’t talk nonsense. Do you really think that I would receive any charity from you?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Useless thing. Putting my good gesture to waste.” Then he turned to the old Mages and said, “Let’s go, I don’t want to fight a crazy dog.”

The young man’s eyes couldn’t help but blaze in anger when he heard Zhao Hai. However, Zhao Hai had the numerical advantage and the young Mage hadn’t ascended for long either. Additionally, the school forbade any unregistered fights, so he cannot make a move.

After that short intermission, Tinkle brought Zhao Hai to the bank. Upon entering, a robot immediately walked towards Zhao Hai and bowed, “Mister, welcome. What kind of transaction would you like to do?”

Zhao Hai looked at the robot and saw that it was just like those Robot Mages back then. It’s quite an advanced robot.

Zhao Hai immediately replied, “I want to exchange some gold coins for machine coins. Can you lead me there?”

The robot quickly said, “Mister, please follow me.” Then he brought Zhao Hai to a room nearby. There weren’t a lot of people inside the hall, but the ones present were doing basic transactions. Exchanging for machine coins wasn’t done inside the hall.

A person was waiting inside the room, this one was human and not a robot. He quickly stood up and greeted Zhao Hai, “Mister, welcome. I’m glad to be of service.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he turned his hand to retrieve a bag of gold coins with 1000 coins inside. He handed it to the person and said, “This is 1000 gold coins. Please exchange it for machine coins.”

Upon receiving the bag of gold coins, the man said, “Mister, please wait for a moment. Since the gold content of the lower realms’ coins aren’t the same, we need to test the coins first before we determine the exchange rate.”

Zhao Hai waved his hand. The man took the coins with him and left. Before long, the man came back as he bowed to Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, the gold content of your coins is very high. Each coin can be exchanged for 20 machine coins. Does Mister still want to go through with the transaction?”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he took his ID card out and said, “Please deposit the money.” Then he handed the card over to the man.

When he came out of the bank, Zhao Hai was now a rich young man with 30 thousand machine coins. Zhao Hai didn’t immediately go and buy items. Instead, he headed to the elevator and went to the restaurant along with Dins and the others.

There was no need to mention that the food of the Machine Field were very good. After eating, Zhao Hai and the others returned to the shops. But this time, they didn’t stay for a long time. They just bought some daily necessities before leaving.

Zhao Hai wasn’t in a hurry to buy items. Thing he needed to buy weren’t available on the first floor shops. The academy’s shops were also divided into floors. Those who have ascended for less than a month could only go to the first floor shops, they were still forbidden to head to the other floors.

Meanwhile, Dins and the others were very happy. The past several days, they had been holed up inside their rooms and had been dejected. Moreover, they failed to prepare items before they ascended, most of their possessions were left behind for their descendants or disciples. In their opinion, those things would have no use after they ascended. Also, if they failed their ascension, then their family members wouldn’t be able to use their items. Therefore, they didn’t bring anything. Unlike Zhao Hai, they were truly poor ascendants.

Zhao Hao returned to his own room. After placing the things he bought in a convenient place, he proceeded to wash himself before going back to the study. He began to read basic runes and their comprehensive explanations. Zhao Hai’s understanding of Machine Theory grew deeper. Even if he didn’t go to class, he could still manage with self-study.

But what Zhao Hai needed to do right now was to send all information about magic runes to the Space. These runes were important to the Space’s research into magic formations. Because of this, as he sat on the computer scanning through the various runes, he also instructed Cai’er to record everything down.

Chapter 1083: The Core of Magic Theory

When evening came, Zhao Hai had already saved all of the runes to the Space. While Cai’er went on to classify each one of them, Zhao Hai took a rest. The next day at exactly seven o’clock, he woke up, read a bit, ate his meal, and then proceeded to the classroom.

Not long after Zhao Hai entered the classroom, Margaret entered. Zhao Hai quickly stood up and gave his greetings, “Zhao Hai has seen Instructor.”

Margaret nodded, then she said, “Take a seat. I heard you had a conflict with Frey yesterday?”

Zhao Hai stared, he looked at Margaret with confusion. Then he said, “Is Frey that young man from the shop?”

Margaret nodded, “Correct. Frey is a young expert that ascended from the Spirit Wind Plane. The plane is quite a good one in the lower realms. It’s rich with spiritual qi, so quite a few people had ascended from there. Moreover, people from the Spirit Wind Plane are being especially cared for in the Machine Realm. Each one of them are arrogant. Since you offended Frey yesterday, people might look for you to cause trouble. There are already people from the Spirit Wind Plane that had become famous here. You should be more careful in the future.”

Zhao Hai gawked, then he smiled faintly and said, “Maybe I won’t be meeting any of that when I leave the academy. In any case, since I’ve offended him, I can’t do anything. Are the people from the Spirit Wind Plane domineering?”

Margaret sighed, “This time, you really made a mistake. The people from the Spirit Wind Plane are very domineering. Their pride didn’t only come from their origin, they also have a very close relationship with the Wind God Palace. Almost every ascender from the Spirit Wind Plane are Wind Element Mages and are very gifted in the wind element. Therefore, most of their ascenders gets recruited by the Wind God Palace. After you head back, make sure to read about the Wind God Palace. This way, you’ll know what you’re up against.”

Zhao Hai nodded, he gave Margaret a salute and said, “Thank you Instructor.”

Margaret looked at Zhao Hai and sighed, “Zhao Hai, you’re talented. However, there are a lot of talents like you in the Machine Realm. Before becoming true experts, nobody would treat you with real respect. A dead genius is a useless genius. You need to remember to protect yourself.”

Zhao Hai nodded. Margaret added, “The waters in the Machine Realm are much deeper. When you go back, make sure to read about the churches. I want you to be intelligent in your actions. After you exit the academy, you need to enter under the umbrella of a strong power. That way, you will be safer.”

Upon hearing Margaret, Zhao Hai’s heart couldn’t help but be moved. He wasn’t a fool, so he was clear about the darkness of this world. Therefore, when he heard Margaret, he immediately understood that Margaret was also from one of those strong influences.

Margaret didn’t express which power she was from. She just turned to Zhao Hai and said, “I won’t say anything else, you will understand them later on. Let’s proceed to studying magic formation runes. Did you remember anything we went through yesterday?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Instructor, I’ve already studied and remembered the runes from the dark element and the space element.”

Margaret couldn’t help but stare. Her expression changed as she made sure, “Remember? You memorized them?”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Yes instructor, I’ve memorized them all.”

Margaret looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Alright, since you memorized them all, I’ll give you a test. As long as you pass the test, we’ll begin studying Magic Theory. If you miss anything and are deceiving me, then you will be penalized.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Instructor, you can rest assured.”

Margaret nodded, then she went around Zhao Hai’s table and said, “Dark and space element tests.” As her voice fell, the table turned into a screen with test questions in them.

Zhao Hai didn’t say anything as he just nodded. Then he became absorbed in answering the questions on the screen. Actually, most of these questions were being answered by Cai’er. But since Cai’er was one with his mind, this was equivalent to answering it on his own. As soon as a question appeared, he was able to effortlessly answer them.

It took about half an hour before Zhao Hai was done answering all questions about dark and space element runes. Naturally, it was impossible for all the runes to be present, only a part of the runes appeared on the test. This was just a test to see Zhao Hai’s understanding about runes.

While Zhao Hai was answering the questions, Margaret was quietly watching by his side. To be honest, Zhao Hai’s ability exceeded her imagination. Moreover, it seems like Zhao Hai provided the correct answers to the questions. This gave here quite a shock.

She already looked highly upon Zhao Hai before, but now it seems like she was still underestimating him. Zhao Hai wasn’t just an ordinary genius, he was an extraordinary genius!

After waiting for Zhao Hai to complete the test, Margaret nodded and said, “Good, it means you can now study magic formations. Let me give you an introduction about the Machine Field’s magic formations.”

While she said that, Margaret went to the wall opposite Zhao Hai and turned it into a screen. Margaret turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Magic formations are actually magic runes combined together, forming a structure that can tap into the energy of the heavens and the earth. Aside from the special formations, most magic formations are circular. Materials in making magic formations have also been heavily researched. After many years of study, we found out that the runes are the main reason we can control the world’s spiritual qi. The materials used to make the formation are just auxiliary.”

Zhao Hai nodded. Just like Margaret said, the relationship between the magic formation’s might and the material used was quite significant. However, the ones that had a major impact on the formations were the runes that the Machine Field had studied.

Margaret continued, “Magic formations is a path itself, magic is also its own path. However, by themselves, the two aren’t very strong. Compared to the Machine Field’s magic theory, each of those paths are weak.”

When she spoke up to here, Margaret looked at Zhao Hai and said, “If you have read the introductions, then you should be aware that aside from the Machine Field, there are also other powers in the World of Cultivation. Moreover, these powers aren’t peaceful with each other. In the beginning, the Machine Field has been heavily bullied by the other powers. But when Magic Theory was invented, and we began making battleships and magic mechs, we slowly gained the qualifications to be treated as equal to the other major powers.”

Zhao Hai quietly listened to the lecture. He was already aware of these matters, therefore he wasn’t startled. Margaret went on, “However, battleships and mechs have always been the weakest part of the Machine Field. Magic Theory covered for this weakness. Because of Magic Theory, it made it possible for us to use our spiritual force in order to make magic formations out of thin air. The more powerful the spiritual force, the quicker the formation is created, and the more powerful it would be!”

Boom! A thunderclap resounded inside Zhao Hai’s mind.

Zhao Hai began to understand the core of Magic Theory. It uses spiritual force as a base of magic formations, this was the main pillar of Magic Theory.

Zhao Hai wasn’t new to using spiritual force. However, he didn’t think about using spiritual force in order to arrange magic formations.

When he thought about this, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but close his eyes, digesting Margaret’s words carefully. The words she said were very simple, anybody would be able to understand them. But those words couldn’t be underestimated, they were essential to Zhao Hai’s current enlightenment.

As she said those words, Margaret was also observing Zhao Hai’s response. Upon seeing Zhao Hai’s reaction, Margaret couldn’t help but smile. Intuition was very important to a Mage since it could bring forth enlightenment. Margaret hasn’t met anyone who became enlightened by those few words. This alone explained how uncommon Zhao Hai’s talent was.

Not only was Zhao Hai digesting Margaret’s words, he was also trying to use his spiritual force to arrange a magic formation. His spiritual force was much stronger compared to most Mages. He can also direct his spiritual force to perform certain functions. Just like Berry’s ability to control hair-like spiritual force, Zhao Hai could also use his spiritual force as minute strands.

Not only was Zhao Hai’s spiritual force formidable, he also had good control over it. But even if this was the case, he wasn’t able to find an appropriate use for this characteristic. As a person, his movements were limited. It was just like tying a rope to a tree, he still wasn’t able to reach the skies. Even if he was skillful, he wasn’t able to make use of it.

Margaret’s words opened a whole new world in front of Zhao Hai. Upon hearing about this new application, Zhao Hai was impatient to try it out.

Zhao Hai and an ordinary Mage’s control over their spiritual force had a huge difference. While most Mages could control their spiritual force as one unit, Zhao Hai was able to divide it by strands. This way, Zhao Hai’s attention was divided into small strands.

Dividing one’s attention in order to control these strands of spiritual force might sound simple, however, it was incomparably difficult. Not to say multiple strands, controlling two strands alone would prove difficult. One might not even find one capable of doing it among 10 thousand people. Meanwhile, Zhao Hai can control countless strands. This wasn’t only because he had a powerful mental strength, this was also because he had learned the Succubus Clan’s methods of controlling spiritual force. And with the help of the Space, this became possible.

Zhao Hai was currently using his spiritual force as a base of a magic formation. Zhao Hai had a basic understanding about magic formations. He also knew that he cannot be ambitious and tie multiple magic formations at the same time. Because of this, he can only arrange a simple formation.

However, Zhao Hai was quick to discover that the magic formations he learned didn’t allow for spiritual force to be their base. This caused Zhao Hai to be puzzled. He slowly opened his eyes and discovered that Margaret was sitting down while drinking tea.

Seeing Zhao Hai opened his eyes, Margaret smiled faintly and said, “Were you trying to arrange a magic formation? Did you fail?”

Zhao Hai nodded. Then Margaret gave another smile and said, “Most Mages will try it when they heard those words. But in the end, they failed. Do you know why?”

Zhao Hai shook his head, Margaret gave the answer, “It’s because magic formations in the lower realm and the Machine Realm are different.  The magic formations used to make magical mechs and battleships are also different from Magic Theory’s formations.”

When he heard Margaret, Zhao Hai’s spirit couldn’t help but shake. He finally began to understand. Machine Field’s Magic Theory was much more complex than he thought. He couldn’t just use it just because of a small realization.

Margaret looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Although there are also circular magic formations in the lower realms, their perimeter circle are mostly just lines. However, nobody knew that the perimeter circle was actually the most important part of the formation. If a magic formation was a building, then the perimeter circle would be the ground where the building was built on. The preparation of the ground dictates the life of the building. For magic formations, the perimeter circle is the foundation where it was built into. A magic formation’s might is directly related to this.”

Zhao Hai’s eyes became brighter and brighter. Margaret was satisfied with Zhao Hai’s expression. She now knew that Zhao Hai didn’t just dabble in magic formation, he had certainly given it some time to study. Otherwise, he wouldn’t have such an expression.

However, Margaret didn’t comment about it as she continued, “In the lower realms, the perimeter circle are just lines. But in the Machine Field, perimeter circles are made out of magic runes!”

Zhao Hai suddenly felt refreshed. He began to believe the difference between the lower realm’s magic formations and the Machine Field’s Magic Theory. No wonder he was unable to use his spiritual force to create magic formations.

Margaret looked at Zhao Hai and smiled as she said, “If formations are used in ordinary magical mechs and battleships, perimeter circles could just be made with lines. At most, it would affect the might of the formation. But in Magic Theory, the perimeter circle needed to be made out of magical runes. Otherwise, even if you have a powerful spiritual force, you still won’t be able to arrange magic formations.”

Zhao Hao nodded, he just experienced it so he believed Margaret’s words. But this time, he wouldn’t easily attempt to arrange a magic formation. This was because he became clear about the complexity of Magic Theory.

Seeing Zhao Hai stop himself from trying it out, Margaret couldn’t help but give a gentle nod. Zhao Hai’s performance made her satisfied. She said, “When arranging magic formations from different departments, some changes needed to be made in the internal pattern. Today, I will tell you about the nine most basic patterns of magic formations.”

Chapter 1084: Condensing a Formation

Zhao Hai is currently sitting inside his room with his eyes closed. In about half a meter in front of him was a magic formation slowly coming to form. This magic formation looked mystical as it is composed of multiple magic runes. However, the process was very slow as each rune needed to be formed individually.

Zhao Hai immediately returned to his room after his class. What he learned today was too important for him. It can be said that he now had a certain understanding about Magic Theory. The lesson was actually very simple, just the condensation of magic formation using spiritual force as a base, how the perimeter circle needed to be made out of runes, and then how to establish a formation so that it could exert its maximum power.

Deciding on which formation he wanted to condense, Zhao Hai finally settled on a summoning formation from the dark element. The formation belonged to a two-element formation with the space element as an auxiliary. It was because of this arrangement that the formation was quite difficult to condense.

For Mages in the Machine Field, condensing their first magic formation was the first hurdle to their path to mastering Magic Theory. As long as they were able to condense their first magic formation, they would then have an idea on how to condense others later on.

As for two-element formations, they were much more difficult to condense compared to formations that only had one element. Zhao Hai also asked Margaret about the Undead summoned using this summoning formation. It seems like the Undead that were called over weren’t ordinary undead, but they were at least King-level in strength.

At this time, Zhao Hai wanted to see what a summoned King-level Undead looks like. If he could really summon King-level Undead, then he could surely bolster the Space’s strength.

The magic formation slowly condensed. When the last magic rune was completed, the formation suddenly shone before an outline of a humanoid was seen.

Upon seeing this outline, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but stare. This was because he summoned a Gold Skeleton!

Gold Skeletons might be powerful to others, but in front of Zhao Hai, they were nothing. Crystal Skeletons and Skeleton Kings were the true powerhouses in Zhao Hai’s eyes. As for Gold Skeletons, Zhao Hai didn’t even know how many he had inside the Space. He didn’t have to work so hard just so that he could summon a Gold Skeleton.

But Zhao Hai changed his mind when he began to understand what was happening. Mages in the Machine Field would often layer formations one after another. If he layered several formations together, then he would surely be able to summon more powerful Undead.

Actually, Zhao Hai didn’t care much about what Undead he could summon. What was important to him was the process of condensing a magic formation.

In order to smoothly condense a magic formation, Zhao Hai didn’t divide his spiritual force but instead concentrated his mental energy and condensed the formation slowly.

The magic formation that Zhao Hai condensed wasn’t self-created. The formation was already a wide-spread format in the Machine Realm. With Zhao Hai’s current understanding of Magic Theory, he didn’t have the means to create his own formation. However, this didn’t stop him from believing that he would be able to create his own formation later on.

Zhao Hai collapsed his formation. However, he didn’t immediately go on to condense another one. Instead, Zhao Hai closed his eyes and sensed the feeling of condensing his first magic formation.

As for the Gold Skeleton that he summoned, Zhao Hai can be sure that it wasn’t summoned from the Underworld. As for which plane it came from, he didn’t know.

Almost all of the Undead in the Underworld had been turned to Zhao Hai’s subordinates. If his formation summoned an Undead from the Underworld, then he would be the first to know. Since he didn’t feel anything from the Gold Skeleton, then Zhao Hai was certain that it didn’t come from the Underworld.

Also, after sending the Gold Skeleton to the Space, he discovered that it was stronger compared to the Underworld’s Gold Skeletons. This caused Zhao Hai to be surprised.

From this point, Zhao Hai could see how extraordinary Magic Theory was. Even if one reached Zhao Hai’s strength, summoning magic in the lower realm didn’t allow a person to summon Gold Skeletons. If you wanted a Gold Skeleton, then you can only subdue one and form a contract with it.

As for the Machine Realm, even if Zhao Hai used the same amount of effort, since he has ascended to a place with a higher concentration of spiritual qi and has used Magic Theory, his summoning magic can now bring forth Gold Skeletons. This just shows how terrifying Magic Theory was.

However, one shouldn’t see Zhao Hai’s number of Gold Skeletons as normal. If he didn’t have the Space, he wouldn’t have this much Gold Skeleton subordinates.

Zhao hai sat in his chair as he looked back at the process of condensing a magic formation. He immersed himself in the feeling so that he could be more relaxed on his next attempt.

As soon as he felt that he was ready, Zhao Hai immediately tried to make his second formation. But this time, his thoughts just accelerated as a formation appeared in front of him in no time. It was a fully condensed magic formation.

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but stare before calling Cai’er inside his mind, “Cai’er, what just happened.”

Cai’er smiled and said, “Young Master, don’t forget that your spiritual force is one with the Space. Since the Space has the ability to record, it functions just like a computer. When you condensed your first magic formation, the Space recorded the entire process. Even if the process was difficult, as long as it was compiled and saved inside, you will then be able to use it any time. Therefore, later on, if you want to arrange a magic formation, you can do so with just a thought.”

Upon hearing Cai’er, Zhao Hai burst with happiness before he said, “So that’s the case. Fantastic! Cai’er, can the Space help be condense the magic formations?”

Cai’er replied, “Young Master, you’re getting lazier and lazier. The space can’t just help you condense magic formations. Since it is like a computer, you will need to write a program so that it could run. Condensing formations is just like writing a program. Therefore, you need to condense the formation on your own before it can be recorded and saved.”

Zhao Hai also felt that he was being a bit greedy. He was certain that no other Mage had this ability. He could essentially condense a magic formation once and then use it over and over again. It was extremely convenient.

After he thought about this, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile, “It seems like I need to condense more magic formations. Laura, how are you doing?”

Although he cannot enter the Space, Zhao Hai can still communicate with Laura and the others. As soon as she heard Zhao Hai, Laura nodded and said, “Brother Hai, rest assured, we’re doing just fine. The Machine Field isn’t the same as the lower realms, you have to be careful. There’s no need to worry about us.”

Zhao Hai gave a nod, “I can’t do anything in the meantime. Later, I’ll inspect the room for some surveillance devices. If there aren’t any, I will have you come out to get familiar with the environment. Right, did father-in-law and the others receive the magic runes?”

Laura smiled and said, “They’ve seen them. In fact, their very happy that they haven’t gone out of their rooms for quite a while now.”

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but chuckle. At this time, Wild Dragon Island’s laboratories were almost abandoned. Karen and the others moved to the small asteroid that was connected to the Hundred Spirit Tree. The small asteroid was close to where Zhao Hai’s villa was located, it had a surface area of about 100 thousand square meters.

A 100 thousand square meter area was quite huge, so Zhao Hai had Karen and the others move into the asteroid. Not only Karen’s group, the other people in Wild Dragon Island also decided to move. After all, the asteroid was many times bigger than Wild Dragon Island.

Besides the asteroid, there were also 99 other fruits that the Hundred Spirit Tree produced. But Zhao Hai didn’t immediately use them. Although these 99 fruits weren’t as huge as the asteroid, their use was still quite significant. They can be used as a spatial item, it can be farmed, and it can also help one’s cultivation. It was a product that went against the will of the heavens. These fruits would surely have great uses in the future.

Zhao Hai exchanged a few words with Laura and the others before stopping. After that, Zhao Hai began to focus on magic formations. There were countless magic formations in the Machine Field, and every magic formation was its own magic spell. These formations can be layered on top of one another in order to create even more varied effects. At present, it’s highly probable that nobody in the Machine Field knew just how many magic formation effects there were.

With the Space’s storage function, the more magic formations Zhao Hai condensed, the better. Naturally, he must take this opportunity and condense as much magic formations as he can.

Zhao Hai understood that even if the academy was safe, once he left, nobody would be able to guarantee his safety. He didn’t believe in the Machine Field’s laws either, they were just there for the common people to follow. For those huge powers, these laws were simply useless.

Moreover, Zhao Hai had offended Frey who was from the Wind Spirit Plane. People from this plane were pivotal beings in the Wind God Palace. Frey and his people might not deal with him inside the Academy, but once Zhao Hai left, it was difficult to say whether these people would try to attack him or not. If his strength was insufficient, even if there was the Space, Zhao Hai would still have to turtle in order to survive, and that wasn’t what he plans to do.

Most importantly, Zhao Hai was somewhat afraid. If he always hid inside the Space, then sooner or later, someone would get wind of its existence. When that time comes, he the troubles coming for him would be even bigger. Therefore, Zhao Hai wanted to use the present time to promote his fighting strength.

Chapter 1085: Laying Cards Out on the Table

Zhao Hai stopped condensing formations when dinner time came. During this time, Zhao Hai managed to condense more than 20 magic formations. People would be shocked by this speed. But to Zhao Hai, this was nothing.

After condensing his first magic formation, Zhao Hai managed to get the feel of the process. Because of this, he was able to condense magic formations much easier later on.

At this point, Zhao Hai could branch his spiritual force out into five threads while maintaining their accuracy. This allowed him to condense more than 20 magic formations in such a short period of time.

These magic formations weren’t just from the dark element, he also condensed formations from the other departments. After all, he was an all-element mage, it wouldn’t be strange for him to use magic from the other elements.

Zhao Hai proceeded to head towards the cafeteria. After seeing Zhao Hai arrive, Dins and the others gave him their greetings. Seeing Zhao Hai’s beaming appearance, Dins couldn’t help but smile as he asked, “Little Hai, did you do anything worth celebrating?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly as he replied, “I just learned some beautiful magic. Of course its a happy event”

When Dins heard Zhao Hai, he couldn’t help but stare, then he laughed and said, “You boastful brat. Today’s your second day of class, what magic could you have learned? Aren’t you still learning about magic runes?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Right, I just didn’t expect that magic formations would be this strong. For the people of the Machine Field to reach this level of research regarding magic formations, I really admire their efforts.”

Dins sighed and said, “The upper realm is really the upper realm. Their magic formations have completely surpassed our expectations. Moreover, these past few days, I’ve been reading about their Void Condensing Formation Technique in my computer. To be honest, it looked extremely formidable.”

The others agreed with a nod. Zhao Hai smiled faintly as he turned his hand, making a pile of snacks appear. These snacks were famous in the Ark continent, therefore Zhao Hai’s Space didn’t lack these things. In order to avert suspicions, the snacks were cold. He also took out several bottles of liquor.

Dins and the others couldn’t help but stare at what Zhao Hai took out. After some time, Dins pointed at the items and said, “Little Hai, where did you get these things?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “I got it from the lower realms. Where do you think I got them from? These are famous snacks back home. Everyone have a taste of our liquor too.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Dins quickly said, “Since that is the case, then we would have to be impolite. I didn’t expect an ascended expert like you to bring these things along. It’s quite strange.”

Zhao Hai just faintly smiled as he replied, “I’m still quite young, so naturally I still enjoy these things. Unlike you old deities who don’t eat commoner food.”

Even if these old men knew that Zhao Hai was ridiculing them, they couldn’t say anything back. When they were about to ascend, they didn’t know that the upper realms would be like this. They thought that they would become immortal gods. Since this was the case, then they won’t need material possessions anymore. Some of them even left their spatial equipment with their families.

Zhao Hai didn’t tell them that he had started condensing magic formations. From what Zhao Hai can see, it seems like these old men had yet to condense their first magic formation. If he tells them that he has, then they might feel down.

After sharing a meal and chatting with everyone, Zhao Hai returned to his own room. But this time, he didn’t immediately condense magic formations. Instead, he sat in front of the computer and looked up information about the Spirit Wind Plane and the Wind God Palace. He offended Frey, so its possible that he had already become their enemy.

The news he gained made Zhao Hai almost jump in fright. Just as Margaret said, the Spirit Wind Plane couldn’t be underestimated. It was a plane that specialized in producing ascenders, almost every year someone would ascend from that plane. Moreover, these ascenders were very close to each other. Offending one of them equated to offending all ascenders from the Spirit Wind Plane. Additionally, almost all of the Spirit Wind Plane ascenders were talents in the wind element. Because of this, Wind God Palace had been recruiting them year after year. This allowed the plane to gain a pivotal position inside the church.

Also the Wind God Palace was one of the major churches in the Church Alliance. At the same time, their strength inside the alliance can be said to be one of the top. It was a huge power.

The entire Machine Field was controlled by three major powers, with the Church Alliance being one of them. With the status of the Wind God Palace inside the Church Alliance, it certainly held great power. Zhao Hai never expected that he would offend such a huge group!

Upon thinking up to here, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile bitterly. It seems like being low-key in the Machine Realm wouldn’t do him any good. With that thought in mind, Zhao Hai turned the computer off and then began to condense more formations.

Zhao Hai stopped at midnight. At this point, he had already condensed about 50 magic formations. Even locally born experts of the Machine Realm wouldn’t be able to do that.

The next day went accordingly. After eating with Dins and the others, Zhao Hai proceeded towards his classroom. But to his surprise, Margaret was already waiting for him inside.

Zhao Hai hastily gave his greetings, “I’ve been unfair to instructor Margaret. I’m sorry for being late.”

Margaret shook her head and said, “You’re not late. I just came early. Take a seat, I have something to tell you.” Zhao Hai complied immediately and sat down.

Margaret looked at Zhao Hai and said, “It is a custom in the Ascender Academy to study magic formations during the first month. Generally, if you still haven’t learned anything after the first month, you will be turned over to a robot instructor. After learning magical runes, your instructor would then teach you about Void Condensing Formation Technique. After that, you will go to a church in order to further study. However, your progress has surpassed my expectations. Have you learned how to arrange magic formations?”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Yes, I have learned how to arrange formations.”

Margaret gave a nod, “I have already contacted the school about this, so you don’t have to come here anymore. In the future, I can just directly contact you. Here, this is for you. It is a small computer with a call function.” Then Margaret threw a wristband-looking thing towards Zhao Hai. It was silvery and bright.

Zhao Hai wore the wristband and then tried to operate it. Honestly, it was more convenient to use than computers. When operating it, there was a light screen that acted just like a monitor, it’s very good.

Zhao Hai stopped playing with the wrist computer after a while. Meanwhile, Margaret just left him to explore the device. When Zhao Hai stopped, she said, “My contact number has already been saved in that device. You can use it to talk to me directly. What you need to learn right now is how to condense magic formations. The more familiar you are to condensing magic formations, the quicker you would be. After you leave the academy, your speed will decide whether you live or die.”

Zhao Hai nodded, he already understood this aspect. But with the Space, the matter of speed was nothing.

Margaret looked at Zhao Hai and said, “I will be open to you. You ascended inside the Ashley Family’s Bone Symbol Camp’s domain. Later on after you leave the academy, someone from the Bone Symbol Camp will invite you to join the camp. I’m also from the Bone Symbol Camp. it seems like our leader has been paying attention to you, so he sent me over. Our Ashley Family is also a member of the Church Alliance and is one of the most important members of the Dark Church. The Bone Symbol Camp was the Ashely Family’s most famous outer sect camp, but now it has fallen. However, this ascender academy is still controlled by us. I hope that you will choose our camp when you graduate. Our leader has already told me that we have stopped monitoring you at school. The surveillance device inside your robot butler has also been removed. You can rest assured.”

Zhao Hai stared. He already knew that Margaret was from a powerful group, but he didn’t expect her to lay everything on the table. But he still believed Margaret’s words. If she really wanted him to join the Ashely Clan, then she wouldn’t deceive him with this matter. Moreover, with the innate skill that he showed, he was certainly worth being groomed by the Ashley family.

Zhao Hai looked at Margaret and said, “Instructor, rest assured. If nothing happens, then I would like to join the Bone Symbol Camp. However, I hope that the instructor could help me look after Dins and the others. If you can, please recruit them to the camp as well.”

Margaret looked at Zhao Hai and nodded, “If I tell the camp leader, I’m sure he will agree. Since I’ve already interacted with you, the other powers would know to not get in touch with you. But since our Bone Symbol Camp has been very low-key recently, there would be some blind fellows who will try to contact you. I hope that you can make your decision clear to them. After you head back, read about the Bone Symbol Camp’s situation. Don’t just look at the overall statistics, also pay attention to the casualty rates of the camps in recent years. You are a smart one, you should understand what I mean by this.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Instructor can rest assured, I understand. But instructor, I managed to offend someone from the Wind God Palace. If I join the Ashley Family, won’t I bring trouble along with me?”

Margaret looked at Zhao Hai and calmly replied, “The Ashley Family is a Dark Mage family, we aren’t afraid to face trouble!”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Yes, instructor, I understand.”

Margaret nodded, then she said, “It might be inconvenient for you to condense formations inside your room. You can go to the grounds to condense your formations and then try to see its power. I’ll give you two things. This first one will allow you to use a special room in the practice grounds. Besides you, nobody would be able to enter this room. This other one is a formation used to adjust the density of spiritual qi. After one month, this formation will adjust the concentration of spiritual qi around you. This way, you will be accustomed to the normal amount of spiritual qi by the time you graduate.” Then she threw two things over to Zhao Hai.

Chapter 1086: Special Robot Store

Zhao Hai looked at the two things he received. One looked like a card that you use in hotels, it also had a room number on it. The other one was a metal plate that had a small magic circle. It wasn’t very heavy and looked much like an ornament. However, Zhao Hai knew that the magic formation was more than just a decoration.

He deposited the two items in the Space before expressing his gratitude to Margaret. Margaret nodded and said, “I hope that you can live up to our expectations, don’t waste the camp leader’s efforts. I’ve already taught you everything I can. What you need to do now is to learn the Void Condensing Formation technique. Your further development will depend on your efforts. After you go back, you can look at how others layer their magic formations. However, don’t waste your time mimicking their style. You need to pave your own road. Understand?”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Instructor, feel relieved. I know what to do.” Margaret nodded, then she left the room.

Seeing Margaret leave, Zhao Hai’s brows couldn’t help but wrinkle. He didn’t expect to be on someone’s sights this quickly. Moreover, now that he entered the struggle of the Machine Field, it seems like withdrawing was impossible.

Although it can be seen that Margaret wasn’t forcing Zhao Hai to join the Bone Symbol Camp after he graduates, there was a veiled threat in between her words. Margaret told him that this Ascender Academy was under the Bone Symbol Camp’s control, and it seems like they can dictate where someone can go after they graduate. Also, since they can take the surveillance device away, this also meant that the Bone Symbol Camp had formidable control in this academy. If he didn’t join the Bone Symbol Camp, then he might not have a very good future.

Internal struggles exist everywhere, the Machine Field wasn’t exempted. The Wind God Palace wouldn’t dare deal with the Ashley Family. However, if Zhao Hai joins the other powers, then the Ashley Family might not mind killing him.

The reason Zhao Hai had this thought was because he had been showing shocking talent in these past couple of days. Studying magical runes would take others months to memorize, but he only did it in two days. Others might start to practice the Void Condensing Formation Technique by the time they graduate, but Zhao Hai was doing it right now. These caused powerful groups to take notice of him, especially the Ashley Family.

Other powers might not be aware of Zhao Hai’s talents, but the Ashley family was clearly aware of it because of Margaret. If Zhao Hai doesn’t join the Ashley family, then the family definitely wouldn’t allow him to join other powers. In the eyes of the Ashley Family, Zhao Hai was someone who has a good chance of being a powerful expert. Letting this person join a group other than them would be impossible.

Because of this, Zhao Hai could only join the Ashley family. However, Zhao Hai doesn’t object to joining the family. What he needed to do now was to understand the Bone Symbol Camp’s situation.

Moreover, Zhao Hai needed to have the old Mages join the Bone Symbol Camp as well. This was for self preservation. With the old Mages together with him, his future would be more secure.

The Machine Field was a strange new place. Being in a group was definitely much better than being all alone.

With this thought in mind, Zhao Hai stood up. He was preparing to head to the shops in order to see whether there were any anti-surveillance devices. If there were any, he was prepared to buy one.

This didn’t mean that he didn’t trust Margaret’s words. Since Margaret said that they had removed all of the surveillance equipment, then those should have already been removed. This was the Ashley family’s way of showing their sincerity.

Zhao Hai wanted to buy anti-surveillance equipment not because of the Ashley family, but because of the other powers. The Ashely family’s intent of stopping any surveillance on him wasn’t necessarily shared by the other powers. At the very least, Zhao Hai wanted to be assured.

Zhao Hai had always been a careful person. And since he was in a strange new environment, ne needed to be extra careful. Margaret’s words weren’t enough to make him feel relieved.

When he thought of this, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but sigh. He really wished to ascend without any problems so that he could bring his wives to explore new places. But now it seems like this would be impossible. The struggles of the upper realm wasn’t any better than the lower realm.

Bringing Tinkle along, Zhao Hai went to the elevator and headed towards the shops. After looking through the shops, he was finally able to spot the place he wanted to find, a special robot store.

Gu Mingyue recommended Zhao Hai to look for this shop in order to remove any surveillance devices installed inside Tinkle. Zhao Hai had always kept this suggestion in mind.

Although Gu Mingyue wasn’t an upper level staff in the academy, he still had some information that only people from lower-levels knew. Because of this, he can tell Zhao Hai about these special robot stores.

 Zhao Hai inspected the shop. It looked just like any other shop, it didn’t have any special qualities. If not for Gu Mingyue, Zhao Hai wouldn’t have paid attention to this place.

After seeing nothing special, Zhao Hai brought Tinkle inside. Just as he entered the store, a robot immediately welcomed him. This robot wasn’t an advanced one and it had the same appearance as Tinkle. However, Zhao Hai was surprised since this robot didn’t have any clanking sounds that Tinkle always had.

When the robot arrived in front of Zhao Hai, it gave a bow and said, “Mister, welcome. Is there something we can help you with?”

Zhao Hai stared, then he smiled faintly and said, “I want to modify my robot butler. Can you do that?”

The robot immediately said, “Of course. Please come with me.” Then it gestured towards Zhao Hai. The robot’s movements weren’t stiff at all. Moreover, it can give answers very quickly. At the same time, it didn’t seem to have programmed responses. This caused Zhao Hai to be more curious about this shop.

From outside the shop, you can see ordinary robot parts and electronics. It looked like any other shop of its kind. But as the robot lead Zhao Hai further in, things began to become different. Behind the shop was a repair station with a lot of old robot components piled up. A person was sitting on the pile while manipulating a robot placed in front of him.

As Zhao Hai entered the room with the robot, the robot suddenly said, “Hey, sober up. This gentleman here wants to modify his robot butler.”

Upon hearing the robot, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but gawk. The robot was actually speaking like a human. It seems like this was the setting the robot was given. Zhao Hai couldn’t help but feel interested about this person.

The man turned his head towards Zhao Hai. Seeing the person’s face, Zhao Hai stared for a moment. His age didn’t seem to be high, maybe around 30 years old. His face was a bit pale and he had ordinary work clothes on. He looked very ordinary aside from his fiery eyes.

The man looked at Zhao Hai and quickly gave his greetings as he said, “Mister, you want to modify your robot butler?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “I just ascended from the lower realms and the academy gave me this robot butler. So I’m here to modify it.”

When he heard Zhao Hai, the man’s eyes turned bright before he said, “Since the robot is given by the academy, then it should be fine. Why do you want to modify it?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “I just want a robot butler that is completely loyal to me. Do you understand what I’m saying?”

The man’s eyes turned brighter, he nodded and said, “It seems like you’ve been introduced by a friend. I know what you want. What else do you require?”

Zhao Hai said, “I want it to help me scan my room for any surveillance device. I’m someone who doesn’t want to be monitored.”

The man nodded, then he held his wrist computer out and typed some things out as he said, “Go on, say all of your requests in one go.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Make him more advanced, not easily damaged, and store more energy so that it wouldn’t need to charge every day. It would be best for it to last a long time. I also want it to know some knowledge about the Machine Field’s machinery. And that doesn’t mean just robot repair, I want it to know how to tinker with other things. Naturally, since it is a robot butler, I don’t need it to fight. Instead, make sure that it can attend to my everyday needs.”

After the man recorded everything, he looked at the list and couldn’t help but knit his brows. Then he said, “Let me tell you the truth. I can certainly do all of this, but I think that it would be a waste. If you want all of these functions, then you could just buy a more advanced robot. Not only can advanced robots meet your requirements, they can do it much better than this one. Do you want to change your request?”

Zhao Hai stared for a moment before he nodded as he said, “Since that is the case, then I’ll do what you say.” Then he gestured to Tinkle and said, “Just make sure that it doesn’t have any sounds whenever it moves. Also, make its battery last longer. As for the advanced robot, I’ll take whatever Mister recommends me. As long as it meets my requirements, then its fine. But it needs to be able to connect to the network at any time.”

The man smiled and said, “No problem. Being connected to the network is the most basic function that everyone wants, so there’s no need to worry about that. Making your robot butler silent and last longer is very simple. You can leave him to me right now and come back after an hour or so. You can take a stroll around the shop to kill time. As for your new robot, It would take me three days to make it match your requests.”

Zhao Hai thought for a moment and then said, “Alright, I’ll leave Tinkle to you first. Do I go outside to choose my advanced robot?”

The man replied, “What’s outside are ordinary goods, they’re no good. If you trust me, I can choose for you. I have some robots I assembled myself. Although their functions are inferior to those bought outside, I can guarantee that they are more easy to use. Moreover, they are made out of better materials.”

Zhao Hai faintly smiled and said, “Since you’re recommended by a friend, I’ll trust Mister’s choice.”

The man gave Zhao Hai a look before he laughed and said, “You’re an interesting fellow, I like you. And don’t call me Mister. My name is Qi Yi. You can call me Ah Yi.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “So it is Manager Qi Yi. You have an interesting name. Then I’ll be calling you Ah Yi from now on. Ah Yi, let’s go see the robots you recommend.”

Qi Yi smiled and said, “Okay. Right, what’s your name. You still haven’t told me.”

Zhao Hai quickly replied, “Right, right. I forgot to introduce myself. I’m called Zhao Hai. You can also call me Ah Hai.”

Qi Yi smiles and said, “Good, let’s go see my robots. Also, who told you to come see me?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “It’s Mister Gu Mingyue. He’s a reception staff. We got along well, so he told me about your shop and to make sure to come visit in order to modify Tinkle. Since someone from the academy told me that the surveillance on my robot was removed, I decided to come here since I’m not an expert in robots.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Qi Yi stared for a moment before his eyes shone. Then he replied, “Oh, if that’s the case, then there’s no problem. If that’s what they said, then it means that you’re a genius, you can rest assured. If they said that the surveillance has been removed, then nobody in the academy will be monitoring you. If they removed their surveillance on you and other parties still dared to look into your actions, then this only means that the other party is being hostile. This will most likely cause a conflict. I reckon that only a few people would dare take such a risk.”

Zhao Hai replied, “Is that so? I really didn’t know. It seems like coming over to you was the correct decision. Right, how about having dinner with me? I also have some friends from the academy, I hope we can share a few cups together.”

Qi Yi looked at Zhao Hai and said, “How long have you been in the academy? You already made a few friends? Alright, that’s not an issue. Come over at night, I’ll be waiting.” As he said that, the two arrived at a door. Qi Yi put his hand on the door before it opened. Then the two proceeded to enter a room.

This room was about a hundred square meters, it wasn’t small at all. Inside the room was a huge display of robots. These robots were all humanoid. They don’t look beautiful, but all of them were very clean and well polished.

Chapter 1087: You’re From the Bone Symbol Camp?

Zhao Hai inspected the robots. They were evidently much better than Tinkle. At the very least, the facial features of these robots were closer to being human. Their joints looked more flexible as well.

Qi Yi looked at these robots with the looks that one might give a lover. Then he said, “All robots in this room are assembled by me. The parts used to make them are also slowly being processed by me, they’re not made by some huge company. These robots are my unique products.”

Looking at Qi Yi’s expression, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but sigh. Qi Yi truly had an unparalleled attraction to robots. All of these robots were actually made entirely by him. It was an amazing feat if you think about it.

After some time, Qi Yi let out a long breath, then he turned to Zhao Hai and said, “You and me are destined to be friends. You can choose any one of these robots.”

Zhao Hai looked at Qi Yi and smiled, “Alright, then I’ll have to thank you in advance. But since you made these robots, I’ll have to ask you to choose one that can match me the most. In any case, you’ll also be the one to modify them.”

When he heard Zhao Hai, Qi Yi couldn’t help but ask, “You trust me that much?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Just like you said, we’re destined to be friends. And from what I can see, you’re a guy I can trust.”

Qi Yi suddenly laughed, “Alright, then it’s settled. You can come back three days later. I can assure you that you won’t be disappointed by your robot. Let’s head out.” Zhao Hai didn’t say anything else and just followed Qi Yi out of the room.

Outside the workshop, Zhao Hai looked at Qi Yi and said, “Qi Yi, with your ability, you should be capable enough to make your own company. Why do you only have a small shop in the academy?”

Qi Yi forced a smile as he replied, “Supporting this academy is the Ashley Family’s Bone Symbol Camp. I’m from the camp myself. However, I don’t like magic and would prefer studying robots. People like me won’t get accepted anywhere except the Bone Symbol Camp. This shop isn’t even mine. I don’t operate this shop to make money, I’m just handling it on behalf of the camp.”

Zhao Hai stared, he didn’t expect Qi Yi to also be part of the Bone Symbol Camp. He looked at Qi Yi and said, “I’ve just recently heard about the Bone Symbol Camp. I heard that this ascending point is controlled by them. Are you an ascender as well?”

Qi Yi just gave a bitter smile as he answered, “How is that possible. With my skill, I won’t even be able to ascend. As you can see, my talent is just ordinary. However, I like to research robots. And the ones I make aren’t inferior to the ones made by huge companies. Because of this ability, I was able to be recruited by the Bone Symbol Camp. In my opinion, the Machine Realm is just like the lower realms. There are powerful beings and then there are the commoners. I’m just a commoner in this realm, not any different from commoners from the lower realms. If not for my talent in robotics, it would be impossible for me to be invited by the Bone Symbol Camp’s leader.”

Zhao Hai looked at Qi Yi in confusion, then he asked, “Why did you join the Bone Symbol Camp?”

Qi Yi smiled and said, “Doesn’t your lower realm have a division between nobles and commoners? If you are a commoner and then suddenly you’ve been invited by a noble to join their clan, wouldn’t you accept?”

Zhao Hai began to understand Qi Yi’s decision, he nodded and said, “I understand. But is the Bone Symbol camp good? I heard that they’re somewhat declining.”

Qi Yi coldly snorted and said, “Bone Symbol Camp hasn’t declined. However, it’s just different from the other camps who employ brutal training methods. In the Bone Symbol Camp, everyone is a friend, a brother. The camp leader never eliminates anybody and had everyone play to their strengths. In the other camps, everyone is an enemy and competitor. Every camp would add people to their numbers every year, some even reaching 100 people annually. Those who survive will be recruited. The Bone Symbol Camp doesn’t follow this path. Aside from deaths during battle, nobody dies when training. Because of this, the Bone Symbol Camp is somewhat weaker than the other camps, making it seem like we’re declining.”

Zhao Hai nodded. Looking at Zhao Hai’s response, Qi Yi’s eyes couldn’t help but shine as he said, “Why don’t you join the Bone Symbol Camp? That would be fantastic. If that is the case, then I will give the robot to you for free.”

When he heard Qi Yi, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but laugh. Qi Yi was truly a straightforward person. Although he understood some worldly wisdom, he still falls short compared to those old foxes.

If other powers wanted to recruit Zhao Hai, the conditions they would provide would certainly be very good. Compared to those offers, a little robot would be nothing. However, Zhao Hai can see the Bone Symbol Camp’s attitude by looking at Qi Yi.

If nobody protected people like Qi Yi when they entered other camps, then they would certainly be long dead. Qi Yi living up to this point was actually an abnormality.

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Then give me a good one. I have already promised Instructor Margaret to join the Bone Symbol Camp. The people we’re going to dine with will also be joining the camp. If there’s a chance, I’ll have them visit so that they can have their robot butlers be modified too.”

Qi Yi patted his chest and said, “Just hand them over to me. I might not be good at anything else. But when it comes to robots, there’s nothing I can’t accept. Have all of them send their robots over.”

Zhao Hai gave a nod. Then after leaving Tinkle behind, he left the shop to explore the other shops. It can be said that this area had too many stores. But this time, Zhao Hai didn’t buy anything. He was a lower realm ascender with no backers. If he showed-off by wantonly buying a lot of things, then people might begin to get suspicious.

Moreover, things sold in these stores would certainly be available anywhere else in the Machine Field. As long as he graduated from the academy, he could just buy what he wants outside. Therefore, there’s no need to be anxious at this time.

One hour passed and lunch time was approaching, so Zhao Hai returned to Qi Yi’s shop. Seeing Zhao Hai return, Qi Yi immediately invited him in and said, “Come, take a look at your robot.” Then he took Zhao Hai to the workshop.

Upon entering, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but stare. In the middle of the room was a robot. He could see from its head that it was Tinkle, but the body seems to be new, making Tinkle more pleasing to look at.

Looking at Zhao Hai’s reaction, Qi Yi proudly smiled and said, “What do you think? The robot now has an automatic solar charging system as well as a noise suppression upgrade. Most importantly, I’ve installed an anti-surveillance device inside to make sure that nobody will monitor you. Take it, return for your other robot in three days.”

Zhao Hai laughed and said, “Alright. Thank you, Ah Yi. Don’t forget our evening meal.”

Qi Yi waved his hand and said, “Don’t worry, I won’t forget.”

After that, Zhao Hai brought Tinkle to the academy’s cafeteria. Dins and the others were already waiting for him inside. Currently, Dins and the others also have their own instructors. However, since their instructors were part-time, they weren’t as approachable as Margaret. Nevertheless, the old Mages still take their regular classes.

Seeing Zhao Hai arrive, Dins immediately called him over. Dins and the others were also quick to discover Tinkle’s changes. Dins looked at Tinkle and said, “Little Hai, did you have Tinkle modified? It looks very good.”

Zhao Hai faintly smiled and said, “It really does. There’s a special robot shop in the market that can modify your robots. I’ve reached an agreement with the shop’s manager to have your robots be modified as well.”

Dins and the others had already regarded Zhao Hai as one of them. They also knew that Zhao Hai didn’t lack money. Because of this, they didn’t decline his goodwill. Dins nodded and said, “Alright, when do we send the robots?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “This afternoon. I’ve invited the manager to have dinner with us. You can use this chance to have your robots modified. By tomorrow, you should be able to get them back.”

Dins stared, he looked confused as he asked, “Do you know the manager? You even asked him to have dinner?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “It’s nothing special. I just talked to him and judging by his character, I decided to invite him to dinner. He’s also a Machine Field native. Talking to him will give us more understanding about the Machine Field.”

Dins nodded, “Alright, we’ll go meet him. Having friends here will give us advantages in the future. After all, the academy doesn’t teach us everything.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he looked at the others and said, “How about we meet here at 5 o’clock. Then we’ll set off to the store to look for Qi Yi. Don’t forget to bring your robots. You’re going to leave them behind so that Qi YI can modify them.”

Dins and the others nodded. However, the faces of several people don’t seem quite right. Zhao Hai mentioned modifying their robots multiple times now. These old men were also old foxes, so they knew that Zhao Hai might be hinting at something. However, none of them said anything as though they didn’t get anything from what Zhao Hai said.

After lunch, Zhao Hai returned to his room. Upon entering, Zhao Hai turned to Tinkle and said, “Tinkle, inspect the room. See whether there are any surveillance devices hidden inside.” Tinkle responded, “Yes, Young Master.”

Then Tinkle’s eyes emitted flashing red lights as they scanned the entire room. After some time, Tinkle stopped and said, “Young Master, there are no monitoring devices inside the room. You can rest assured.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he began to relax. However, he didn’t immediately let Laura and the others out. Instead, he sat down and practiced his magic formations. At the same time, he had Cai’er monitor Qi Yi’s actions to see if he was really sincere in helping him modify his robot. If Qi Yi changed anything, then Zhao Hai will not take Laura and the others out.

Chapter 1088: Unusual Level Division

Zhao Hai’s condensation of magic formations was getting faster and faster. At this point, he could already condense ten formations at once. But compared to the total amount of known magic formations in the Machine Field, his speed was still far from enough.

However, Zhao Hai wasn’t worried as he continued to condense ten magic formations at the same time. Each batch needed ten minutes to be finished. He could now condense at least 50 formations every hour. Such speed has never been seen before and might never be seen again.

Moreover, Zhao Hai’s condensed magic formations weren’t as simple as that. Every magic formation that Zhao Hai condensed has been recorded by the Space. Then Cai’er would take these formations and run them under the scanner. This way, the Space could come up with the most appropriate combinations.

In the Machine Field, the level of a Mage depended on the number of magic formations they could layer on top of another. The overall division came in ten levels. The levels were divided as so: 1st level Mages were those who could layer less than 5 formations. 2nd level Mages could layer 5 to 10 formations. 3rd level Mages would be 10 to 50 formations. 4th level Mages needed 50 to 100. 5th level, 100 to 500. 6th level is 500 to 1000. 7th level is 1000 to 3000. 8th level ranges from 3000 to 5000. 9th level, 5000 to 10,000. And then 10th level was over 10,000 layered formations.

Nobody knew for how long the Machine Field has existed, but Magic Theory had existed for at least tens of thousands of years. But until now, the highest level Mage could only reach the 9th level. There has never been a 10th level Mage.

The most powerful 9th level Mage could only layer 9,999 magic formations. Achieving 10,000 layered formations seem to be impossible.

It can be said that layered formations were the symbol of strength in the Machine Field. Moreover, with the number of magic formations present in the Machine Field, layering them together was an almost impossible feat.

In fact, in the current Machine Field, it was speculated that even the most senior mage couldn’t layer 3000 magic formations together. This meant that currently, nobody had reached 8th level. The most powerful mage of this generation was at the 7th level.

Layering 3000 magic formations together needed a massive amount of time to accomplish. Also, in the middle of battle, where would one find time to spend in order to arrange such a huge formation? It was practically impossible. But if you only use a few layers of formations, they would be too weak to fight against other experts.

In the World of Cultivation, the cultivation speed of every realm was almost the same at the early stages. In the Machine Field, Mages that can layer five formations could resist against a forged body expert. If you follow the Divine Realm’s metric, then forged body experts were equivalent to 9th rank or Demigod-rank experts.

As for Mages that can layer 10 formations together, they would be equal to qi condensation experts, God-ranks to Peak God-ranks. Cultivating to this stage generally wouldn’t take a long time.

Wanting to layer 10 to 50 formations wasn’t that difficult either. As long as one can layer 30 magic formations, then this meant that they had already reached foundation establishment. Most Mages would be stuck at this level.

There were a lot of Mages that would never go beyond 3rd level. But for the Cultivators, foundation establishment was just the beginning of their path of Cultivation.

It can be said that only one in a hundred Cultivators could reach foundation establishment, for Mages, this ratio drops down to one in ten thousand. In this case, Mages would find it hard to go against Cultivators.

The power divide between Warriors in the Machine Field was also the same as the Mages. However, the Warriors didn’t base their levels on how much magic formations they can layer on top of another. Instead, they base their strength on how far their sword qi could reach.

Their division of level was also very simple, it was just like the Mages but the numerical values were multiplied by 100. For example. 1st level Warriors could release their sword qi for less than 500 meters. 2nd level Warriors is 500 meters to 1 kilometer, and so on. The highest level Warrior could release his sword qi as far as 1 million meters. Naturally, this level only existed in legends.

One needed to note that the term ‘sword qi’ was only a generalization. This didn’t mean that it was energy released using a sword. There were Warriors in the Machine Field that use weapons that were not swords. As long as they can launch their energy to a certain extent, they would be similarly ranked.

Because of this system, Mages and Warriors of the Machine Field found it hard to go against experts from other realms. In the end, they could only rely on the might of battleships and magic mechs.

As for Zhao Hai, he was just concentrating on condensing magic formations in the meantime. He wasn’t planning to layer magic formations yet. He was planning to try it inside the Space and not in the academy.

Even if he was alone in a secluded part of the academy, Zhao Hai still thought that it wouldn’t be safe. Therefore, he could only do it inside the Space.

By afternoon, Zhao Hai managed to condense several hundred magic formations. After looking at the time, he stopped and went out of his room to head towards the cafeteria.

Seeing that Dins and the others were already in the cafeteria, Zhao Hai quickly called them over so that they could head to the shops. There was a small advantage to being in the academy. It didn’t matter if it was the shops or the cafeteria, all of them were open all the time. You can buy items and eat food whenever you want.

It didn’t take long before Zhao Hai and the others arrived outside the strange robot shop. Qi Yi was still busy inside the workshop and would be for a long time. When Zhao Hai arrived, he stopped working as he laughed and said, “A Hai, you’re here. As you can see, I’ve been busy with work..”

Zhao Hai smiles and said, “It’s alright. Let me introduce you. They are recent ascenders to the Machine Field. They’re just a little bit older than me. I’ll have to trouble you to modify their robots as well. We’ll be leaving their robots here for now. Just tell them when they can get them back.”

Qi Yi laughed and said, “You guys really want me to work huh. Alright, rest assured, I will complete everything in time.” Then after greeting Zhao Hai, he proceeded to greet the old men.

After the two sides exchanged their greetings, Zhao Hai brought everyone to the first floor restaurant. This time, the restaurant was chosen by Qi Yi. This restaurant was simply called Academy Restaurant. It wasn’t a large one nor did it look anything special.

Once they arrived at the restaurant, Zhao Hai turned his head towards Dins and the others as he said, “Everyone, there’s something I need to tell you. The Ascender Academy that we’re in is controlled by the Ashley Family’s Bone Symbol Camp. The people from the camp has already contacted me and hoped that I could join them after I graduate. I also told them that it would be great if everyone here can join.”

Dins and the others stared. To be honest, they were completely unaware about this matter. Zhao Hai scanned them and then continued, “From what I understand, besides the Bone Symbol Camp, the other powers that recruit ascenders employ the survival of the fittest mindset. They would carry on brutal training in order to eliminate the weak. Those who stay behind are recruited while the others would be dead. The Bone Symbol Camp doesn’t do the same program. As long as you join the camp, they will make sure that you play to your own strength. At the same time, they would arrange jobs that is appropriate to your abilities. Qi Yi is someone from the Bone Symbol Camp. Since he is only interested in robots, the camp leader had him manage a robot shop in the academy. Everyone should be able to understand what I want to say. You aren’t like the young ascenders, so people from the Machine Field wouldn’t place great importance on your existence. If you join other camps, then you will certainly be treated as cannon fodder. Because of this, I’d like all of us to join the Bone Symbol Camp. Then later on, we can take care of each other. What do you think?”

Hearing Zhao Hai’s words, Dins and the others turned silent. They weren’t fools. Conversely, they had gained rich experience from the lower realms, so they knew how people acted. There were a lot of stronger people among the young ascenders, therefore they couldn’t help but believe Zhao Hai.

Additionally, they were aware that joining a camp together meant that they can protect each other more effectively. The old men looked at each other before they nodded. After that Barlett said, “Rest assured little Hai, we understand what you’re saying. Since you want us to join the Bone Symbol Camp, then everyone will follow you.”

The others nodded, showing their agreement. Zhao Hai smiled and said, “It’s good that everyone agrees. Since Qi Yi is also from the Bone Symbol Camp, we will have to trouble him to modify your robot butlers. This is because there are monitoring devices inside each of your robots. Your every action and movement have fallen to the other people’s attention. We’ll have Qi Yi help use to remove these devices. After all, all of us are now part of the same family.”

As soon as they heard Zhao Hai, the faces of Dins and the others changed. They turned to look at Qi Yi for affirmation. Qi Yi couldn’t hide his excitement. In the past, old Mages like them would join other camps to be cannon fodder instead of the Bone Symbol Camp. Because of this, the Bone Symbol Camp was lacking in numbers. Having this much people join at the same time naturally made him happy.

Looking at the old Mages’ expressions, Qi Yi immediately nodded and said, “Right, each of your robot butlers has monitoring devices inside them. And these devices don’t only send information to one or two people, but to multiple groups at once. These people would gauge you depending on your performance. If you can meet their standards, then they will contact you to invite you over to their camp.”

Dins and the others’ faces were somewhat ugly. They didn’t expect their day-to-day life to be monitored. This was basically like throwing their undergarments out into the streets, nobody would be able to endure it.

Zhao Hai looked at their expressions and said, “I know that a lot of people will contact you when the time comes. And they might give you a lot of good benefits, but you should also know that your lives are your most important possession. Under such brutal training, you cannot guarantee your survival. Also, we are a minority group, even if you get promised good conditions, nobody can guarantee that they will follow through with their promise. Therefore, I hope that all of us can enter the same camp so that we can help each other.”

Chapter 1089: Connecting to the Network

Dins and the others nodded. They’re already late into their ages, past the times when one would want glory and power. To the current them, survival was more important than anything. Therefore, as soon as they heard Zhao Hai, all of them thought that his words were reasonable.

Zhao Hai looked at everyone and said, “Earlier, I looked up the situation with the Ashley Family’s Bone Symbol Camp online. Although they don’t seem to differ compared to the other camps, they were even seen as declining, but after going through the Bone Symbol Camp’s casualties in the past ten years, their ratio only came up to 1:1000. And when carrying out special tasks, they would have a casualty rate of 1 to 5. In other words, in five people, only one would die. Meanwhile, the other camps would have a casualty rate of 1 to 1. This means that there are times that all of their recruits die during missions. It’s a very brutal statistic. If everyone is interested, you can look it up yourselves.”

Dins and the others nodded. They will look it up, but this didn’t mean that they didn’t believe Zhao Hai. They just wanted to see this casualty rate with their own eyes. They believed that Zhao Hai wouldn’t deceive them with this matter, there simply was no need to do so. As long as they go back, they can prove it themselves.

Zhao Hai looked at the others and said, “We didn’t ascend here just to die. Therefore, joining the Bone Symbol Camp is our best choice. Even a low allowance wouldn’t be a problem. And from what I had looked up, the Bone Symbol Camp’s allowance wasn’t even that low.”

Dins nodded and said, “Just like what Little Hai said, we didn’t ascend in order to become cannon fodder. It would be best for everyone if we can enter the Bone Symbol Camp. This way, we can take care of each other.” The others also gave their agreement.

Seeing that everyone has agreed, Zhao Hai said, “Good, since everyone agrees, then I don’t have anything else to say. Come, let’s drink. Let’s work hard together and enter the Bone Symbol Camp.” The others raised their glasses and cheered.

The reason why Zhao Hai dared to say all of this at this time was because the robot butlers were currently left behind in Qi Yi’s shop. Moreover, the restaurant that they were currently in didn’t have any monitoring devices. Of course, this was something that Zhao Hai asked Qi for.

The Ascender Academy that Zhao Hai was currently in was closely monitored by the Bone Symbol Camp. There were only a few places that didn’t have any surveillance device. Zhao Hai knew about this point so he asked Qi Yi for a restaurant that wasn’t monitored. Because of this, they were now inside this specific restaurant.

After eating their meal, Zhao Hai and the others returned to their own rooms. Zhao Hai checked the internet for a while before going back to condensing formations.

For the following days, Zhao Hai’s life went normally. Every day, he would go to the cafeteria to have breakfast, then he would go to the classroom in order to get a lecture. After that, he returned to his room and whatever he liked.

Zhao Hai had yet to release Laura and the others. However, he kept monitoring Qi Yi in the past three days. He wanted to see whether Qi Yi really didn’t want to monitor him or was he just feigning ignorance.

It didn’t take a long time before Zhao Hai knew that Qi Yi was a genuine ally. The man seems to have a heavy obsession with robotics. He always stayed inside his shop. When it was time to eat, he would just have the cafeteria deliver food to him. Most of the time, he was in his workshop tinkering with robots.

Dins and the others’ robots were done being modified the day after they were sent in. Qi Yi didn’t ask them for money. After all, in Qi Yi’s eyes, Dins and the others were already people on his own side.

Besides looking at Qi Yi’s actions, Zhao Hai was also monitoring Dins and the others. Zhao Hai wanted to see if they would agree to being recruited by other people.

Three days went by fast. Zhao Hai got up early to eat before going to Qi Yi’s shop. Today was the day he would get his new advanced robot.

Zhao Hai didn’t know what kind of robot Qi Yi had prepared for him. Although he was monitoring Qi Yi, the moment Zhao Hai knew that he was an ally, he stopped.

When Zhao Hai entered Qi Yi’s shop, Qi Yi wasn’t there. Zhao Hai didn’t need to be polite and just went straight to the workshop.

Qi Yi had already modified the robot in his shop to allow Zhao Hai entry. Because of this, Zhao Hai didn’t encounter any troubles as he went to the workshop.

When he arrived at the workshop, Zhao Hai saw Qi Yi being busy tinkering with a robot. This wasn’t the robot that Zhao Hai saw back in that room three days ago. Instead, it was a robot with a high degree of human appearance.

The body of this robot was covered with a biochemical skin. Its two eyes looked like genuine eyes. If not for its lack of emotion, one might mistake it as a real person.

Zhao Hai can affirm that this wasn’t his robot. This was because Qi Yi’s robots never had biochemical skin. To Qi Yi, robots were robots. They were their own lifeforms and they didn’t need to cater to humanistic standards regarding appearance.

Although Zhao Hai thought otherwise, he didn’t say anything. For people like Qi Yi, this aspect was regarded as very important.

Zhao Hai looked around the room and saw a robot at the side. He had seen this robot in the room back then. Its whole body was made out of shining metal. It wasn’t very tall, only at about 1.8 meters. It had a somewhat human face but it was still very far from robots with biochemical skins.

Seeing that Qi Yi was completely focused on his task, Zhao Hai gave out two light coughs. Qi Yi quickly turned his head towards Zhao Hai. After grabbing Qi Yi’s attention, Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Ah Yi, I’m here for my robot. How is it? Is it done?”

Qi Yi immediately said, “It’s done. Take a look. It has everything you requested. What do you think? Do you want to leave your old robot here? Having this one is already enough.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “It’s alright. There’s no harm in having two robots. You seem to be busy, I’ll take my leave.”

Qi Yi nodded and said, “Alright, come over later in the evening. How about we share a cup or two?”

Zhao Hai agreed, “Get two meals delivered and we’ll drink here.”

Qi Yi nodded. Then Zhao Hai turned around and left the shop along with his two robots.

Since it was still time for classes, there were very few people wandering the shops. Zhao Hai didn’t meet anyone as he was returning to his room.

When he arrived at his room, Zhao Hai had Tinkle inspect the new robot. Finding that there were no monitoring devices on the robot, Zhao Hai began to feel relieved. Then he waved his hand and had Laura and the others come out.

As soon as they came out, Laura and the others immediately cheered as they threw themselves towards Zhao Hai. Being hugged by several women, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but feel incomparable satisfaction.

After some time, Laura and the others calmed down. Zhao Hai looked at them and smiled as he said, “You’re still unable to leave this room. However, you can browse the internet on the computer so that you can understand this world more. After I leave the academy, I’ll find a way to provide all of you with Machine Field ID Cards.”

Laura waved his hand and said, “It’s fine, we like being inside the Space anyway. Brother Hai, I had father study the plate that Margaret gave you. He believed that it wouldn’t take long before they can duplicate it. When the time comes, we would also be able to adapt to the Machine Field’s spiritual qi.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Good. After you go back, I’ll also have Tinkle go along with you so that father and the others could see it. However, I can’t have Tinkle enter the Space for long. It wouldn’t be good if people see me without my robot butler for a long period of time..”

Laura nodded. Zhao Hai took out several wrist computers and then handed them over to Laura and the others. This way, they could access the internet on their own.

Computers in the Machine Field were much better than the ones in the Space. Computers in the Space didn’t have any network connection. Because of this, computers can only perform basic functions. But in the Machine Field, computers were connected to each other, and in a degree one hundred times more advanced than Earth. Therefore, it didn’t take long for Laura and the others to be immersed on the internet.

Zhao Hai just discovered that connecting to the Machine Field’s internet didn’t require any payment. Whether they were robots or computers, connecting to the network was free.

While Laura and the others were accessing the net, Zhao Hai was on the side condensing magic formations. When dinner time arrived, Zhao Hai stopped what he was doing. Then he turned to Laura and the others and said, “Alright, it’s already late. You should go back. You can come over to play tomorrow.”

Laura and the others looked at the time, and it was indeed already late. However, some of them were still reluctant to leave. Zhao Hai just smiled and had them download some content to their computer so that they could do something when they return to the Space.

After waiting for Laura and the others to be done, Zhao Hai sent them over to the Space along with Tinkle. But just as Tinkle entered the Space, a prompt was suddenly heard, “Robot from a high-rank Science and Technology civilization detected. Space upgraded to level 130. Host can now buy ten high-ranking science and technology backgrounds and 50 ordinary backgrounds. Since the robot has advanced wireless connection to its source civilization, the Space has now obtained the civilization’s advanced wireless network function.”

Zhao Hai stared for a moment before a wave of happiness washed over him. He had always wanted to make a network inside the Space. However, the computers had yet to become popular inside the Space. Moreover, he didn’t have any experience in making networks. He didn’t expect the Space to solve the problem for him.

However, Zhao Hai suddenly thought that the Space was now connected to the Machine Realm’s network. Did this mean that the Space was now exposed? When he thought about this, he immediately called Cai’er, “Cai’er, what does this mean? If the Space can connect to the outside world, then does this mean that the Space’s secret will soon be discovered?”

Cai’er smiled and said, “Young Master, there’s no need to worry. Although it can connect to the outside world’s network, the Space will not emit any signals. The Space can only receive information, it cannot send.”

Upon hearing Cai’er, Zhao Hai relaxed. Then his two eyes shone as he said, “Cai’er, can you connect to secret bases of the Machine Field and steal their secrets?”

Cai’er shook her head and said, “I’m afraid we can’t, Young Master. I just tried it. It seems like the Machine Field’s public network is just a place to play around. Real secrets aren’t connected to the public network and exist on isolated networks.”

Zhao Hao nodded. Although he felt helpless, he could also accept this fact. Nevertheless, this network would be extremely useful for the Space.

Turning his head to Cai’er, Zhao Hai said, “Cai’er, popularize the use of computers in the Space’s academies. Let everyone know about the Machine Field and let them see what kind of place it is.”

Cai’er nodded. Looking at the time, Zhao Hai said, “Alright, I need to head out. It wouldn’t be good if I stay here for longer.” Cai’er nodded. Then Zhao Hai returned to his room. After reorganizing his thoughts, he proceeded towards the cafeteria.

The Space’s connection to the internet was a crucial development for the people inside the Space. This connection became a bridge that allowed the people to be aware about the massive World of Cultivation outside.

Zhao Hai wasn’t afraid that these people would want to leave. Because of the Space’s benefits, it was already common sense for them to stay inside.

Compared to the intense competition in the Machine Field, the Space was incomparably peaceful and rich. How could someone from the Space think of leaving? At most, they would look at the situation outside as entertainment.

Even the people inside the Space couldn’t help but pity the people in the Machine Field. These people were going all out in order to become stronger. Average people were also working extremely hard.

The new technology was very helpful to Karen and the others. They can now get direct access to magic formations. This caused their research to be more relaxed than before. Being able to gain the Machine Field’s foundation had saved them a lot of trouble.

The only regrettable thing to all of this was the fact that the network was only limited to the Machine Field. Because of this, Zhao Hai was still blind about the situation of the other realms.

Chapter 1090: Monthly Examination

Time quickly passed by, and unknowingly, Zhao Hai was already in the Machine Field for one month. In this month, Dins and the others already passed the requirements and rose to the second floor classroom. Besides Zhao Hai, only two other ascenders were left on the first floor.

Ascending didn’t have a set time interval. Sometimes, there would be dozens of newcomers in one year, some years might even reach hundreds. But at the same time, there would also be times when only one person ascended. This situation was very normal.

The two other ascenders on the first floor were young men. Zhao Hai tried to talk to them but the two were full of vigilance towards him. Moreover, their arrogance was something that even Zhao Hai couldn’t bear. In the end, Zhao Hai can only give up on them and focused on condensing magic formations instead. At this point, the number of magic formations that Zhao Hai had managed to condense had reached 100 thousand. Moreover, this wasn’t the only improvement he had in this month. At this point, Zhao Hai can now condense 100 magic formations at the same time. And these 100 magic formations would be condensed in 5 minutes or so.

Although Dins and the others had moved to the second floor, they didn’t stop contacting Zhao Hai. The group ate their meals together almost every day. Naturally, Qi Yi would be part of this from time to time. Margaret also got in touch with Dins and the others to invite them to the Bone Symbol Camp. This caused the old men to feel relieved.

On the other hand, the time for Zhao Hai’s monthly examination came. As long as he passed this examination, he would then be able to rise to the second floor. Additionally, the metal plate would begin to function.

The magic formation on the metal plate would adjust the density of spiritual qi inside Zhao Hai’s body. This would enable him to slowly adjust to the Machine Field’s spiritual qi. When one year passes, he would then be able to fully adjust to the realm’s environment.

Zhao Hai was able to see the exam that Dins and the others underwent. However, upon seeing their exam, Zhao Hai was no longer sure what kind of exam he would face.

The exam that Dins and the others took was the same test that Margaret had given Zhao Hai on his second day. In other words, Zhao Hai had already passed the monthly exam in his second day. This made the monthly examination redundant. Zhao Hai believed that Margaret wouldn’t give him the same test.

Although he was wondering about what his test would be, Zhao Hai didn’t actually ask Margaret about it. He just continued to live his days on the first floor, either attending classes or staying inside his room condensing magic formations.

The day of the test quickly arrived. Zhao Hai punctually arrived in his classroom before 9 o’clock. This time, he didn’t bring his robots. The two were left behind his room accompanying Laura and the others.

Zhao Hai believed that Margaret would also arrive in time. And sure enough, Margaret entered the room at 9. When she saw Zhao Hai, Margaret just said, “Follow me.” Zhao Hai nodded and didn’t say anything.

Margaret was a quiet person and never said anything useless. Apart from giving lectures and answering questions, she generally kept quiet during classes. Zhao Hai was already used to her cold and quiet demeanor.

Although it can be said that Margaret only instructed him for three days, these three days were the most important days for Zhao Hai. This was because it was in these three days that Margaret opened up Zhao Hai’s path to being an Expert.

Magic Theory was very suitable to Zhao Hai’s cultivation method. As long as he had condensed a specific formation, he would no longer spend time in arranging it in the future since it would appear almost instantaneously. This also applies to layered formations.

Although Zhao Hai was condensing magic formations in these past several days, he didn’t relax when it comes to layering formations. Layering magic formations wasn’t as simple as putting one formation on top of another. Layered formation came in many types. The simplest one of them was layering two of the same formations. For example, if Zhao Hai layers his summoning magic formation, he wouldn’t need to spend a lot of time on it since there would be no conflicts between parts of the formation. Because of that, this type was said to be the simplest.

However, this arrangement also meant that this type of layered formation was the weakest. If it was in numerical terms, it was just adding one to one. The effect wasn’t amplified that much.

The most difficult layered formations were those who incorporated formations from multiple elements. Even layering two formations would prove difficult. But since this increased the resulting formation’s geometric structure, the magic formation would be very powerful.

In the Machine Field, there were people who tried to make the strongest layered formation using computers. However, there had yet to be any success.

Computers weren’t omnipotent. And even if it managed to calculate the strongest combination, the requirements to condense such formation would be extremely strict; to the point where no errors should happen during the entire process.

In the end, Mages were still people, they weren’t machines. Even machines had flaws, much less Mages. For a Mage to layer formations without a single error was borderline impossible.

Layered formations simulated by computers required perfection. As long as a single error appears, the formation would be rendered useless, it might even injure the Mage casting it. Because of this, the best layered formations in the Machine Field were those made by Mages who had battled for a long time. Moreover, starting from five to ten layered formations, these were deemed as a secret by Mages. They would only pass their formations down to their disciples or younger generations. It was impossible for these formations to be revealed to the public.

However, these things weren’t an issue for Zhao Hai. Inside the Space was the Universal Scanner. Although the scanner was still level 1, it was something that most computers couldn’t compare to. The biggest characteristic of the scanner was that it was made to cater to Zhao Hai’s needs. It can be said that everything inside the Space revolves around Zhao Hai, the scanner was not different. Because of this, Cai’er had the scanner analyze the formations that Zhao Hai condensed so far. At the same time, the scanner would create combinations that would suit Zhao Hai the most.

In addition to practicing Magic Theory, Zhao Hai was also trying to layer magic formations. At this point, he can now layer 100 magic formations together.

Zhao Hai and Margaret took the elevator and went up the building. There were some floors in the academy that weren’t open to the students. These floors were some of the most important facilities of the academy. Teachers usually lived on these floors.

They went through the uppermost floor of the academy and then to the platform on the roof. Parked on the platform was a small battleship that was shaped like a small bean. It had a rounded head and tail.

The entire battleship was 50 meters long and 20 meters wide. Painted on its side were four characters that spelled ‘Ascender Academy’

Seeing this battleship, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but gawk. He turned his head to Margaret and said, “Instructor, are we going outside?”

Margaret nodded and said, “There’s no point in testing you using the standards we use om the others. In the Ascender Academy, there would be ten tests per year. This first exam tests your knowledge of magic runes. The second tests if you can condense a formation. And then the third exam is a smelting trial outside the Academy.”

Zhao Hai frowned for a moment before he said, “I still haven’t adjusted to the concentration of spiritual qi. Is it alright for me to go outside?”

Margaret answered, “There’s no need to worry about that. The academy’s battleships are all modified to automatically adjust the concentration of energy. Also, the place that you’ll be going to will have less concentration of spiritual qi compared to normal. These tests are specially arranged for ascenders to undergo, the academy had prepared everything in advance. Your test this time is to go outside and eradicate a malicious ghost.”

Zhao Hai replied, “Malicious ghosts? Are they like the Lich?”

Margaret gave a nod and said, “There are similarities, but malicious ghosts aren’t the same as Lich. These malicious ghosts are stronger than the Lich from the lower realms. They not only use magic, they can also do physical attacks. For you who just learned Magic Theory, dealing with these things would be tough.”

Zhao Hai gave a nod. Margaret continued, “The place we’re going to is an area on the edge of the Machine Field. Its concentration of spiritual qi isn’t high, but there are still people living there. Moreover, it is an important sector for mithril mining. But because of the constant mining, it had become a place with rich yin energy. This caused the place to produce dark creatures. This place is also one of the smelting trials of the Machine Field’s academies. Besides you, there are also other ascenders undergoing their smelting trial in that place. Therefore, not only do you need to be wary of malicious ghosts, you also need to be vigilant against other ascenders.”

Zhao Hai gave another nod. At this time, they had arrived in front of the battleship’s door. Then door automatically opened and then closed when they entered. In front of Zhao Hai was a corridor. Margaret led Zhao Hai towards a door, then she said, “This will be your room. Don’t wander around aimlessly. The battleship has its own internal security system. If for some reason you end up inside forbidden areas, you will immediately be attacked by the ship.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he said, “Instructor Margaret, how long will it take us to reach our destination?”

Margaret answered, “In about three days. In these three days, people will come to deliver food to you. You can use the internet inside your room and you can also practice. It would be best if you don’t go out.” Zhao Hai nodded for the last time before he went inside his room.

The room wasn’t very big, only about 20 square meters. It had a bed, a table, a bathroom, and a sofa, nothing else.

But what made Zhao Hai surprised the most was that there was a window inside the room. Although it wasn’t big, he could still see the scenery outside.

Chapter 1091: 4th-level Talent

Zhao Hai sat by the window and looked outward. He didn’t know when the ship took off, he simply didn’t feel it moving. He couldn’t help but praise the technology of this world.

After looking at the window for some time, Zhao Hai turned away and faced his room before taking out a small device. The device was an anti-monitoring device that Qi Yi had made for him. It had the most advanced anti-surveillance technology in the Machine Feild. As long as a room had monitoring devices, this device would immediately issue an alarm before emitting an electromagnetic signal that causes the monitoring device to malfunction.

In the Machine Field, there were two ways to monitor a person. The first method was through monitoring devices. There were plenty of monitoring devices in the Machine Field, the same was true for anti-monitoring devices. But compared to monitoring devices, anti-monitoring devices were much easier to make.

Anti-monitoring devices were ingeniously crafted. As long as they emit their electromagnetic waves, they would certainly disturb any monitoring device in the vicinity. This way, the person who set-up the monitoring device wouldn’t be able to get anything.

Besides monitoring devices, the other method used to spy on other people was through magic. This method was difficult to guard against. Surveillance magic was generally very secretive and difficult to detect. However, Zhao Hai wasn’t really afraid of surveillance magic.

Zhao Hai’s spiritual force was very formidable. And with the existence of the Sace, monitoring him using magic was almost impossible. Because of this, Zhao Hai only needed to worry about monitoring devices for now.

Seeing that there were no monitoring devices inside his room, Zhao Hai began to feel relieved. His figure immediately flashed as he returned to his room back at the academy. Laura and the others were also inside his room, waiting for Zhao Hai to bring them information.

When they saw Zhao Hai come out from the Space, the women couldn’t help but stare. Then Laura stepped forward and said, “Brother Hai, why did you use the Space to come back? Are you starting your test? What kind of test is it?”

Zhao Hai smiled bitterly and said, “My test this time seems to be on a planet called Tyro, killing malicious ghosts. I won’t be taking it in the academy, you can go with me on the ship.”

As soon as they heard Zhao Hai, Laura and the others cheered before following Zhao Hai out of the Space. Zhao Hai also took the robot that Qi Yi had made for him. Zhao Hai named this robot ‘Number Nine’.[1]

Bringing Laura and the others as well as Number Nine to the ship made Zhao Hai’s room look cramped. However, they only stayed inside for a short while before they returned to the Space. In any case, if someone came to look for him, it wouldn’t be too late to head back to his room.

Upon returning to the Space, Zhao Hai let out a long breath before going to the hot spring to take a nice bath. When he returned to the living room, Meg had already prepared a delicious meal for him.

Zhao Hai hadn’t entered the Space recently since he needed to adapt to the environment outside. Now that he had returned to the Space, he can finally relax.

After eating, Zhao Hai went on to condense magic formations at the side. Meanwhile, Laura and the others were browsing the internet. There wasn’t anything wrong with the Space, Laura and the others just preferred to stay beside Zhao Hai. They spent most of their time going to Zhao Hai’s room to accompany him.

Zhao Hai also understood their feelings. Therefore, he would accompany them while condensing his magic formations. Zhao Hai can spend more time with Laura and the others since he now has more control over his spiritual force.

Currently, Zhao Hai had already condensed nearly a hundred thousand magic formations. He had also gathered several hundred magic formations combinations. These combinations had been provided by the scanner. The least powerful combination he had composed of five layers while the most powerful one was actually a hundred layers.

A hundred layered formation was a symbol for level 4 Mages. There were only a small amount of people who had reached this stage in the Machine Field. If people become aware that Zhao Hai, who has yet to graduate from the academy, could use a hundred layer formation, they would certainly die from shock.

However, wanting to use the scanner to analyze formations with more layers would be impossible. This was because the Universal Scanner was still level 1. The most it could do was 100 layers.

Zhao Hai also accessed the net to look at how strong hundred-layer formations were. Take a small fireball for example. On its own, it was a weak magic. Even if Zhao Hai reached his current level, his fireball still wasn’t strong. At the most, the fireball would be as strong as an anti-tank grenade.

However, after passing through a hundred-layer formation, its might would become similar to a missile. Killing several hundred people with it wouldn’t be a problem.

The current issue for Zhao Hai at this moment was how to upgrade the Scanner. Only when the Scanner gets upgraded would his strength increase.

But as he was worrying about this, Zhao Hai discovered something. His spiritual force was just enough to use a hundred-layer formation. If he used anything more than that, his spiritual force would be extremely stressed out.

Because of this, there was no point for Zhao Hai to worry about upgrading the Scanner. Even if the Scanner could analyze more powerful formations, Zhao Hai still wouldn’t be able to use them.

Although Zhao Hai’s body was being constantly improved by the Stellar Transformations Art, it was still not enough for him to use magic with more layers.

Of course, Zhao Hai wouldn’t idle because of this. Besides condensing formations as well as trying to compile formation combinations, Zhao Hai also did one other thing. He was looking into how Warriors in the Machine Realm fight.

In the Machine Field, combat methods of Warriors were very simple. They just need to increase the energy inside their body and then their groups would provide them with corresponding weapons. However, these weapons were different than what Warriors from the lower realms used. These weapons were specially made in the Machine Field to contain magic formations. These formations allowed the energy inside a Warrior’s body to concentrate so that they could send it out.

Warriors in the lower realm would use their energy in order to coat their weapons, making them sharper. On the other hand, Warriors in the Machine Field can actually send their sword qi out, providing them with long-ranged attack.

Moreover, the sword qi that was sent out would be supported by the formation inside the weapon, increasing its attacking power. But in the end, how far the sword qi would travel still depended on the user’s strength. It was said that there was once a legendary Warrior in the Machine Field that used his sword to slaughter his enemies in all directions unhindered.

Although this legend might be fake, Zhao Hai still took it with caution. He had already found some magic formations used for engraving weapons. After having it go through the scanner and then combining it into a hundred-layer formation, Zhao Hai had it engraved on his staff. This would be another one of his cards in the future.

Zhao Hai also conducted tests inside the Space. He used his staff and turned it into a sword in order to send a sword qi out into the distance. His sword qi reached ten thousand meters, which was equal to a level 4 Warrior. After testing both paths, Zhao Hai can confirm that his strength was indeed at level 4.

The current strongest being in the Machine Field was about level 8. Being only level 4, Zhao Hai still fell short.

However, if people from the Machine Realm knew that Zhao Hai had level 4 strength, they would certainly be startled. This was because, generally, lower realm ascenders would at most only reach level two upon graduating. There were a minority that reached level three, but never level 4.

Zhao Hai was constantly condensing magic formations inside the Space, he was also familiarizing himself with arranging layered formations. Although he can now use hundred-layer formations in almost a flash, he would still need to practice on it for a long time.

Being able to use layered formations wasn’t a direct indicator of a person’s strength. Layered formations were just like weapons, some were like spears, some were like shields. As long as one practices to the point where they knew the most appropriate way to use formations, only then would they effectively grasp its power.

At this point, Zhao Hai’s everyday program has been arranged. Besides eating and sleeping, he spent most of his day practicing his layered formations while also practicing how to launch his sword qi.

Zhao Hai had just discovered why the swordsmanship in the Machine Field was so strong. This was because he can attach a bit of his spiritual force on the qi as it was launched. This allowed him to make the sword qi change directions.

This skill was new to Zhao Hai, so he needed to digest how to use it effectively. Zhao Hai was very clear that these things would be the basis of his survival in the Machine Field.

Although it looks like Laura and the others were leisurely browsing the internet, Zhao Hai actually knew that they were scouring for information. They were looking for things related to the Cultivation Realm as well as any methods to make the Undead stronger.

Even if there were a lot of information that were deemed confidential in the Machine Field. Information that was public was already enough for Zhao Hai and the others to use.

Information about Magic Theory, magic formations, alchemy, and other disciplines were definitely useful. This was especially true for alchemy.

Although Warriors still had their weapons in the Machine Field, lower realm magic staffs and magic potions were useless to Mages. However, Mages still had their weapons. The first of these weapons were magic staffs. Magic Theory was different than magic formations in the lower realms. According to their spiritual force, Mages in the machine field were able to engrave a number of magic formations on their staff.

* * *

Don’t know why it was named like that.

Chapter 1092: Tyro Planet’s Mining City

Engraving magic formations on their staffs allowed Mages to bypass using the void condensing technique. This way, they could launch magical spells instantly, strengthening a mage’s combat ability.

However, the more magic formations they engrave on their staffs, the more spiritual force they would need. Therefore, the number of magic formations a Mage could engrave was limited by their own strength. If they engrave too many, they wouldn’t be able to cast it. Their magic staff would burn and become useless trash.

This was also the difference between using staffs and using the void condensing magic formation technique. Magic formations from staffs required spiritual force to start. On the other hand, formations using the void condensing technique were already condensed using spiritual force. Because of this, there was no need for it to be started with spiritual force.

Besides magic staffs, there were also magic potions. Magic Potions had more uses in the Machine Field compared to the lower realms. In the lower realms, magic potions would generally heal wounds or enhance cultivation. But in the Machine Field, the most popular magic potion could rapidly restore one’s spiritual force.

It was normal for Mages to run out of spiritual force during a fight. And once their spiritual force dries up, they wouldn’t be able to cast magic formations, putting them in a dangerous position.

Having magic potions that can restore a significant amount of spiritual force greatly enhanced the capabilities of the Mages in the Machine Field. Ths allowed Mages to have more avenues for survival.

………………………….

For someone who was focused on their job, three days would quickly fly by. In these three days, aside from having his meals inside his room, he would practice and rest inside the Space.

On the third day, Zhao Hai left the Space and spent the entire time inside his room. He was afraid that Margaret would look for him. Therefore, he decided to wait for her inside his room. Although he came out of the Space, Zhao Hai still continued his nonstop condensing of magic formations. He can now condense more than 10 thousand formations at the same time.

After some time, while Zhao Hai was condensing formations, two faint knocks were heard on the door. Zhao Hai immediately got up and opened the door to see Margaret on the other side.

Margaret looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Come with me to the hall. We’re about to arrive at our destination.”

Zhao Hao nodded, then he followed behind Margaret. Normally, people couldn’t casually go inside the ship’s command hall. Of course, Zhao Hai wasn’t aware of this rule since he stayed inside his room all this time. But since he can monitor the ship using the Space, he was able to find out that Margaret’s status wasn’t simple. Even the ship’s commander was very respectful to her.

Meanwhile, Margaret was thinking that Zhao Hai wasn’t only a genius and a clever person, he was also very patient. For three days, he was able to stay inside his room without leaving. Because of this, Margaret began to favor Zhao Hai.

From what Margaret had experienced, most people would be restless after entering a ship for the first time. On the other hand, Zhao Hai didn’t have such restlessness. He didn’t even seem to be curious as he just stayed inside his room. Such willpower made Margaret look at Zhao Hai in a favorable light.

The two quickly arrived at the ship’s command hall. The room wasn’t very large, it was only around a hundred square meters. There were about a dozen people inside operating the ship. However, these people didn’t look busy. Most of them had cups of tea on their hands as they chatted with each other.

In the middle of the hall was a table with a couple of chairs. Sitting behind the table was a man about 40 years old. He had a neat appearance and also held a teacup on one hand. Meanwhile, displayed on his table was the view outside the ship. A planet was getting bigger and bigger on the display, showing that the ship was getting closer. This man was the ship’s commander.

Seeing the two arrive, the commander quickly stood up and greeted Margaret, “Instructor Margaret.”

Margaret nodded, then she gestured towards Zhao Hai and said, “This is Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai, this is the ship’s commander, Kirk.”

Zhao Hai gave Kirk a salute, the latter did the same. During this exchange, the other people inside the ship were looking at Zhao Hai with curiosity.

Zhao Hai didn’t particularly care about their curiosity. Among everyone here, only Margaret and him had mage robes, showing that she was an academy instructor and he was the student. Therefore, it wouldn’t be strange if these people were curious about him.

Margaret arrived by the commander’s table and looked at the planet that was getting closer and closer. The planet was black and yellow. Zhao Hai came to know that this black part was actually the planet’s oceans. Instead of being blue, the planet’s waters were actually black. On the other hand, its lands were yellow. Scattered on these yellow lands were weeds. Moreover, there was no drinkable water on this planet, making it inhospitable.

The main reason why humans chose to develop this planet was because it had something that they need, Mithril!

This mithril was different than mithril found in the lower realm. In the lower realms, mithril was just a metal with magical properties. Mages wouldn’t necessarily make use of it. But in the Machine Field, mithril wasn’t just something used by Mages, it was something that they cannot separate themselves from.

In the Machine Field, mithril was a material with high conductivity. Whether it was magic or battle qi, both needed good conduction materials for their weapons. Therefore, both magic staffs and weapons couldn’t be made without mithril.

In the beginning, Tyro planet only had miners operating in its mines. They lived inside tunnels and rarely went above ground. This was because the planet had a lot of powerful magic beasts. In addition, the plants and even the planet’s water were toxic. These beasts had been eating and drinking these things while growing up, making them poisonous themselves. As long as they cut your skin, you’ve basically forfeited your life.

Afterwards, major powers from the Machine Field decided to develop the planet, establishing permanent residences. In these residences were water filtration systems as well as food manufacturing facilities. Although these residences were still inside tunnels, they gradually formed underground cities. Most people inside these residences were still miners, but their families also took residence in the planet.

At this time, besides its mining industry, Tyro planet also had a special tourism sector. They allowed tourists to explore the mines and stay in specially made tunnel hotels. There were also services that allowed people safe travel aboveground to kill the local poisonous beasts.

Tyro planet wasn’t owned by any of the three major forces. Although those forces would want to swallow the planet, because of the other two, nobody was able to succeed. In the end, they granted Tyro planet its own independence. The planet would trade its ores for machine coins and other supplies from the three powers. Although the job was hard, the miners could earn a lot. It wouldn’t be strange for a miner to be rich after working here for more than ten years.

Although the tunnels in Tyro planet were safe, the areas where the miners work in weren’t. The underground had poisonous beasts as well as malicious ghosts. But since their population was little, and the density of spiritual qi was small, it wouldn’t be worth it if an army was stationed here all the time. Therefore, the tasks of eradicating this danger was handed over to the academies.

This information wasn’t something that Zhao Hai looked up, instead it was Laura and the others who found out about it.

Zhao Hai wasn’t too concerned about this mission. With the density of spiritual qi not being strong, it would be impossible for powerful creatures to emerge from this place.

Although the ship seemed slow, it was actually approaching the planet quickly. But as it got closer to the planet’s atmosphere, the ship began to slow down.

As soon as they entered Tyro planet, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but stare. The place was really desolate, there was an endless number of yellow rocks as far as the eye could see. Growing on the cracks on the ground and the rocks were grasses and shrubs. These plants were similarly colored as the rocks, yellowish.

One could often see beasts roaming the surface or fighting for food. Zhao Hai couldn’t see even a shadow of human civilization.

At this time, the spaceship descended on an enormous crater. It was at least a kilometer wide and was too dark to be able to see what was inside.

The ship slowly descended. Its speed got slower and slower and in about ten minutes, Zhao Hai discovered a beeping light. Then a staff turned towards Kirk and said, “Captain, a communication request.” Kirk nodded and said, “Accept it.”

Then the staff member nodded before tapping the desktop. Before long, an image of a person about 30 years old appeared. He appeared refined as he bowed and said, “Welcome, friends from the Ascender Academy. I am the station master of Tyro Planet’s space port. Please follow the lights as you land your ship on port number five. Thank you in advance for cooperating.”

Kirk gave a saute and said, “Yes, Station Master.” Then the image vanished. Shortly after that, lights appeared, showing signals to lead the ship to its landing point.

After the ship landed successfully, Margaret led Zhao Hai to exit the ship. On the other hand, the staff on the ship actually stayed. They still needed to settle things on the ship before they could leave.

As Margaret led Zhao Hai out of the ship,  someone was already waiting for them outside. He was an old man with white hair and beard. Surprisingly, this person was wearing mage robes.

After seeing Margaret and Zhao Hai, the old man immediately bowed and said, “Instructor Margaret, welcome. Please follow me.” Margaret returned the greeting and said, “Mister Sim is too polite.” Then the three proceeded towards nearby car. The car was quite big. It had four rows of seats. Margaret and Sim were on the second row while Zhao Hai was sitting alone on the third row.

The vehicle also had tea for its passengers. After going in, Sim offered Margaret and Zhao Hai a cup each. Then he opened his mouth and said, “To the Academy Reception.” Zhao Hai knew that those words were meant for the computer driving the car. Just as Sim’s voice was heard, the car immediately moved.

At this time, Sim turned to Margaret and said, “Instructor Margaret. I apologize for the trouble. Is this the only student that will take the trial?” Margaret placed her cup next to her chair and then nodded, “Yes, this time, only Zhao Hai will participate in the exam. In addition to our academy, who else is here?” Sim lowered his voice as he replied, “In addition to your academy, there’s also the Adam family’s academy as well as the Wild academy. Altogether, they brought ten people for the trial. The Adam Academy brought six people while the Wild Academy brought four.”

Upon hearing the names of these two academies, Margaret couldn’t help but knit her brows. She didn’t say anything and just nodded. At this moment, the car stopped. The cave in front of them had ten layers overall. It looked like a ten-story building, but instead of floors it was made out of holes.

Besides the entrance and the exit, as well as the glass windows, the entire cave was made out of stone. It was a space of about a thousand square meters. There were already several cars parked inside.

Exiting the vehicle, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but inspect the surroundings. The place was very lively, completely uncharacteristic of a mining tunnel. It was more than 200 meters high. On its ceiling were magic formations that provided light. Aside from the columns, the other places were places where people live in. There were also flying cars going in and out. The street was full of traffic. The neon signs on the shops added to the liveliness of the place.

If this wasn’t a mining tunnel, it wouldn’t have been different to a city. But since it was a mining tunnel, instead of buildings, people dug into holes. Because of this, the place exuded a unique characteristic.

Zhao Hai just gave the area a glance before he followed behind Margaret and Sim towards the reception. As soon as they entered, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but stare for a moment. The inside was beautifully renovated. There was a bar inside the hall and even a lounge to relax. Carpet covered the floors and beautiful wallpapers plastered the walls.

Chapter 1093: Provocation from the Adam Academy

The cave was actually this beautiful. Zhao Hai didn’t expect this. If he didn’t see what it was like outside, he would’ve thought that he had just entered a hotel.

Sim, Zhao Hai, and Margaret proceeded to the counter. Behind this counter wasn’t a human, instead it was a robot. Sim said, “Bring the room card prepared for the Ashley Ascender Academy.”

The robot nodded before pulling out two cards and handed them over to Sim. After receiving the two cards, Sim gave them to Margaret and said, “Instructor Margaret, these are the rooms prepared for your academy. Please take a rest first.”

Margaret took the room cards and then gave a polite nod, “Thank you, Mister Sim.” After that, Margaret led Zhao Hai towards their room.

Just as the two arrived in front of the elevator, the elevator doors suddenly opened. On the other side of the doors were seven people wearing mage robes. This group ranged from young to old. At the center of the group was a middle-aged man. This man was very thin with a mouse-like moustache. He looks particularly annoying.

The man had expensive-looking golden yellow mage robes. Seeing this person, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but stare. The man was one of the very rare metal element Mages.

There wasn’t any magic for the metal element in the lower realms. Only people born in the Machine Field would have a talent in this area. Moreover, it was recognized by many people that metal magic was the hardest to deal with.

Naturally, this didn’t mean that the other magic elements were inferior to the metal element. Their might also depended on the Mage’s ability. Even if one had a peerlessly good sword, if it fell into the hands of an idiot, it was still impossible for the idiot to use the weapon’s might. Magic was also the same. It was just that metal element Mages were rare than Mages from other elements. And with the metal element’s strong attack and defensive magic, it was considered as the element that was the hardest to deal with.

In the past few days, Zhao Hai had also consumed knowledge about metal element magic. However, he was left disappointed. There wasn’t anything special about metal element magic. It was just like any other magic in the Machine Field. It was only because metal element magic required a special physique that it was very rare.

Actually, one could study metal element magic in the lower realm. As long as one has physique compatible with metal element magic, they were able to study metal element magic.

People in the lower realms with metal element physique were heaven defying beings. Although they didn’t have any cultivation methods, their bodies alone made them formidable. Therefore, they were slowly able to make their mark on society. In the Ark Continent, they were known as Divergent ability users. It was just a pity that there weren’t any cultivation methods for the metal element. Or else there would be metal element Mages in the lower realm.

Behind this Metal element Mage were six other Mages. The ages of these people were greatly varied. The oldest of them already had white hair while the youngest seems to be nearing 30 years old. Their expressions were also varied. The old Mage had a gloomy look as though he had lost interest in everything. Dins and the others had this same look in the past.

As for the youngest Mage, he looked very arrogant, just like the Mage Frey that Zhao Hai ran into. Seeing these expressions, it seems like the Ascender Academies had the same atmospheres.

Still, Zhao Hai didn’t say anything. He didn’t want to make any contact with these people. After all, he wasn’t a saint. If he wasn’t trying to survive in the academy, he might not even care about Dins and the others.

In such an unfamiliar environment, it was unwise to meddle in other people’s business. It wouldn’t bring you any benefits, only risks.

Zhao Hai didn’t plan to meddle with these people, but the other party actually stopped after going out of the elevator. With the thin Mage at the lead, he looked at Margaret with shining eyes. It seems like he was harboring evil intentions.

This caused Zhao Hai’s heart to sink. Zhao Hai was able to see Margaret’s reaction when Sim told her about the other academies present. Seeing the expression on the thin Mage’s face, it seems like there was going to be a confrontation.

The thin Mage looked at Margaret and suddenly smiled, “Margaret, I didn’t expect your academy to send you for the exam. Generally, it was those old turtles who would come here. Seeing you is rare, really rare.”

Margaret looked at the Mage, and with a cold voice she replied, “Jin Changji, why are you talking to me with your stinky mouth? Want me to teach you a lesson?”

It was obvious that this Jin Changji somewhat dreaded Margaret. After a brief pause, he coldly snorted and said, “Margaret, don’t forget where this is. This isn’t your academy. If you dared to make a move here, then if not me, other people will deal with you. Right, it seems like your academy’s talents have gotten less and less. This time, only one came to take the exam. What a pity.”

Margaret jus coldly snorted and didn’t say anything else. Then she turned and entered the elevator. All this time, Zhao Hai stayed silent and just followed Margaret to the elevator. Seeing that Margaret didn’t care about him, Jin Changji coldly snorted, then he led the other mages forward.

Sim arranged the Ashley Family academy to be on the eighth floor. After Margaret settled things in her own room, she entered Zhao Hai’s.

Zhao Hai quickly invited Margaret to take a seat and then offered her a cup of tea. He then sat opposite Margaret, he knew that she had something to say, so he waited.

Sure enough, Margaret looked at Zhao Hai and said, “You should have heard what Sim said. In addition to our academy, there’s also the Adam Academy and the Wild Academy. Wild Academy is an institute for warriors, they have no conflict of interest with us. The Northfield Family behind even has a friendly relationship with the Ashley Family. Therefore, you don’t have to worry about them.”

Zhao Hai nodded. He wasn’t quite clear about the relationship between various influences in the Machine Field. Although he had looked things up on the internet, he couldn’t believe anything online.

Margaret continued, “However, you need to pay attention to the Adam Academy. Behind the academy is the Adam Family. Our two families have a grudge against each other. Because of this, no matter which academy, if an extraordinary talent emerges, the other party would do their best to exterminate that talent. This time, Jin Changji saw you, he should be aware that you will be joining the Ashley Family. They have six people this time, so they will definitely try to make a move during the exam. You need to be careful.” Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Rest assured, I will pay attention to them.”

Margaret sighed, “I didn’t want you to do the trial at this time, but your strength has already reached this level. It would be useless to let you learn the basics. Even though the Bone Symbol Camp didn’t employ brutal training methods, exams like these are inevitable in the academy. And you can only join the camp after you pass the exam. In this exam, the most dangerous ones aren’t the beasts and malicious ghosts. Instead, you need to be alert against those who will take the exam with you. You won’t know when they’ll make a move, so don’t trust anyone. If necessary, kill them. Understand?”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Yes, I understand.”

Margaret gave a nod, then she added, “Take a good rest. Sim will tell you about the contents of the exam tomorrow. You should prepare as well. You can go outside and buy things that you need. The money you have on your ID card can be used here as well.”

Seeing Zhao Hai nod, Margaret turned and left the room. Zhao Hai immediately used his anti-surveillance device to see if there were any monitoring devices inside the room. Sure enough, he was able to discover monitoring devices. Moreover, it seems like these devices weren’t installed recently. This caused Zhao Hai to be curious.

After removing the monitoring devices, Zhao Hai took a good look at his room. The place wasn’t very big. There were only two rooms; a living room and then a small bedroom that had a bathroom inside.

Zhao Hai knew that Margaret was just next door. Moreover, the soundproofing wasn’t good. Because of this, Zhao Hai didn’t make Laura and the others come out. Instead, he went to his bedroom, pulled down the curtains, and then entered the Space.

After returning to the Space, Zhao Hai immediately started cultivating. He just discovered that the exam might be more dangerous than he imagined. Because of this, he needed to be more familiar with his strength as soon as possible.

Condensing magic formations, experimenting with magic formation combinations, and even trying out sword qi. Zhao Hai’s workload has increased.

Although Laura and the others felt worried about Zhao Hai, they didn’t stop him. They knew that Zhao Hai’s hard work would only make their lives in the Machine Field much better and comfortable.

Because of this, they decided to be diligent in handling Zhao Hai’s other affairs. They made sure that Zhao Hai ate well, rest well, and was always at his optimum condition.

After practicing for several hours, Zhao Hai proceeded to take a rest. He will understand the contents of the exam tomorrow. Perhaps, it might even start immediately. Zhao Hai didn’t dare to tire himself out at this time since it would affect his condition tomorrow.

Chapter 1094: Killing Intent from Slaughtering a Million People

The academy reception looked similar to any commercial hotel. And in addition to rooms, there were also areas that allowed Mages and Warriors to practice as well as conference rooms.

This conference room wasn’t the room with a round table that normal people might think. Instead, this room looked more like a classroom. There was one person in front while the others sat on the chairs.

Sim was standing in front of the room while Zhao Hai and the others sat on the chairs. Besides Zhao Hai and Margaret, Jin Changji’s group of seven was also present. In addition, there were also five people that looked like Warriors. They were people from the Wild Academy.

Just like Margaret said, the people from the Wild Academy were very polite to them. Just as they entered the conference room, their Instructor greeted Margaret and shared a few words with her.

When everyone had sat down, Sim gestured towards the wall behind him. On the wall was a stretch of map. In this map were dazzling amounts of mining tunnels.

Fortunately, in this cobweb of a mining network, there were green lines that ran through them. There were also tunnels that had red lines and red dots.

Sim referred to the red lines and said, “These are old mining tunnels. Malicious ghosts appeared in these tunnels before so we send people to check them often. As soon as a malicious ghost is spotted, we will immediately inform the academies so that they can send people to destroy them.”

After that, Sim pointed at the red dots and said ,”In this particular tunnel, malicious ghosts and creatures frequently appear. We don’t know what is going on inside. What we know is that some severe change occurred and some Undead creatures appeared. Sometimes, mutant beasts appear as well. At this time, there are five malicious ghosts and more than 100 Undead inside. We haven’t fully explored the tunnel so we cannot rule out other dangers.”

Margaret wrinkled her brow and said, “Mister Sim, how long has it been since you explored this tunnel? Why are there so many malicious ghosts?”

Sim immediately answered, “We explore the tunnels every other month. It isn’t necessary  that these malicious ghosts were produced in this tunnel. They can come from other tunnels and just ran here. This tunnel is very big and the dark energy inside it is strong, very suitable for dark creatures to live in. I think it’s because of this reason that there are so many malicious ghosts.”

Margaret nodded and said, “Is it necessary to be in teams during this exam?”

Sim shook his head and said, “This old man wouldn’t require that. It depends on the arrangement your academies make. If you want to team up, then you can do so. It would also be fine to do the exam alone.”

Margaret frowned, “Aren’t all those malicious ghosts inside the same tunnel? How can one take the exam alone?”

Sim forced a smile and said, “Instructor Margaret, I think you misunderstood. This tunnel is very big, it isn’t smaller than a mining city. In fact, this tunnel was intended to be used to make a mining city. Because of this, there are holes in this tunnel that led to other tunnels. It can be said that this cave tunnel extends in all directions, like a maze. Teams might have more trouble catching a malicious ghosts, but they are safer. On the other hand, those who are alone might find malicious ghosts easier, but they are in more danger..”

Hearing Sim’s words, Margaret understood what he meant. Whether it was Sim or Margaret or the others, they all knew that the most dangerous element in this exam weren’t the malicious ghosts, it was the other examinees. Because of this, going in a team was much more dangerous than going alone.

At this time, Jin Changji coldly snorted and said, “Some people really want to take advantage of others once they see their only candidate in trouble. Our Adam Academy already has six people as a team. We can’t have any more people enter.”

Anger flashed in Margaret’s eyes. However, she didn’t show her anger. She was just asking what being in a team meant. Taking the exam in a team and taking it individually was different. Teams weren’t allowed to attack each other. Margaret also wasn’t aware of Zhao Hai’s current strength. In her mind, Zhao Hai was at most a 1st level Mage. Being able to layer five formations would already be good for him. But with his current strength, entering the exam without a team would be dangerous.

Now, after Jin Changji spoke, it was impossible for Margaret to prepare a team. She couldn’t help but sigh. Zhao Hai was the best talent that the Bone Symbol Camp had seen in many years. She didn’t really want to lose Zhao Hai in this exam.

As she sighed, Margaret began to have thoughts about withdrawing Zhao Hai from this examination. However, she knew that it would be impossible. Once people entered the examination area, participants were no longer able to withdraw. It was even impossible to admit defeat ahead of time.

Margaret began to blame herself for not preparing enough. She should have investigated the exam in advance. She didn’t expect to run into the Adam Academy. Zhao Hai might get unlucky this time.

However, since things had developed up to this point, Margaret can no longer back down. Margaret just snorted as she stood up and approached the Wild Academy’s leader and said, “Hello, Mister Dan, how about forming an alliance with my academy?”

The Wild Academy’s instructor couldn’t help but gawk upon hearing Margaret. Then he turned his head towards Jin Changji. Normally, he would agree to Margaret’s request. After all, a Mage-Warrior team could display even bigger might.

But this time, the Adam Academy was present, and they brought six people with them. On the other hand, the Wild Academy only had four examinees. The Ashely Academy and the Adam Academy had a grudge against each other. Having Zhao Hai with them would definitely bring danger the Wild Academy team.

After seeing the expression on Instructor Dan’s face, Margaret’s heart couldn’t help but sink. She knew what he was thinking. However, Margaret couldn’t  blame him, so before Dan could answer, Margaret just nodded and said, “It’s fine if Instructor doesn’t want to.” Then she turned around and left, incurring Jin Changji’s ridicule.

Seeing the look on Jin Changji’s eyes, Zhao Hai turned his head to Margaret and whispered, “Instructor, will it be a problem if too many people die in the tunnels?”

After hearing Zhao Hai, Margaret couldn’t help but stare. Then she turned to look at Zhao Hai. Although Zhao Hai’s smile stayed the same, Margaret’s heart turned cold.

Margaret knew that Zhao Hai was intending to kill upon hearing his words. However, no killing intent can be felt from Zhao Hai’s body. His body language seemed as if he was talking to a friend. This kind of performance showed that Zhao Hai had been killing people in the lower realm.

The more one kills, the heavier a person’s killing aura would be. If one killed 100 people, the killing aura on their body would be very heavy. If ordinary people met them, the killing aura would be enough to frighten them. However, once one killed more than a million people, they would be able to learn how to hide their killing intent. Even if they killed, they wouldn’t exude any intention of murder.

It can be said that if a person can hide their killing intent well, then they were definitely butchers, people who killed a million people!

Margaret had seen a lot of devils that have ascended from the lower realms. However, these people were still far from killing a million people. These people couldn’t hide their killing aura. In Margaret’s case, she only saw one person who was able to hide their killing aura. This person was a core member of the Ashely family who had went to the six realm’s battlefield for many years. People who came back from this smelting trial became extremely powerful. But even so, this person would still show his killing aura once he lost his temper. He was unlike Zhao Hai could completely hide his killing aura.

This only meant that Zhao Hai hadn’t just killed a million people!

Thinking about this number was terrifying. One person killing a million people, what was this concept? Average people would have long turned insane from killing this much people. And now, Zhao Hai seemed like a normal person. He even gave people a very sunny feeling. Such a person was actually scary, he was certainly an abnormal character.

Zhao Hai didn’t expect that his few words would invoke this many thoughts from Margaret. If he knew about Margaret’s thoughts about his killing aura, he would definitely be rendered speechless.

Margaret’s thoughts ended in an instant, then she replied, “No, there would be no problem if you kill those people.” Zhao Hai nodded.

At this time, Sim looked at Margaret with sympathy. Then he turned his head to the others and said, “There are more than a dozen entrances to this tunnel. Will everyone go together or separately?”

Although Margaret knew that Zhao Hai had killed a lot of people, she still wasn’t assured about his strength. So she was the first to reply, “We’ll be going on our own.” Sim nodded and then looked at the Adam Academy and the Wild Academy. The two also chose to leave separately.

Sim nodded and said, “Alright, then you three groups should prepare things and then eat. I will arrange three cars for you. These cars will send you down the tunnel and wait for your return. Although we can’t see what happens in the tunnel, our people had set up an alarm inside it. Once you kill the malicious ghosts and the undead, the alarm would stop. We will then come and inform you that the exam is over. You have three hours to prepare. After three hours, come back here and I will lead you to your cars.”

Chapter 1095: Like Watching a Horror Film

Zhao Hai calmly sat inside the moving car. The vehicle he was riding on was modified with thick armor. But besides that, the inside of the car didn’t have too much change. The seats of the car could be levelled, allowing a person to lie down and rest. There was also a machine inside that automatically served tea.

While drinking tea, Zhao Hai used his spiritual force in order to examine the situation outside. In fact, the technique that he used was the same technique that was widely utilized in the Underworld. Because of this, he was quite familiar with it.

He didn’t release his flying needles because he didn’t know how people were monitoring this exam. It wouldn’t be good if a Master came and saw the flying needles. Being in a strange environment, Zhao Hai needed to keep his cards secret as long as possible.

The car was very fast and agile. After flying for more than three hours, the car entered the tunnel that Sim described.

As soon as he entered the mine, Zhao Hai’s brows couldn’t help but jump. This was because there was a lot of dark energy inside. The dark energy was very strong. Although it was incomparable to the Underworld’s level, on a planet with thin spiritual qi, it was still a strange phenomenon.

The speeding car advanced without slowing down. However, the lights coming from the front seemed to stop short. Zhao Hai knew that this wasn’t because of the car’s lights. The place just had a very thick dark energy, affecting the distance illuminated by the light.

Zhao Hai felt the dark energy around him and discovered that this energy was different than the one present in the Underworld. The dark energy in the Underworld was calm and pure. On the other hand, the dark energy here had a wild property to it. It can be compared to an angered magic beast.

Zhao Hai knit his brows. He knew that dark energy with this wild characteristic couldn’t grow docile creatures. No wonder malicious ghosts were present here, so it was because of this.

Although Zhao Hai had some concerns about other things, he wasn’t worried about the dark creatures present here. He had been too exposed to dark energy that he had already familiarized himself with it. The dark energy here might be different, but it didn’t affect Zhao Hai at all.

After nearly another hour, the speeding car stopped. Once he was out, Zhao Hai swept the surroundings with his spiritual force. He had arrived at a fairly huge space, it should be a major mining tunnel. It wasn’t any smaller than the mining city that Zhao Hai just came from.

Zhao Hai didn’t stay by the speeding car for long. He quickly flew towards the tunnel. HIs spiritual force also scanned the surroundings. He wanted to see exactly how large the tunnel was.

With Zhao Hai’s spiritual strength, this wasn’t a difficult thing to do. His spiritual strength has been fully developed in the Underworld and could be sent thousands of kilometers away.

This was also the special characteristic of those who live in the Underworld. Because they weren’t able to see anything, creatures in the Underworld needed to use their spiritual force instead of their eyes. Developing their spiritual force was very important.

Zhao Hai stayed in the Underworld for quite some time. In addition to his already formidable spiritual force, his stay in the Underworld made his spiritual force even stronger.

At this point, most Mages at the same level couldn’t defeat Zhao Hai’s spiritual force. And Zhao Hai had already reached level 4 as a Mage, he was considered as a minor expert.

Before long, Zhao Hai’s spiritual force covered the entire tunnel. The total space inside was quite large. There were a lot of small and large tunnels connected to it. Moreover, Zhao Hai already discovered the two other academy student teams inside the tunnels.

Zhao Hai swept one of the team with his spiritual force, they were the four Warriors from the Wild Academy. They had already withdrawn their weapons and formed a circle. The one in front carried a bright lamp.

He didn’t see anything wrong with what they were doing. After all, Warriors don’t have very strong spiritual force.

When Zhao Hai swept the Adam Academy with his spiritual force, he couldn’t help but smile. Although they came with six people, they weren’t grouped up. They were wary of each other and even held their own lamps.

Mages in a dark environment, but they were using lamps, weren’t they just making themselves a target? Warriors don’t have strong spiritual force, so it was understandable for them to use lamps. However, one shouldn’t forget that Warriors had formidable bodies. Even if an enemy gets close to them, they would still be able to defend themselves. As for Mages, they couldn’t achieve this point.

Mages were more suited to long-distance attacks. And with their weak bodies, illuminating themselves with lamps could only be described as courting death.

Fortunately, these Mages still had a bit of brain matter left. They arranged several layers of protective formations on their bodies. However, most protective formations shone. This might not be an issue in a well-lit environment, but in the dark, the shine from the formations just made them moving lighthouses.

Zhao Hai didn’t think about taking action against these people at this time. This was because he just discovered where the malicious ghosts and undead were. In addition to the malicious ghosts and the undead, Zhao Hai also found a few beasts. They were all inside small caves in the tunnel.

But what made Zhao Hai somewhat depressed was that the malicious ghosts and the Undead were very close to the Adam Academy’s students. Meanwhile, he was a bit far from them.

Zhao Hai didn’t know that this was actually because of Margaret’s request to Sim. Naturally, Margaret and Sim didn’t know where the malicious ghosts were. However, Sim can change where Zhao Hai would end up. Margaret requested Zhao Hai to be dropped far away from the Adam Academy. Therefore, the current situation happened.

Through the Space, Zhao Hai used a couple of jumps before arriving where the malicious ghosts were. However, he didn’t make a move. Instead, he waited for an opportunity.

Zhao Hai calculated that if the Adam Academy’s people were to continue going forward, it wouldn’t take long before they meet the malicious ghosts. Once both sides fight, Zhao Hai would see the Adam Academy’s level as well as the strength of the malicious ghosts.

If the malicious ghosts killed the Adam Academy students, then that would save Zhao Hai a lot of trouble. When Zhao Hai asked Margaret earlier, he was really intending to kill these Adam Academy students. Although they were both from the lower realms and didn’t share any enmity, Zhao Hai was certain that Jin Changji had instructed them to get rid of him once they meet in the tunnel. Zhao Hai wasn’t a saint, as long as a potential danger emerges, he will immediately eliminate it.

Zhao Hai had already dissolved into the dark energy around him. Even the malicious ghosts wouldn’t be able to sense his presence, much less the people from the Adam Academy.

Zhao Hai learned this move from the Lich. The Lich had the ability to transform the energy inside their body into dark energy and then integrate it with the Underworld’s dark mist. Actually, their bodies were still present during this time. Zhao Hai made adjustments on this trick so that he can use it for himself.

Before long, the Adam Academy’s students entered the territory of a malicious ghost. From what Zhao Hai sensed, this tunnel didn’t have five malicious ghosts, but seven. However, these seven ghosts weren’t in a group. They were in their own territories and there seems to be no evidence of a close alliance between them.

Each malicious ghosts had several undead as subordinates. However, these Undead weren’t only humanoid, there were also beasts among them.

When the group of Mages entered the malicious ghost’s territory, the malicious ghost immediately discovered their presence. The ghost proceeded to hide itself before sending out a loud shout. The shout was very sharp and ugly to hear. It was truly a ghost’s wail.

Hearing this ghost’s wail, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but knit his brows. This was because the ghost’s cry was actually a spiritual attack.

The malicious ghosts looked a bit like the Lich, they didn’t have physical bodies and were more ugly. They had horrific face and long fingernails. Zhao Hai didn’t expect them to look like this.

As the malicious ghost issued its loud cry, its undead subordinates also moved towards the group of Mages. Besides them, the other malicious ghosts also sent their subordinates over. The beasts inside the tunnel were beginning to move as well.

Although Zhao Hai wasn’t afraid of these things, he wasn’t planning to offer his help. He wanted to see how strong the Adam Academy’s students were.

Naturally, Adam Academy’s six Mages were able to hear the ghost’s cry. The group stopped before beginning to group up, but there were still some distance between them. Zhao Hai looked at their action and couldn’t help but laugh. They were already in a predicament yet they were still wary of each other. It would be difficult for them to survive at this rate.

When he thought of this, Zhao Hai’s figure flashed as he entered the Space. These ghosts were pretty sensitive to dark energy. Zhao Hai didn’t want to risk himself being discovered and keeping disaster from happening to the Adam Academy’s people.

As soon as Zhao Hai entered the Space, he saw Laura and the others looking at the monitor. Displayed on the screen was the situation with the malicious ghosts and the Adam Academy. The women were sitting there with a nervous expression.

Zhao Hai knew that they weren’t really worried about the Mages of the Adam Academy. They were looking at the scene as though they were looking at a horror film.

Zhao Hai coughed lightly, causing Laura and the others to jump in fright. Seeing their reaction, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but laugh. When Laura and the others saw Zhao Hai laughing at their frightened expressions, they couldn’t help but scold him in anger. After some time, the group sat down and looked at the monitor.

Although the Adam Academy students kept some distance from the others, they could still see each other. At this time, an old Mage waved his staff, causing a magic formation to appear followed by a burst of light. The light condensed into a light ball that illuminated the surrounding area.

Zhao Hai nodded, seeing that it was light magic, it seems like the old Mage was a Light element Mage. Moreover, he seems to be able to use Magic Theory.

The younger Mages saw the old Mage’s move and also cast their own magic. But since all of them weren’t Light element Mages or all-element Mages, they can only use lower realm light magic.

Zhao Hai actually gave a nod. In this mining tunnel, only light energy can suppress the dark energy. Although Magic Theory was more formidable than ordinary magic, only light magic could suppress dark magic. Moreover, it wasn’t a wise choice to use magic that one wasn’t familiar with.

Ascenders like Zhao Hai could use almost all elements from the lower realms. Even if they weren’t skilled, it still wouldn’t be difficult to use low-level magic from other elements.

At this time, knowing that your enemy was a dark creature, the best choice was to use light magic of the lower realms other than using unfamiliar magic from Magic Theory. At the very least, they could guarantee their own safety.

Seeing that the Mages had used light magic, the malicious ghost didn’t go forward and stayed hidden in the darkness. Its mouth cried time and time again. Besides being a spiritual attack, this cry also instructed its subordinates to charge towards the enemy.

The ghosts’ subordinates were Undead, so they also have an innate fear of light magic. However, they couldn’t hold back the command of the ghosts, the only thing they could do was to slowly move forward.

When the Undead got in contact with the light element magic, their bodies immediately emitted black gas. Each Undead gave out a pitiful yell as their bodies slowly dissolved.

The Adam Academy’s students relaxed when they saw this happening. The magic in their hands went past the Undead but they weren’t able to hit the malicious ghost at all. The ghost just floated in place like a viper hiding in the darkness, staring at the six Mages.

At this time, the other malicious ghosts did the same as the other ghost. They commanded their Undead towards the Mages as they themselves hid.

Chapter 1096: Wild Beasts

Although the undead controlled by the malicious ghosts weren’t strong, there weren’t 100 just like Sim said. Instead, it was more than a thousand!

The Mages present here were strong, but in such an environment, they were already under tremendous pressure. And even if the light element magic were lethal to the Undead, the Undead just stopped going inside the range of the magic. Instead, the Undead took stones and began throwing them towards the Mages.

These Undead were low-level zombies. They weren’t fast nor were they defensive, however, they were actually famed for their strength. Each stone that these zombies threw would certainly have great strength behind it.

Fortunately for the Mages, they already had protective measures on their bodies. Because of this, the stones didn’t pose too much of a threat to them. And these Mages weren’t just standing targets, they immediately launched their own magic towards the Undead. And after passing through layers of formations, the might of these spells couldn’t be underestimated. It didn’t take long before the Mages were able to decimate the more than 1000 Undead.

However, the Mages only managed to destroy the Undead. Their original target, the malicious ghosts, remained unharmed.

Not only did the malicious ghosts remained uninjured, the sounds of fighting also attracted the nearby beasts. The strange thing was, although the beasts could sense the malicious ghosts, both of them were actually living in peace. They seem to have a mutual understanding that the Mages were their enemy.

These beasts weren’t simple. When Zhao Hai scanned them using his spiritual force, these beasts actually reacted. This reaction surprised Zhao Hai the most.

Zhao Hai’s spiritual force was very hard to detect. However, these beasts actually managed to faintly sense it. Zhao Hai also discovered that these beasts and malicious ghosts had at least king-level strength. Although their strength couldn’t compare to the Mages present, this didn’t mean that they couldn’t do anything.

Although Magic Theory produced great power, its requirements for spiritual force was also quite huge. These Mages had just ascended, even the staff they used were from the lower realms. If these Mages exhaust themselves, then they wouldn’t be able to stop the assault coming from the malicious ghosts and the beasts.

Zhao Hai sat inside the Space and looked at the monitor. The malicious ghosts and the beasts had encircled the six Mages, prepared to attack at any time. However, the Mages were clueless about this development, they just continued to advance with caution.

Zhao Hai could see that the environment of the tunnel closely resembled the Underworld. Not only was its dark energy dense, it also had a slight suppression on the soul. This caused the strength of the people inside it to be suppressed. However, Zhao Hai already accustomed himself to the Underworld, and with his formidable spiritual force, this effect didn’t have any use to him.

Zhao Hai knew that these Mages wouldn’t live for long. The malicious ghosts and the beasts had coordinated themselves well. Currently, the Mages still had enough strength to put up a fight. But once they run out of energy, these malicious ghosts and beasts would definitely be impolite.

However, this development didn’t make Zhao Hai glad. Even his feeling of watching a movie had disappeared. The movements of these malicious ghosts and beasts were very unusual. They were too smart and knew how to work with each other. This wasn’t something that ordinary ghosts nor beasts could do.

Naturally, this didn’t necessarily mean that these malicious ghosts and beasts were under someone’s control. In fact, there was a very small probability for this to happen. Dark cultivators would never choose Tyro planet. Even if this tunnel had thick yin energy, almost similar to the Underworld, there were much better places for them to go in the Cultivation Realm.

Instead of being under someone’s control, all signs indicated that these malicious ghosts and beasts were probably protecting something. The question now was, what were they protecting?

Does this tunnel have something like the Underworld’s giant heart? Was it worth their protection?

The thought of this caused Zhao Hai’s brows to wrinkle even more. Laura and the others had no time to notice Zhao Hai’s expression at this time. Currently, all of their eyes were stuck on the monitor. They were completely immersed in this horror story happening in front of them.

Zhao Hai gently waved his hand, causing another smaller monitor to appear in front of him. Shown on this screen were the four Warriors from the Wild Academy. Hearing the battle between the Mages and the Undead, the four Warriors decided to come.

Zhao Hai didn’t stop them, and he didn’t have any reason to. Although the Ashley Family had some friendship with the Northwild family, Zhao Hai could see that this relationship wasn’t that deep. Otherwise, when Margaret asked their instructor to team up, they wouldn’t have disagreed.

Zhao Hai had certain classifications for people. The first type were his family, like Laura and the others. If someone dared to make a move on his family, then they would die!

The second type  were his friends like Dins and the others. Although Zhao Hai would provide them help during their difficult time, he wouldn’t treat them as though they were his family. And if there came a time where Dins and the others could help him but didn’t, then that would be the time to end their friendship.

The third type of people were passers-by. These people had no relationship with him. He wouldn’t go out of his way to give them a hand. To him, they didn’t matter. After all, he wasn’t a saint.

The last type were his enemies. Needless to say, they were people he needed to eliminate.

To Zhao Hai, people from the Wild Academy were passers-by. Their lives didn’t matter to him. He wouldn’t kill them, but he also wouldn’t stop them if they were courting death.

Just before the Warriors from the Wild Academy reach the Adam Academy’s Mages, the beasts suddenly began their attack. Meanwhile, the malicious ghosts stayed put.

However, those dark beasts were enough to deal with the Mages. All in all, there were 12 dark beasts with strengths equal or greater than king-level experts in the Underworld. Most importantly, although the energy inside these beasts were dark, they weren’t Undead, thus they were alive. In turn, this gave them the ability to resist light magic.

Of the 12 dark beasts, 10 looked like wolves. But instead of fur, they had scales on their bodies, making them look more terrifying.

The other two beasts had the form of snakes. Their entire body was black and covered in scales, making them fully integrate into the darkness. These snakes didn’t look strong and could even be grabbed by one’s hand. However, the snakes were very long, both of them had bodies that extended 20 meters out.

While searching for information about Tyro Planet, Zhao Hai was introduced to these snakes. In fact, these snakes were quite famous in the planet. They were relatives of Ironthread Snakes, known as Poisonous Ironthread Serpents!

Poisonous Ironthread Serpents were beasts unique to Tyro Planet. Their bodies were harder than iron and comparable to steel. Most importantly, their poison was very lethal; even their scales were poisonous. If one was bitten by this snake, even level four Warriors wouldn’t be able to survive.

The wolves weren’t simple either. They were known as Poisonscale Wolves. They were beasts that lived in a pack of five to ten members. They weren’t strong but all of them were poisonous. They were also able to spit poison from their mouth. Their poison could corrode battle qi and magic. If the poison hits a human, the person would soon dissolve into black liquid.

Naturally, these things weren’t found by Zhao Hai. They were all presented to him by Laura and the others. After knowing that Zhao Hai was heading to Tyro Planet, Laura and the others began to check for information regarding the place. Tyro Planet was relatively famous in the Machine Field, so they were able to find information about the planet quite easily. While they were browsing, they were able to find information about the Poisonous Ironthread Serpents as well as the Poisonscale Wolves.

The Poisonscale Wolves slowly came out of the shadows, coming under the light produced by light magic. The range of the Old Mage’s light element magic was now smaller than before. It was obvious that he was beginning to be exhausted.

Seeing the Poisonscale Wolves, the expressions of the Mages couldn’t help but change. They were here to eliminate malicious ghosts, they didn’t expect to meet poisonscale wolves. They weren’t fools, so after arriving at Tyro Planet, they immediately searched for information about the planet. Therefore, they were aware about how terrifying these wolves were.

Upon seeing the wolves, a young Mage couldn’t help but say, “Poisonscale Wolves? Why are they here? Where are the malicious ghosts?”

Nobody replied to him, causing the Mage’s face to turn uglier. At this time, the poisonscale wolves began to launch their attack. As the wolves attacked, the two poisonous ironthread serpents began to scale the walls of the cave.

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but frown upon seeing the wolves. Although poisonscale wolves were quite strong, they don’t seem to be able to fly. In the lower realms, those with the same strength as the wolves were able to fly, so why weren’t these wolves flying?

It was certainly strange.

While Zhao Hai was thinking about this, the poisonscale wolves swarmed the six Mages. The malicious ghosts and snakes stayed put, preparing to stage an ambush if an opportunity came.

Chapter 1097: Malicious Ghost’s Possession

Hu!

A poisonscale wolf pounced towards a Mage. Although the wolf couldn’t fly, its leap still covered a huge distance. It jumped a hundred meters in one go. The Mage didn’t expect the wolf to jump so far, so he wasn’t able to guard on time. This allowed the wolf to hit the Mage’s protective barrier.

Boom!

The Mage’s barrier fiercely shook, causing his body to fly backwards. While the Mage was pushed back, his barrier shattered as well.

This caused the Mage’s expression to change. One should know that this protective barrier was made using Magic Theory. Although it was only a single-layer formation, it was still very powerful compared to normal barriers. How could such a barrier be destroyed by a poisonscale wolf in one strike?

However, it seems like the strike also exhausted the wolf. As it fell from the air, the wolf looked like a falling leaf as it fluttered to the ground.

The Mage relaxed. But just as he was about to arrange another single-layer barrier, he suddenly felt his back turn cold. He was startled and immediately flew forward.

But it was already too late. As the Mage was flying forward, he felt his neck turn cool, then his arms felt light, then his entire body completely shut down. At this time, the other Mages had yet to notice this, but Zhao Hai was able to see everything. A poisonous ironthread serpent just attacked. After tying down the Mage’s neck, the snake bit off one arm before proceeding to take the Mage’s life.

Not long after the Mage died, the snake wrapped around his neck tighter, slammed its body on the ground and then flung the body towards the darkness. At the same time, the snake used the momentum from throwing the Mage’s body in order to retreat and find an opportunity to attack another Mage.

Before the first Mage’s body hit the dark floor of the cave, a malicious ghost suddenly charged forward and slowly possessed the Mage’s body. The ‘Mage’ then opened his eyes. However, the eyes were completely black. Also, his body was filled with strong killing aura.

The possessed Mage fluttered back into the light magic. But as he entered the range of the light magic, he began to emit black gas. His eyes also showed a painful expression. However, he didn’t make any noise. Instead, he continued to get close to another Mage. This Mage turned out to be the Old Light Mage.

Zhao Hai calmly looked as all of these happened. After the poisonous ironthread serpent flung the Mage towards the darkness, Zhao Hai knew that the Mage was already dead. However, instead of being transformed into an Undead like he expected, the malicious ghost actually possessed the Mage’s body.

Back on Earth, it was well-known that ghosts were able to possess a body. However, Zhao Hai didn’t see any ghosts in the Ark Continent nor the Underworld that could do so. He didn’t expect to see this ability here.

The possessed ghost was already beside the Old Mage. Although the Mages from the Adam Academy weren’t united, they weren’t stupid. They were aware that the Old Mage was the only Light element Mage among them. If the Old Mage died, then they would have a very difficult time fending off the ghosts and beasts.

Because of this, the Mages grouped up with the Old Mage being in the center.

But since these Mages weren’t able to see the action made by the poisonous ironthread serpent, they didn’t have any suspicion towards the possessed Mage. This allowed the possessed Mage to get close to the Old Mage without any difficulties.

The possessed Mage also pretended to hold off the assaulting poisonscale wolves. At the same time, he went closer and closer towards the Old Mage. Before long, the malicious ghost was already five meters away from the Old Mage.

Although the Old Mage noted this action, he didn’t attack the malicious ghost. The Old Mage’s magic now had reduced range. Also, the other Mages didn’t use light magic from Magic Theory, instead they used lower realm magic.

Zhao Hai knew that the old Mage’s spiritual force was beginning to be exhausted. It must be said that the Old Mage’s spiritual force shouldn’t have been exhausted this soon. However, the Old Mage still wasn’t familiar with Magic Theory, this caused him to consume more spiritual force than usual.

Another reason for this consumption might be the Mages’ underestimation of the Undead. These Mages had also met Undead in their own lower realms, so they didn’t take the Undead too seriously. Because of this, they attacked the Undead without thinking. As a result, they consumed their spiritual force too quickly before even meeting a malicious ghost.

While the Old Mage was distracted, the possessed Mage suddenly charged towards him. Then the possessed Mage stretched his hands out. These hands didn’t cast any magic, instead it became long black claws that looked very menacing.

The Old Mage wasn’t on guard against this surprise attack. When he discovered the attack, it was already too late. Before the Old Mage could react, the ghost’s claws had already ripped a whole on the Old Mage’s throat.

The Old Mage’s throat gave out a horrifying sound as he looked at the malicious ghost in horror. It didn’t take long before the Old Mage lost his strength. With nobody left to maintain it, the light magic began to vanish.

With the Old Mage dead and the powerful light element magic gone, the other malicious ghosts began to charge towards the other Mages. The poisonscale wolves and the poisonous ironthread serpents also pounced towards the remaining four Mages.

The four Mages panicked, they didn’t expect the Old Mage to die just like that. They were confident that as long as the Old Mage lived, even if they couldn’t kill the malicious ghosts, they could still escape. Now that the Old Mage was dead, their opportunity to escape was gone.

While the four Mages were still flustered, the ghosts and the beasts seized the opportunity as their roared and charged over. With the cooperation between the ghosts and the beasts, the four Mages were killed in less than ten minutes.

After the remaining Mages died, the other malicious ghosts proceeded to possess their bodies. At the same time, the beasts hid themselves in the darkness. This was because they could feel other people entering the area.

This time, the team that entered were the Warriors from Wild Academy. Each one of them were now carrying lamps as they flew forward.

Zhao Hai looked at the four Warriors and then sighed, “If they came a few minutes earlier, they might have been able to unite with the Mages. Even if they can’t kill the ghosts, it wouldn’t be a problem for them to escape. But now, they are already too late.” Laura and the other nodded. Then Laura turned to Zhao hai and said, “Brother Hai, will you make a move now?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Not immediately. If I do, then wouldn’t I just be telling them that I have been watching all this time? At the very least, they should get injured before I make a move.”

Laura nodded, then didn’t say anything else. The experience that Laura and the others gained wasn’t any less than Zhao Hai’s. They also had their own ideas regarding human nature. And as they grew together with Zhao Hai, they were wise enough to know that they didn’t need to be polite to their enemies.

Before long, the Warriors of the Wild Academy met with the malicious ghosts. Although the ghosts had completed their possession, they didn’t use any of the Mages’ magic. And with the Warriors being extremely cautious, the group of dark creatures weren’t given any chances to sneak attack. The only thing they could do now was to attack head-on.

The four Warriors had impeccable cooperation. Naturally, this was taught to them by their academy. Because of this, they were able to hold on amidst the attacks of the seven ghosts and 12 beasts.

However, the faces of the Warriors were quite ugly. They had just discovered that the Mages were all dead. Also, there weren’t four or five malicious ghosts, instead there were seven. And of the seven, six of them possessed the Mages. Not only that, there were also 12 powerful beasts. They couldn’t win against this much enemies, the only choice they have was to retreat.

One of the four Warriors suddenly said, “Wu Quan, Lan Jiang, you two block them while me and Fei Ni attack them with our sword qi. We’ll try killing two of them at a time as we retreat. The situation here is much worse than what Instructor told us. We aren’t their opponents.”

The three other Warriors nodded. After that, two of them began to take their weapons out and blocked the ghosts and the beasts. Meanwhile, the other two also took their weapons out as they readied themselves to launch their attack.

The latter two’s aura got stronger and stronger as the swords in their hands shone. Then the two gave a shout as they waved their sword to cut the nearby poisonscale wolves.

The two poisonscale wolves just pounced. With their body still in mid-air, the wolves were unable to dodge. The sword qi slashed through the wolves as though they were paper. The wolves were immediately cut in half. They gave a pitiful sound as they hit the ground, their internal organs spewing out of their bodies. They only twitched for a few moments before they became motionless.

This wasn’t the end, the Warriors wielded their swords once more as they killed another two poisonscale wolves, two malicious ghosts, and one poisonous ironthread serpent.

This attack caused the remaining malicious ghosts and beasts to be afraid. The dark creatures stopped their attack before retreating to the dark, plunging the cave into silence once more.

Chapter 1098: The End of the Exam

The Warriors weren’t naive enough to think that the ghosts and the beasts wouldn’t try to attack them again. On the contrary, the ghosts and beasts were now more dangerous since they were hidden.

The two Warriors that sent the sword qi were now very pale. They had just exhausted themselves and would need to recover for some time.

The group’s leader made a decision, “Let’s retreat immediately. The Adam Academy’s Mages are dead. Also, there are more enemies than reported. We cannot kill them all by ourselves. We need to head back and look for instructor.”

The others immediately agreed. The two Warriors who didn’t send sword qi proceeded to protect their two weakened comrades.

Seeing that the situation had reached a crucial point, Zhao Hai stood up before turning his head to Laura and the others and said, “It’s my time to enter the stage. Everyone, witness my performance!”

Laura and the others gave a warm applause, causing Zhao Hai to laugh before his figure flashed and left the Space. The next moment, Zhao Hai appeared back in the tunnel at a distance away from the battlefield. Naturally, he wasn’t stupid enough to appear directly in the middle of the fight. That would make people think that he was just watching all this time. Therefore, Zhao Hai appeared at a distance and pretended to have just arrived at the scene.

When Zhao Hai appeared in the tunnel, he immediately released light element magic. His light element magic was released using Magic Theory. However, this magic wasn’t an area attack. Instead, the light was concentrated, as though it was a searchlight from a lighthouse.

After that, Zhao Hai roared as he flew straight into the battle. His speed was very fast. Currently on Zhao Hai’s hand was his blood ghost staff. He lifted his staff as the magic formation directed the light magic forward. The light looked like a sharp sword that was plunged into the darkness.

Zhao Hai made sure to have the Warriors notice his arrival, hoping that the Warriors would stop retreating and deal with the enemy together with him. With this, there would be no suspicions placed on him. If the Warriors left, then the Adam Academy might doubt his claims.

With how huge Zhao Hai’s move was, it was impossible for the Warriors to not notice him. Seeing the glaring beam of light, the Warriors immediately looked for its source. It didn’t take long for them to know who was coming over.

There were three academies participating in this trial. And the Adam Academy’s six students were already dead. The only person that has yet to show themselves was the Ashley Academy’s sole participant.

With this thought, the Warriors couldn’t help but hesitate. Then one of them said, “Khan, what do we do now? Should we keep retreating?” Khan looked at the beam of light and said, “That’s light magic, it should be able to suppress the Undead. We can use this opportunity to fight alongside him. If we retreat now, we will fail the exam.”

The other Warriors agreed, so all four of them stopped before they roared and joined the battle. Wu Qian and Lan Jiang put Fei Ni and Khan in the middle so that the two could recover their strength as soon as possible.

Zhao Hai was very fast. He also pretended to miss the Warriors’ location. After the Warriors roared, he immediately adjusted his course and flew towards them at the quickest speed.

Before long, Zhao Hai arrived where the Warriors were. Zhao Hai also discovered that the malicious ghosts and the beasts had already encircled them.

Zhao Hai looked at the Warriors and smiled as he gave his greetings, “So its our friends from Wild Academy. What happened? I just sensed a disturbance in the energy of this place. Did you manage to find the malicious ghosts?”

Khan and the others returned the greeting. Then Khan answered, “We’ve seen Mister Zhao Hai. Yes, we’ve met with the malicious ghosts. They’ve already dealt with the Adam Academy. At this time, it’s possible that we have been surrounded. Mister should be careful.”

Zhao Hai wrinkled his brows as he said, “Really? I didn’t expect malicious ghosts to be that strong.”

Khan quickly answered, “Mister, there aren’t just five malicious ghosts, but seven. There are also 12 poisonous beasts. But now, their numbers have been reduced to five ghosts and seven beasts. The others have already been killed by us.”

Zhao Hai said ‘oh’ then he laughed as he waved his hand. A magic formation appeared on his magic staff. This magic formation caused a huge explosion of white light. This explosion illuminated a kilometer of area. Naturally, this illumination revealed the presence of ghosts and beasts.

After seeing the forms of the ghosts and beasts, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but laugh as he said, “You dark creatures truly have skills. But unfortunately, it’s time for you to die.”

Appearing in Zhao Hai’s had was a magic formation. This formation was different than the light element one he used earlier. When the formation was released, the dark energy not being hit by the light beam became absorbed into the formation. The formation got darker and darker before it became extremely black. Then Zhao Hai waved his hand, causing the formation to enlarge and cover the malicious ghosts. While the malicious ghosts were struggling to get free, Zhao Hai muttered, “Receive!”

Just as his voice fell, the magic formation sucked everything into the middle. Khan and the others saw several shadows going out of the bodies of the Mages. Without the ghosts possessing them, the bodies of the Mages collapsed to the ground.

This was dark element magic. Dark element magic wasn’t strong by itself, but after passing through formations, their strength multiplied. Because of this, the ghosts were easily sucked in and sent to the Space.

Just as the group of malicious ghosts entered the Space, a prompt was immediately heard, “Mutant Dark Element Undead detected. Undead has a large tendency for violence. Sensing negative sentiment towards the Space. Subduing. Undead has been subdued.”

Zhao Hai wasn’t too surprised about this prompt. As long as the ghosts were sent to the Space, then there was no way for them to escape.

After dealing with the malicious ghosts, Zhao Hai turned his attention to the remaining beasts. Then he said, “You bastards also want to join in on the fun right? Then you might as well join them!”

Zhao Hai waved his hand, causing five formations to appear in front of him. As these formations appeared, the dark energy in the surroundings began to move once again. And this time, the suction speed was much greater. In a blink of an eye, the formations turned pure black. Zhao Hai looked at the formations and then said, “Dark being, tear the space open!”

After Zhao Hai spoke, the five formations broke the space. Shortly after that, an ancient savage roar was heard from the rift. Then two claws grabbed the rift, ripping a bigger hole. The spatial rift grew bigger and bigger. It was as if the world itself was being torn apart.

Then a head emerged from the rift.

The huge head was covered with black scales. It had a huge mouth enough to swallow ten people in one bite. It had teeth that seem like it could tear into one’s soul. This caused the head to send chills to a person. The eyes on the head had slits, appearing both cold and ruthless.

The huge head looked around before fully emerging out of the rift. After going through, it issued a loud cry, causing pressure on the beasts. The beasts couldn’t help but cower in its presence. They seem to be panicking at the sight of the monster.

Zhao Hai recognized the being at first glance. It turned out to be a Black Dragon. It looked similar to the dragons in the Ark Continent. However, the strength of this dragon was much stronger.

This dragon doesn’t seem to be able to fly. From its looks, Zhao Hai thought that it was a T-rex. It was about 15 meters tall. It had two short front limbs. However, its legs had sharp looking claws. All of these plus its sturdy-looking tail demonstrated the creature’s strength.

After the black dragon faced upwards and roared, its cold eyes turned towards the posionscale wolves and poisonous ironthread serpents. Then the dragon opened its mouth, breathing black flames towards the beasts.

The posionscale wolves immediately turned around and ran. However, the black dragon didn’t give them the opportunity to escape. It immediately charged over and overtook the wolves. Then it swung its tail, sending the wolves flying into the air. On the other hand, the poisonous ironthread serpents slithered towards a nearby tunnel to get out.

Khan and the others were looking at these events in a daze. They didn’t expect a single person to deal with the wolves and the serpents. Wasn’t this too easy?

In fact, they weren’t aware that after the poisonscale wolves were sent flying, Zhao Hai opened a spatial rift and caught them, sending them to the Space. The same outcome happened to the poisonous ironthread serpents. As the serpents ran into the tunnels, they didn’t expect a spatial rift waiting for them. Without even recognizing it, the serpents went towards the Space.

Seeing that the beasts had been taken care of, Zhao Hai gave a satisfied nod. Then he waved his hand, causing a spatial rift to appear, taking the black dragon in.

After he received the black dragon, Zhao Hai turned towards Khan and the other. He smiled faintly and said, “Everyone, I think there’s nothing else left here. I’ll be taking my leave first.”

Just as his voice fell, he heard a voice, “The exam has been completed. Students, please return to your own vehicles.”

Zhao Hai gave one last nod to Khan and the others before flying towards his car. It didn’t take long before he reached his car, rode it, and proceeded to leave the place.

When Zhao Hai left, Khan and the others let out a long breath. Wu Quan turned to Khan and said, “Big Brother Khan, that Zhao Hai, how could he be that strong?”

Khan sighed, then he said, “By his present standard, he should still be a level 1 Mage. However, he can use more than one element. If it came to combat power, he is more powerful than most people at his level. Things aren’t looking so good.”

Wu Quan said, “Big Brother? Isn’t the exam finished?”

Khan replied, “The Wild Academy and the Ashely Academy are in good terms with each other while the Adam Academy and the Ashley Academy are on bad terms. In this exam, all of the Adam Academy’s Mages died. Although Zhao Hai and us aren’t related to their deaths, I’m afraid the Adam Academy wouldn’t believe our testimonies. Even if we are safe inside our Academies, we might be met with revenge once we left. This would bring us endless trouble. It would be great if we could store their bodies inside a spatial item. This way, we might be able to find a way out of this.”

Wu Quan and the others understood what Khan wanted to do. However, when they ascended, they had already left their spatial item behind. They didn’t have one right now.

Lan Jiang looked at the Mage corpses and then said, “Big Brother Khan, maybe those Mages have spatial items on them. Let’s search their bodies first before we go back.”

Those words made Khan nod. He said, “Right, I forgot about that. Go and search their bodies.” Then the group flew towards the Mages. After they searched the bodies, they were able to get three pieces of spatial equipment. The group immediately placed the corpses inside a spatial item. Then they left the area and returned to their car.

As they flew, Wu Quan turned to Khan and said, “Big Brother Khan, since we’ve decided to join the Northwild Camp, how about we take two of these spatial items for ourselves? Let’s return only one of them to the Adam Academy.”

Khan shook his head and said, “We can’t touch these spatial items. I’m almost sure that they’re registered with the Adam Academy. If we take it, they would only doubt us. We’ll hand everything over. Rest assured, after searching the Machine Field’s network, it seems like spatial items aren’t that rare. We can buy some if we earn some money.”

Wu Quan and the others nodded. They agreed to this decision. When they returned to the car, the vehicle began to fly.

After a couple of hours, everyone returned to the tunnel city. Margaret and the others were already waiting for them there.

Seeing that Zhao Hai was safe, Margaret began to relax. Not long after Zhao Hai arrived, Khan and the others also came back.

After Zhao Hai gave Margaret his greetings, he stood behind her and didn’t say anything. And while Khan was greeting his instructor, he also whispered a couple of words to him. Upon hearing Khan, the instructor’s face couldn’t help but change. He turned to Khan and said, “Are you telling the truth?”

Khan nodded and said, “It’s true. These are their spatial items. There are three all in all.” Then he handed the three items to the instructor.

Seeing the spatial items on his hands, the instructor sighed before walking towards Jin Changji.

Chapter 1099: You’re Lying!

Jin Changji was currently feeling strange. The Wild Academy and the Ashley Academy’s students had already returned. However, the Adam Academy’s students had yet to arrive.

He didn’t believe that the Adam Academy’s students would have no survivors. After all, there were six of them, how could none of them survive?

Instructor Dan went to Jing Changji and said, “There’s no need for Instructor Jin to wait. The Adamy Academy’s students wouldn’t be returning.” Then he handed over the three spatial items.

Jin Changji stared at the spatial items in Instructor Dan’s hand. His expression changed as he said, “Why do you have their spatial items? Did the Wild Academy kill them?”

Instructor Dan didn’t expect Jin Changji to turn hostile this soon. He coldly snorted before taking out six corpses. These corpses belonged to the Adam Academy’s six Mages.

After releasing the corpses, Dan looked at Jin Changji and said, “Surnamed Jin, don’t just bark like a wild dog. Act like your position. You aren’t an idiot, you can look at their injuries to see how they died. Take these three spatial items, my Northwild family has a lot of them.” Then he slammed the spatial rings into a nearby table. It might even be said that he embedded the rings into the table. One could see from this point how strong Dan really was.

Seeing Dan’s conduct, Jin Changji’s eyes couldn’t help but shrink. But he just coldly snorted before turning his head to the six Mages.

After carefully looking at the corpses, Jin Changji’s expression sank. This was because the injuries seen on the bodies indicated that they had been killed by malicious ghosts and beasts. And there wasn’t any indication of tampering.

This wasn’t the first time Jin Changji brought students to an exam. Therefore, he could see injuries caused by ghosts and beasts.

After some time, Jin Changji stood up slowly. He looked at Dan and said, “What happened?”

Although Dan was mad at him, that was only a momentary anger. Even so, he didn’t look at Jin Changji’s face and just answered, “There aren’t just five ghosts in the tunnel, but seven ghosts and twelve beasts. It was your team that met them first. As for the state of the battle, Khan and the others only arrived when it was finished. When they sensed fighting, they immediately headed over. But when they arrived, the battle was already over. At that time, the six bodies had already been possessed by the ghosts. Khan’s team was also surrounded by the ghosts and the beasts. They have no choice but to retreat. And just as they retreated, Zhao Hai appeared, killing all the ghosts and beasts.”

Jin Changji quietly listened to Dan. Not only him, Margaret also took note of Dan’s words. Upon hearing that Zhao Hai appeared and killed the ghosts and beasts, Margaret’s eyes shone with happiness. She turned her head to Zhao Hai and said, “Zhao Hai, is Instructor Dan telling the truth?”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “When I appeared, the friends from Wild Academy had already killed five beasts and two ghosts. Therefore, I only killed five ghosts and seven beasts. As for what happened before, I haven’t seen anything.”

Jin Changji looked at Zhao Hai and said, “How could you possibly kill five ghosts and seven beasts? You’re lying!”

Zhao Hai just coldly snorted and didn’t answer. At this moment, Khan lightly coughed and said, “Instructor Jin, Mister Zhao Hai can certainly kill five five ghosts and seven beats. This is because he is already a level 1 Mage.”

Jin Changji and Margaret who were listening to Khan couldn’t help but gawk. Margaret felt pleasantly surprised at Zhao Hai. She turned to him and said, “Zhao Hai, are you really a level 1 Mage?” Jin Changji and Dan might not know how significant Zhao Hai’s current level was, but Margaret did. Zhao Hai had just ascended last month. One month after ascending to the Machine Field, he was already a level 1 Mage. If others knew about this, it would certainly cause huge waves.

Not even waiting for Zhao Hai to answer, Jin Changji interfected, “Stop talking nonsense. How could he possibly be a level 1 Mage? I don’t believe it.” Then his hand moved, causing a ten layer formation to appear. Immediately after the formation appeared, a huge sword appeared and pierced towards Zhao Hai.

Margaret was able to see Jin Changji’s movement. However, when she noticed it, the sword had already attacked. She just stopped thinking and went in front of Zhao Hai. Then she waved her hand, summoning a five-layer formation. The formation immediately activated, causing a water shield to appear.

With Jin Changji’s sudden action, Margaret could only use this method to deal with it. A five-layer formation versus a ten-layer formation, their difference was a level. In this case, Margaret’s water shield could only block the sword for a moment.

It didn’t take long for the sword to cut through the water shield. WIth a force as strong as lightning, the sword cut towards Margaret. Seeing this development, Jin Changji’s face turned pale as a corpse. But it was already impossible to stop the magic at this time.

Jin knew very well that Margaret wasn’t just any other Instructor. Her true status wasn’t simple. If he really killed Margaret here, then even the Adam Family wouldn’t be able to save him.

At this time, a fiery red formation suddenly appeared in front of the sword, melting it slowly.

Fire magic just so happens to subdue Jin Changji’s sword. Additionally, fire element magic was inherently strong. Otherwise, it wouldn’t have been able to deal with the giant sword.

Repulsion between the five elements was also relative. Even if water counters fire, pouring a cup of water over a mountain of fire was still a useless move. At that time, it would be the fire repelling the water.

Seeing his sword being blocked, jin Changji couldn’t help but feel relieved. But at the same time, he could also see that the fire magic came from a five-layer formation. Moreover, it can be seen that this magic shield was made by Zhao Hai.

This discovery made Jin Changji’s expression sink. He can now affirm that Zhao Hai was truly a level 1 Mage. Moreover, it seems like his spiritual force was strong. Level 1 Mages were usually unable to melt his sword. Although the sword was blocked by Margaret’s five-layer water shield,  its energy was mostly preserved after piercing through. At least, the sword should still have seven-tenths of its power. Nevertheless, Zhao Hai’s fire shield was still able to block it. This meant that Zhao Hai’s five-layer shield was able to block a seven-layer sword’s strength. This was enough to show Zhao Hai’s strength.

Margaret also responded at this time, her pale face turned towards Jin Changji and said, “Jin Changji, good, good. You actually dared to attack here. It seems like we’ll see more deaths today!”

After she said that, she began to wave her staff. Upon seeing Margaret’s expression, Jin Changji knew that if she went through with this, things wouldn’t turn out great. He immediately bowed and said, “Instructor Margaret, you misunderstand. Please, calm down. Please calm down. I didn’t do it on purpose!”

When she saw Jin Changji’s helpless expression, Margaret decided to stop. Then she said, “What? You believe it now?”

Jin Changji smiled bitterly and said, “I believe it. I just didn’t expect the Ashley Family to send a level 1 Mage for an exam. Instructor Margaret, how many months has it been since he ascended? How did he get so strong?”

The reason why Jin Changji asked this was because people who came to Tyro Planet for the exams were ascenders who had ascended for three or four months. And generally, three to four-month ascenders had yet to reach level 1.

Margaret looked at Jin Changji, she seemed to be dissatisfied with how things turned out. But she still replied, “Five months. He’s the most talented genius that Ashley Academy had in the past ten years. Therefore, we had him participate in the exam a bit later. You’re unlucky. If he met your students sooner, then those ghosts might not have killed them. I really didn’t expect the ghosts to increase at this time.”

After she spoke, everyone turned their attention to Sim. After all, it was Sim that gave them information about the ghosts. If Zhao Hai wasn’t strong enough, then nobody would have survived the exam.

Although lower realm ascenders still needed some training, it was undeniable that they were geniuses. Especially those like Zhao Hai and Khan’s group. After they develop in the Machine Field for several years, it would be possible for them to become intermediate level experts, capable of handling important matters. So if they died in this place, the losses incurred would be huge. This situation wasn’t something that Sim would permit.

Receiving the gazes from Margaret and the others, Sim immediately knew what they were thinking. He couldn’t help but force a smile and said, “Everybody, you should know that I wouldn’t permit such things from happening. We really aren’t aware that there would be that much danger. We’ve already known each other for many years, you already know that I wouldn’t dare harm ascenders from the lower realms.”

Margaret and the others nodded upon hearing Sim’s words. Sim certainly wouldn’t harm ascenders since he was an ascender himself. It has been 30 years since Sim had ascended. And he was also considered as someone with talent. It was only when he suffered a severe wound that his strength stopped progressing any further. In the end, he could only become an official responsible for exams. Because of his origin, Sim held special sentiments towards fellow ascenders. It was impossible for him to cause them harm in this exam.

Chapter 1100: Ghost Mithril Ore!

Margaret and the others sighed. They couldn’t help but admit that they were unlucky this time. They couldn’t blame this matter on Sim. This was because there had been numerous times where the exams had mistakes in their investigation. This wasn’t the first time that the strength of the enemy had suddenly increased.

Everyone rested for a day before they headed back to their own academies. Naturally, Zhao Hai and Margaret rode their own ship. The other academies had their own spaceships to take them home.

After Zhao Hai returned to the ship, he immediately entered his room, closed the door, and didn’t make any sound. Margaret didn’t comment on this. In her mind, Zhao Hai was practicing. If he didn’t act like this, he wouldn’t have been this strong.

However, she was wrong. Zhao Hai returned to his room and entered the Space. But this time, he didn’t cultivate.

Upon entering the Space, Zhao Hai looked at Laura and said, “We need to take a look at that tunnel. It’s very weird to have that much beasts and malicious ghosts in one place. I want to see what they were there for.”

Laura lightly frowned and said, “Brother Hai, why do you need to do this? Isn’t it just a little weird? It has nothing to do with us.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “You don’t need to worry about me. I just want to see if there are any treasures back there. Didn’t you see? Those ghosts and beasts seem to be guarding something. Otherwise, they wouldn’t have worked that well with each other.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai say treasure, Laura and the others immediately understood what he was saying. Ever since they arrived at the Machine Field, they understood that it would be difficult for them to live comfortably with their present strength. Not to mention that the Machine Field was one of the weaker powers in the World of Cultivation.

Zhao Hai’s current strength could be considered to be medium-grade in the Machine Field. Medium-grade experts might be one of the top people in the Machine Field, but they still wouldn’t be able to contend against mechas and battleships.

If they wish for the Space to level-up, then they would need to seek treasures of the World of Cultivation. Otherwise, it would be very difficult for the Space to level up.

Even if Laura and the others didn’t want Zhao Hai to take any risks, they also saw the ghosts and the beasts from the tunnel. At the same time, they could see that Zhao Hai didn’t have any problems dealing with them. With this thought in mind, Laura didn’t prevent Zhao Hai any longer as she nodded and said, “Alright. But Brother Hai, you need to be careful.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Rest assured, there wouldn’t be any problems.” Then his figure vanished. The next moment, he appeared back in the mining tunnel. Meanwhile, Laura and the others began to move and opened their computers. They divided the mine into sections and scoured through to see any peculiar things.

This was what Laura and the others planned to do in order to give Zhao Hai help. They couldn’t go outside the Space and help Zhao Hai fight. This was the only way they could do in order to provide assistance.

Their computers weren’t any ordinary computer. These were devices specially created by the Space. They had large screens like the Space’s monitor and were more convenient to use.

Zhao Hai didn’t just randomly teleport to a random place in the tunnel. He was currently inside the region that the malicious ghosts and the beasts used to occupy.

The malicious ghosts and beasts didn’t nest in the center of the tunnel. Instead, they were based at the northern part. This also happened to be where the Adam Academy’s students were dropped off.

Malicious ghosts and beasts usually never moved from their areas unless a problem occurred. They wouldn’t have made a move if they weren’t protecting something.

When he appeared in the tunnel. Zhao Hai immediately released his spiritual force in order to scan the area for any dangers. Sure enough, he was able to discover something.

The malicious ghosts and the beasts had just been cleared up. But there were already several weaker ghosts here!

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but stare at this discovery. Then he smiled and said, “Interesting, there already ghosts here. It seems like this place really isn’t normal. Laura, go take a closer look at the surrounding area.”

Laura and the others complied and immediately carried on a careful examination of the nearby region. On the other hand, Zhao Hai released a five-fold light element magic, instantaneously killing the weak ghosts that had gathered.

Zhao Hai also released his own spiritual force in order to scan the surroundings.

At this time, Meg’s voice was suddenly heard, “Young Master, I discovered a very high density of dark energy southeast of your location. The dark energy here is much thicker than the Underworld. Maybe it’s the place we’re looking for.” Zhao Hai nodded, then a map appeared in his head. The map marked the place that Meg mentioned. With a flash, Zhao Hai appeared in that place.

Upon experiencing the density of dark energy, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but stare. It was very thick, much thicker than in the Underworld. What puzzled Zhao Hai was the fact that even though the dark energy was thick, it wasn’t black. Instead, it was actually silver in color.

Dark energy generally manifested as black, this was common knowledge. However, the dark energy of this place didn’t follow this rule. This caused Zhao Hai to wonder.

At this moment, a ring suddenly sounded inside Zhao Hai’s head. It seems like this ringing was Lizzy’s doing.

Lizzy had also seen the place, what’s the point of this alarm? Zhao Hai quickly answered, “What happened?”

Just as his voice fell, Lizzy said, “Big Brother Hai, a kilometer under you is a mithril vein. However, this vein looks very strange. They were all mithril ores, but they looked like ghosts. It’s weird. Wait a moment. Sister Laura and the others are looking for information about this ore online.”

Just as Lizzy finished talking, Laura’s voice was heard, “Found it. Brother Hai, a kilometer under you is a ghost mithril ore vein. Ghost mithril is a special type of mineral in the World of Cultivation. It is a mithril ore that had dark energy mixed into it while it formed. It’s a dual-element material. It is mainly used to forge yin-type weapons, but it has a lot of other uses. Any realm in the World of Cultivation consider it as a treasure. Moreover, there’s a good possibility for ghost mithril essence to be born inside each ore vein. Surrounding the ghost mithril essence would be the best ghost mithril of the entire vein. If we can get them all, that would be equal to gaining a lot of ghost mithril weapons. This is something that experts in the World of Cultivation long to get hold of.”

Zhao Hai stared, then his two eyes shone and said, “Really? Fantastic. Right, what are mithril weapons used for?”

Laura answered, “There aren’t that much uses for mithril weapons. This is because it isn’t known for its hardness. Instead, mithril is the best metal when it comes to conduction. Ghost mithril has a strong memory storage function. If Mages in the Machine Field use a weapon made with ghost mithril, then they could store their layered formations much easier. When the time comes, they would be able to release it all in one go. This will save a lot of time.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he said, “Good, then let’s go take a look.” Then Zhao Hai waved his hand, taking his blood ghost staff out. After he entered the blood lotus, it proceeded to drill below the ground.

It didn’t take long before Zhao Hai drilled a kilometer down. What appeared in front of him caused his to be greatly surprised. He didn’t expect ghost mithril to look like this.

Zhao Hai could affirm that in front of him was a rich reserve of high-quality ore. There were pieces of silvery-white ores closely clumped together. Seen on these ores were different forms of ugly faces. All of them looked incomparably scary. Additionally, these ores projected a strong presence of dark energy. The strong gloomy dark energy perfectly matched the ugly faces on the ore. It would cause ordinary people to flee in terror.

Zhao Hai just smiled. He wasn’t actually afraid of these things. He moved his hand and immediately released large amounts of Undead in order to mine these ghost mithril ores.

As the ghost mithril ore entered the Space, a prompt was heard, “Special mithril ore with dark energy detected.” Then there was no other sound. Zhao Hai expected the Space to say more. But it was just that.

Zhao Hai didn’t care and just had the Undead continue to mine the ores and had it sent to the Space. What he wanted to see right now was the ghost mithril essence.

The Undead were connected to the Space by Cai’er. As long as they mine ghost mithril ore, the ore would be immediately sent to the Space. There was no need for Zhao Hai to open a rift. With this arrangement, the Undead moved very quickly.

Zhao Hai wasn’t in a hurry and just advanced bit by bit. Since he had already found this place, even if the ship arrived at the academy, he could still return from his room. At this time, Zhao Hai wanted Laura and the others to look for the ghost silver essence.

Although ghost mithril essence was a little weak for Zhao Hai, it was still a treasure in the eyes of other people. Moreover, Zhao Hai had an idea. In the past, when he placed ore essences in the Space, it allowed the Space to produce the ores themselves. He wanted to see whether the ghost mithril essence would allow the Space to create ghost mithril ore!

Chapter 1101: Terminator?

Zhao Hai wasn’t attracted to the ghost mithril ores, he wanted the ghost mithril essence. If he can get his hands on the ghost silver essence, the Space might be able to create endless amounts of ores. It might even provide experience, allowing the Space to level-up.

For Zhao Hai, there was nothing more important than levelling up the Space. After all, if the Space levels up, his strength would increase. And nothing was more important than increasing his strength.

Although Zhao Hai wishes the Space to level up quickly, he wasn’t too anxious about it. This was because being anxious was useless. Worrying would just cause him to make mistakes. And in the World of Cultivation, mistakes were closely related to death.

Zhao Hai let his spiritual force loose as he sat inside the blood lotus. At this time, the blood lotus had reduced its size to a person’s fist. It was currently on a crack in the ore vein.

Behind him, the mithril ores were vanishing in a constant rate. With the Undead coordinating with the Space, receiving the ores was very simple

As Zhao Hai proceeded forward, he suddenly felt a trace of spiritual waves in front of him. This spiritual movement was very well hidden, but Zhao Hai was still able to feel it.

Zhao Hai immediately stopped in place. There was no possibility of any creatures in this place. Sensing spiritual movement only meant one thing, the ghost mithril essence!

Zhao Hai carefully pushed his spiritual force towards the direction of the waves. He controlled his spiritual force to be as discreet as possible. This was because he was afraid of making the other side discover him.

Before long, Zhao Hai’s spiritual force arrived at its destination. But when he saw what was giving out spiritual waves, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but stare. This wasn’t what he expected. In his mind, he expected either a rock or a humanoid, or an animal-shaped ghost mithril. In the end, it turned out to be an egg!

Zhao Hai scanned the egg. It wasn’t a huge egg. It was about half a meter high and a diameter of 30 centimeters. Its body was also bright silver.

There were no ores nor dirt surrounding this egg. The egg floated in the void appearing both peaceful and strange.

Zhao Hai paused for a moment before leading the blood lotus to approach the egg. As soon as he reached the egg, Zhao Hai stopped because not only was the egg emitting spiritual waves, it was also physically shaking. It was as though it was afraid.

Zhao Hai had the blood lotus slowly approach the side of the egg. He reached out and gently touched the egg. After touching the egg, Zhao Hai was shocked once more. This was because the egg’s shaking had reduced. He could also feel a breath of life inside!

Zhao Hai stared, he couldn’t help but extend his spiritual force towards the egg. He wanted to sense the inside of the egg.

Just as Zhao Hai’s spiritual force reached the egg, the egg suddenly sucked the spiritual force in. Zhao Hai was surprised, he wanted to retrieve his spiritual force but found out that he wasn’t able to. The egg seemed to produce a huge cortex, sucking up Zhao Hai’s spiritual force into the egg.

Zhao Hai suddenly found out that he had no longer any control over his spiritual force. When he tried to pry his spiritual force away from the egg, he felt that there seems to be a connection that tied his spiritual force to his egg. This connection gave a steady stream of spiritual force for the egg. And it was impossible for Zhao Hai to sever this connection.

Zhao Hai was more surprised to find out that he wasn’t able to enter the Space. If he cannot enter the Space, then his greatest advantage was gone. He can only wait for death.

It was at this point that Zhao Hai discovered that the Space cannot guarantee his safety all the time. If other people could deal with him with the same method, then he could only wait to die.

Just as Zhao Hai thought that the egg would suck him dry, a stream of spiritual force suddenly spread out from the egg. This spiritual force was sent to Zhao Hai’s head, making up for the spiritual force that was just consumed.

Zhao Hai stared as he felt the spiritual force that the egg had sent back. At the same time, there were some information being sent over. Zhao Hai closed his eyes and comprehended this information.

To Zhao Hai’s surprise, he found nothing. The egg just sent information about its loneliness, its fears and so on. It was like a child being locked up in a dark room all alone.

Zhao Hai gawked, he didn’t know what was going on. At this moment, he suddenly felt the egg sending an expression of joy. Then the egg shone with beams of light as its shell melted in Zhao Hai’s hand. Before long, the egg transformed into a molten metal version of a human.

Zhao Hai discovered that this figure of molten metal didn’t have any evil intentions towards him. Although it was in his hand, it didn’t hinder his movement at all. Moreover, he could feel a warm feeling from the figure.

Then the liquid figure suddenly flowed to Zhao Hai’s arms before it gathered on his shoulders. After that, the molten liquid slowly turned into a child.

Zhao Hai curiously watched the little thing. It was smaller than Cai’er. Its upper body had a small belly band while its lower body had baby shorts. It looked quite adorable.

Zhao Hai stared blankly at the kid. Although it was very adorable, its entire body was bright silver. It looked like a baby robot.

At this time, the kid sent another wave of spiritual force. This spiritual force passed its sentiment towards Zhao Hai stating that it was going to depend on him.

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but let out a helpless smile. He really couldn’t understand what was going on. But in the end, he changed his mind and saw that the kid had just been born, and that it had already labeled him as his family.

Zhao Hai didn’t know if he should laugh or cry. But in the end, he rubbed the kid’s belly. In turn, the kid rubbed its small face into Zhao Hai’s cheek. Although the kid looked like a metallic being, its skin was actually very soft.

Zhao Hai smiled faintly before he brought the kid into the Space. Just as the two entered, a prompt was heard, “Metallic man discovered. Metallic man is accepting of the Host. Extracting the metallic man’s ability to improve the Host’s genes. The Host now has the ability to turn into liquid metal. Because the metallic man is the ghost mithril’s essence, the Space can now produce ghost mithril ore veins.”

“Ability to analyze and store detected on the metallic man. Space’s Universal Scanner has levelled up. Hoping the Host to continue working hard.” Just as the prompt was heard, the Space’s scanner had been improved. It was much taller now at ten stories high.

After seeing this development, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but laugh. Ascending to the Machine Field showed his how important the Universal Scanner was. At this moment, he already had several hundred thousand magic formation combinations gathered. All of this was because of the scanner’s ability. Now that the scanner has been upgraded, things would only get better.

However, with this thought, Zhao Hai’s brows couldn’t help but wrinkle. Although this aspect of his strength has been improved, his overall status didn’t increase that much. This could help him get stronger indeed, but Zhao Hai still haven’t found out a way to increase his spirit nor advance in the Stellar Transformation art.

At this time, his Myriad Stellar Transformations art had reached the peak of the first layer, he had yet to enter the second layer. He was able to break through to the second layer at any time, but he seems to be unable to.

Taking a deep breath, Zhao Hai calmed down. He knew that even if the scanner had leveled up and can analyze more layered formations, it was still useless to him. This was because he didn’t have enough spiritual force to support it. With his current strength, 100-layer formations was his limit.

Nevertheless, getting his hands on the ghost mithril essence and allowing the Space to produce ghost mithril ore veins was already a good harvest. He wasn’t too greedy to expect for more.

Zhao Hai didn’t go to see the scanner, there was no need to. He didn’t have much involvement with the machine. It was Cai’er, Laura, and the others that used it frequently.

Upon returning to the villa, Zhao Hai needed to stop his jaw from falling. Laura and the others were in front of their computers and commanded the Undead to move the ghost mithril to the Space. It looked just fine as it was, but looking at the computers, it seems like they were competing in a computer game.

While Zhao Hai was shocked, Cai’er suddenly flew over. Looking at the kid, Cai’er smiled and said, “Young Master, is this the kid the prompt mentioned?”

Zhao Hai nodded, he turned his head to the kid and said, “Kid, this will be your companion from now on. She’s your elder sister Cai’er. Treat her and also my wives as your family. Since you’re silver colored, we’ll start calling you Little Silver from now on. Go on, play with Cai’er.”

Little Silver looked like he couldn’t understand Zhao Hai’s words. However, it could understand what Zhao Hai wanted to say. Therefore, it giggled before a pair of silver wings appeared on its back. The wings fluttered as Little Silver flew crookedly towards Cai’er.

Looking at Little Silver’s appearance, Cai’er smiled before leading the kid to play around. Meanwhile, Zhao Hai went to Laura and the others and looked at the game they were playing. Each one of them were commanding ten Undead creatures and competed on who could mine the most ghost mithril ore.

Zhao Hai didn’t care about their conduct. They had been inside the Space all this time, bored. Being able to find things that could amuse them was good. Zhao Hai didn’t disturb them as he teleported to an uninhabited area in order to try his newly gained ability.

Zhao Hai already discovered that ever since he took Little Silver with him, the dark energy in the tunnel had decreased. It seems like all those dark energy had been supplied by Little Silver. Therefore, there should no longer be any danger in future examinations.

Liquefying his body into metal was Zhao Hai’s new ability. In order to understand more of the ability, Zhao Hai tried to use it. He immediately felt his body turn silver up to the cellular level. Moreover, he could feel his bones and internal organs dissolve. He was now ready to transform.

Then Zhao Hai thought about turning his hand into a sword. And before long, a bright silver sword was in place of his hand. Zhao Hai suddenly thought that he was now like the terminator, being able to turn into liquid metal at ease. At this point, his personal appearance held little meaning.

Zhao Hai smiled bitterly. He began to think that he was becoming less and less human. However, he didn’t necessarily need to become metallic being. For Zhao Hai, this ability was just one means among the many that he already had. It was just like a sword. He didn’t need to use it all the time.

After letting out a long breath, Zhao Hai began to cultivate. He had already decided on his schedule moving forward. Besides sleeping, he would condense magic formations nonstop for two hours. Then after that, he would familiarize himself with formation combinations. This way he would know which ones were the most appropriate to use in future battles.

Like this time, for example. Besides the formation he used to defeat the beasts, the other five-layer formations he used were the most appropriate ones to use at that time. If the Mages from the Adam Academy knew which formation to use, then they wouldn’t have died.

It was one thing to have power. It was another thing to hold complete control of that power, making it your own. Because of this, Zhao Hai made sure to familiarize himself with formations every day.

Besides his condensing formations and familiarizing himself with formation combinations, Zhao Hai also allotted time to practicing sword qi. He’s both a Warrior and a Mage. Not using sword qi would be a waste of his talent.

Zhao Hai saw how Khan and the others utilized their sword qi in order to destroy even the hardest defenses. As long as he gained a good grasp on sword qi, then Zhao Hai would have more cards to play in the future.

Besides magic formations and sword qi, Zhao Hai was also sharpening his usage of spiritual force. In the Machine Field, spiritual force was also very important.

And lastly, Zhao Hai also practiced in his Stellar Transformation Yin-Yang art. In the past, Zhao Hai didn’t deliberately practice this technique. But now that he was actively cultivating this method, his fundamental strength would certainly increase.

While Zhao Hai was learning formation combinations, Cai’er’s voice was suddenly heard, “Young Master, return to the ship quickly. Margaret is looking for you.”

Chapter 1102: Pirates

Zhao Hai paused for a moment before he quickly exited the Space and reappeared inside his room. And just as he arrived in his room, Zhao Hai immediately heard knocks coming from the door.

Zhao Hai quickly went to the door and opened it. Margaret was on the other side, her facial expression somewhat anxious. She looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Zhao Hai, come with me to the command hall quick. There are Space Pirates, we might have to retreat.” Then she turned around and walked towards the command hall.

Zhao Hai hastily followed behind. Before long, they arrived at the ship’s command hall. The atmosphere inside the room was completely different from before. The last time Zhao Hai was here, everyone was very relaxed, some were even drinking tea. Even those who controlled the ship didn’t look busy.

But now, the place was extremely active. Those who controlled the ship were very busily typing on the keyboard as they shouted information. The entire hall was noisy.

Margaret didn’t make any noise as she just led Zhao Hai towards the ship’s commander. The commander stood in front of his table, looking at the display. His expression was very strict. He would also issue commands from time to time.

Zhao Hai looked at the display on the table. From what Margaret said, Zhao Hai expected space pirates to be driving their own spaceships, just like those written in fiction back on earth. However, it seems like this wasn’t the case at all. They were just people who were flying in space.

Seeing this, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but stare. He didn’t expect people to be able to fly in space. Moreover, these people were wearing Mage and Warrior clothes. This was completely out of Zhao Hai’s imagination.

Zhao Hai turned to Margaret and said, “Instructor, these are pirates? And are those Mages?”

Margaret didn’t turn her head to Zhao Hai, but she still nodded and said, “Yes, those are the pirates. Some of them are also ascenders from the lower realms. Their strength should be level 3 or above, since that is the level you need in order to fly in space. They rob people for a living. With their strength, the Mages and Warriors are powerful enough to damage ordinary ships. The academy’s ship is also an ordinary spaceship, but with a little bit more defense. However, it would still be difficult for us to get rid of them.”

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but stare. He was now level 4. If level 3 allowed one to fly in space, then this means that he could fly in space as well.

Margaret hasn’t been paying attention to Zhao Hai’s expressions. She was still looking at the space pirates. Then she added, “Commonly, space pirates don’t attack academy ships. This is because they know that academy ships don’t hold anything valuable. Even if they take an academy ship, it would still be useless for them since it is just a common ship. Nobody would buy it from them.”

Zhao Hao knitted his brows. From the information he checked online, the status of ascender academies were very high. Moreover, academy ships were protected by the three major powers of the Machine Field. Anyone who dared to attack academy ships would be jointly pursued by these powers.

Margaret then said, “The way they appeared is strange. We just left Tyro Planet and now they’re here. It seems like they were waiting for us.”

Upon hearing Margaret, Jin Changji’s image suddenly appeared inside Zhao Hai’s mind. So he immediately said, “Instructor, is this Jin Changji’s plot? Since nobody from the Adam Academy came back, he won’t allow any of us to safely return.”

Margaret stared, but she shook her head and said, “That’s impossible. Jin Changji knows about my status. He wouldn’t dare do anything like this!”

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but pause, then his two eyes shone. Margaret’s words just made him understand that her status wasn’t simple.

But Zhao Hai didn’t dwell on it for long as he said, “Instructor, I can think of four possible reasons . First, they are just pirates and met us coincidentally. But that’s not very likely to happen. It’s common sense for pirates to leave academy ships alone unless some strings are pulled. Second reason is that they are people that are hostile to the Adam Family. They want to attack us in order to frame the Adam Family. If this succeeds, then the Adam Family and the Ashley family would fight and they would profit.”

“The third possibility is that these people are from the Adam Family. They can attack us because they could just claim that they are being framed by other people. People would think that they wouldn’t blatantly attack like this and set themselves on fire. In this case, people might even believe them.”

“The fourth possibility is that these people are other enemies of the Ashley Family. They attack us here so that we would blame the Adam Family, causing a war in the process.”

It wasn’t just Margaret who heard Zhao Hai’s words, the captain was listening as well. When they heard this, they couldn’t help but think that this pirate attack wasn’t as simple as it looked.

Margaret turned to Zhao Hai and said, “So who do you think these people belong to?”

Zhao Hai answered, “First of all, these people cannot be pirates. Tyro Planet being an examination area isn’t a secret. Us being here isn’t strange as well. Therefore, pirates wouldn’t be lurking in this place. Secondly, they couldn’t he from the Adam Academy. Even if the Adam Academy’s students were wiped out in the exam, it didn’t cause too much loss to them. They will not risk damaging themselves just by this event alone, it just isn’t worth it. Third, It is also likely that they aren’t Adam Academy’s enemies. Although killing us would incite a fight between the Ashley Family and the Adam Academy, the two families aren’t stupid enough to not understand the implications of this fight. Both would certainly launch investigations about this matter. And if the perpetrator is found, they would definitely meet a violent retaliation.Therefore, although it seems like it would be a good move to attack us, it is in fact a stupid action. So in the end, I think that the only possibility is that these people are the Ashley Family’s enemies. With enough grudge, people wouldn’t let off any opportunity to attack a member of the family.” Zhao Hai made a careful analysis of this matter. Because of this, Margaret couldn’t find any point to rebut. In the end, Margaret and the Commander nodded.

After nodding, Margaret asked Zhao Hai, “What do you suggest we should do?”

Zhao Hai looked at the Mages and the Warriors on the screen and said, “I think we should return to Tyro Planet. We just left the planet, so it wouldn’t take long for us to head back. Being in Tyro Planet would be the safest move we could do. Upon arriving at the planet, we can send word back to the family and ask them for support.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Margaret nodded and then turned to Kirk and said, “Kirk, what do you think?” Kirk thought about it for a moment and said, “It’s reasonable. We’re not far from Tyro Planet. As long as we turn around, we should be able to reach it if we use our shields. Even if we take damage before arriving at the planet, it wouldn’t be too heavy. At the very least, we can guarantee everyone’s safety.”

Margaret nodded, “Then let’s head back to Tyro Planet at our maximum speed.” Kirk complied and then gave the order. Since the ship wasn’t overly large, it wasn’t difficult for it to turn around and leave.

The attackers didn’t expect the ship to make a sudden turn. They were too surprised that they weren’t able to respond for some time.

Just when they were about to start attacking the ship, it was already quite a distance away. Although these people could fly in space, they weren’t as fast as spaceships. The reason why they can ambush the ship was because the ship was already heading their way. It was the same concept as train robbers. It was impossible for them to catch up to the train, but it was possible to wait for the train to come to them.

However, now that the ship suddenly turned around, these people were left behind. Also, the ship’s defensive shield wasn’t just for decoration. It was a shield that had evolved with Magic Theory, allowing it to block level 5 attacks. Because of this, after the Mage and Warrior attacks hit, they still weren’t able to make a substantial damage.. The ship was now using almost all of its energy on propulsion, but this didn’t mean that they slacked on using their shield. Blocking attacks from these pirates wouldn’t be a problem.

Margaret and Zhao Hai didn’t expect that just as the ship turned around, Kirk suddenly said, “Increase energy use to 100%. Place 80% on propulsion while 20% are on shields.”

At this moment, the ship began to shake. Then a staff member reported, “Commander, cabin 5, 7, and 11, have been damaged. The cabin pressure is beginning to change.” Along with this report, the ship began to slow down.

Kirk quickly made an order, “Close the emergency doors outside cabin 5, 7, and 11. We don’t need them anyway. Make a straight course towards Tyro Planet!!”

And with Kirk’s command, the ship’s speed increased once more, leaving the Mages and Warriors far behind.

Chapter 1103: Full Support In Cultivation

Spaceships had protective shields, but this didn’t mean that these shields were omnipotent. In outer space, danger was in every corner. They may be attacked by space junk, cosmic rays, or anything else at any time. There even some cosmic rays that could tear apart a ship’s shield like paper.

Because of this, most ships had emergency doors installed on its outer cabins!

These emergency doors were there to be used whenever the ship gets damaged. Once the hull gets breached, these emergency doors would immediately be activated, isolating the affected compartments. Even if the pressure on those compartments shred and rip apart everything inside, it still wouldn’t affect the ship’s overall operation.

Those three cabins had been damaged because they had been targeted by the pirates. Therefore, Kirk immediately ordered the emergency doors of those cabins to be closed. This way, it ensures that the ship continues to fly normally.

If the emergency doors were left open, then the pressure on the ship would get bigger and bigger. It might even cause the ship to break in two. If that happens, then they would surely be finished.

Seeing that the pirates had been shaken off, Kirk and the others began to relax. Then Margaret and Kirk looked at Zhao Hai with an unusual gaze. They didn’t think that Zhao Hai would stay calm in such a critical event.

One shouldn’t underestimate the decision to turn back. In their position, it wasn’t an easy task to calmly choose to turn around and head back. Although they were indeed closer to Tyro Planet, they weren’t that close. They had already been travelling for close to day, and were now one-third of the way back to the academy. Most people might just bite the bullet and push through.

Zhao Hai also thought about going forward. However, if the Ashley family’s enemy really did want to deal with them, then it’s possible that they would stage multiple ambushes along the way. Because of this, Zhao Hai knew that going back was the only solution that could provide them with an assured chance of survival.

And his choice was correct. As the ship turned around, the pursuing Warriors and Mages couldn’t catch up. This allowed Zhao Hai and the others to escape with their lives.

Zhao Hao saw Margaret and Kirk’s gaze, but he just smiled and didn’t say anything. Margaret didn’t ask Zhao Hai anything as well as she turned to Kirk and said, “I’ll send news back to the family and ask them for assistance as soon as possible. Meanwhile, let’s stay in Tyro Planet and recuperate.” Kirk nodded.

Although they still haven’t arrived at Tyro Planet, Kirk knew that they were as good as safe. And as long as they reach the range of the planet’s defenses, nothing would happen to them.

Planetary defenses were quite common in the Machine Field. And on a planet with mithril ore, Tyro Planet had defenses much stronger than most.

After landing on Tyro Planet, the people on the ship were finally able to let out relieved sighs. Margaret took Zhao Hai back to the reception area and told Sim about the situation. Then she asked Sim to provide them with a place to stay.

Naturally, Sim immediately agreed to the request and arranged a room for them. After the rooms had been assigned, Margaret went to Zhao Hai’s room.

After being invited inside by Zhao Hai and offered a cup of tea, Margaret sat opposite her student. She looked at Zhao Hai for some time before she said, “Zhao Hai, I need to thank you for your calm thinking. If it weren’t for you, we would’ve decided to proceed.” Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Instructor is too polite. I’m just thinking for myself. If we really continued going forward, then not everyone in the ship might have survived.”

Margaret nodded, then she said, “I reckon you’ve already known about the Bone Symbol Camp. To be honest, the camp’s present state isn’t the same as the past. There’s nothing in the camp that could attract an expert. However, I still hope that you can join the camp. At the very least, you will be safer if you join us. And after you enter, I will tell the camp leader to concentrate the camp’s resources into cultivating you. With your talent, you will definitely be a famous expert in the region.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Instructor, there’s no need to go that far. I will join the Bone Symbol Camp because I want to. I definitely won’t regret this decision.”

Margaret nodded, then after a moment she said, “I’ll give you more freedom when we go back to the Academy. This way, you can adapt to the spiritual qi at your own pace. Once you adapt to the normal density, you can tell me and I will let you graduate in advance.”

Zhao Hao nodded. To be honest, he didn’t want to stay in the academy anymore. And he also wanted to adjust to the Machine Field’s normal spiritual qi density as soon as possible so that he could strengthen himself more effectively. He wanted to advance quicker so that he could gain a footing in the World of Cultivation, as well as providing Laura and the others with an identity This way, they would be able to boldly move about in the Machine Field and not stay inside the Space all the time.

Margaret added, “I’ve already informed the family. They will be sending support but they would arrive the day after tomorrow. You need to be careful in these two days. Although nobody would dare make a large-scale assault on Tyro Planet, this doesn’t mean that they won’t send someone to do assassination. If you have nothing to do, it would be best if you stay inside your room.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Alright. Instructor can rest assured.” Margaret nodded before she stood up and left.

Through this event, Zhao Hai was able to confirm that the Bone Symbol camp had already settled on recruiting him. Otherwise, Margaret wouldn’t have told him that they would allocate all their resources in order to cultivate him.

Besides this, Zhao Hai also discovered something from Margaret’s words. First, it seems to be true that the Bone Symbol Camp lacked experts. And second, Margaret’s was certainly someone of considerable status.

After Margaret left, Zhao Hai immediately entered the Space. Seeing Zhao Hai return, Laura and the others quickly welcomed him. Then Laura said, “Brother Hai, that was dangerous. You need to be more careful.” Zhao Hai just smiled and said, “It’s fine, you don’t need to worry. You heard Teacher Margaret, after returning to the academy, I will be able to adapt to the normal level of spiritual qi quicker. This way, I could leave the academy earlier. Once I leave, I will find a way so that you can go out. You don’t have to stay inside the Space every day.”

When they heard Zhao Hai, Laura and the others immediately cheered. For them, this was a very important matter. They’ve already seen how colorful the Machine Field was, so they all wanted to explore the place with their own eyes. It was just a pity that they had yet to gain the opportunity to do so. So when Zhao Hai told them about this, they couldn’t help but be happy.

Seeing their happy expressions, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but be happy as well. After everyone had calmed down, Zhao Hai said, “However, we still have to stay in Tyro Planet for a couple of days. I plan to use these days to take a look at the tunnels and take normal mithril for ourselves. It would be a waste if I couldn’t get some mithril after coming here.’

Laura smiled and said, “You don’t need to worry yourself about this. Since we’ve been here already, you can return at any time. I think what you need to focus on right now is to improve your combat effectiveness. Right, if you have time, you should go to the mining city and buy some gifts for Dins and the others. If Brother Hai really wants Dins and the others to follow you in the future, you need to increase their strength and provide them with formations to practice on. Take Dins for example, he’s a Fire Mage so he should be studying fire element formations. You can give him a combined formation and have him condense a formation that suits him best. Not only would he get stronger, he will also feel indebted to you. Although Margaret said that the Bone Symbol Camp would concentrate on cultivating you, there would still be people inside the camp that will feel dissatisfied with this decision. Therefore, you need to cultivate your own group.”

After listening to Laura, Zhao Hai felt that her words were justified. If he joins the Bone Symbol Camp in the future, he would need to cultivate his own influence. Otherwise, he would be isolated. Although Dins and the others were older, Zhao Hai didn’t find any problems with them. The Space had potions that can extend life so they should be able to live a couple of hundred years more. Moreover, as their cultivation increased, their lifespan would also increase. When the time comes, they would be experts that nobody would dare underestimate.

As long as Zhao Hai shows them favor now, then when he joins the Bone Symbol Camp later, he wouldn’t be afraid of being surrounded on all sides. He would have his own group to rely on.

With this thought in mind, Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Alright, I’ll listen to you. I’ll use these days to practice. Right Cai’er, I was thinking of using potions to break through my bottleneck. Help me look for herbs that can allow me to break through to the second layer of the Stellar Transformations art. I always felt that breaking through the second layer would bring me a huge benefit.” Cai’er nodded. Then she turned around and flew away. At this point, Little Silver had become Cai’er’s assistant, following behind her all the time. As for Bubble, the fellow actually liked to hang around in the villa alongside Laura and the others. The women were already used to its existence. They even use Bubble as a pillow from time to time.

By this time, Zhao Hai had lost interest in dealing with Bubble. Although this fellow looks lazy, its strength was actually pretty good. Zhao Hai had already placed a lot of things inside Bubble’s body to undergo water refining. Among these things were two grown azure dragon snails as well as the column of ice where Bubble was originally taken from.

It needs to be said that Zhao Hai was able to learn about the azure dragon snails in the Machine Field. As long as the snails were refined to a certain degree, they could be used as a warship. As for the column of ice, it was born from Bubble and was very rich in the water element. This type of material had numerous uses in the Machine Field. There would definitely be great uses for it in the future.

Chapter 1104: Bone Symbol Camp’s Hope

Just an hour after Zhao Hai started cultivating inside the Space, Cai’er suddenly went to look for him. Upon seeing Cai’er, Zhao Hai knew that she was here regarding the potion that he needed to break through.

Sure enough, when Cai’er reached Zhao Hai, she said, “Young Master, we’ve found a potion for your cultivation. However, it needs some time to brew. Moreover, you also need a massive amount of spiritual qi when you consume it. How much spiritual qi you absorb will have a great impact on your strength.”

Zhao Hai nodded. Then he said, “Are you saying that the spiritual qi inside the Space and the Academy are not enough? So do we need the Machine Field’s spiritual qi in order for me to advance?”

Cai’er nodded, “Yes, Young Master. Also, Sister Laura and the others just checked online and discovered that there’s a spirit gathering formation in the Machine Field. It can accumulate massive amounts of spiritual qi in a specific area. Moreover, we’ve analyzed that as Young Master adapts to the Machine Field’s spiritual qi, the spiritual qi in the Space will also increase up to the point where it will be the same as the Machine Field. Therefore, it would be better for you to get used to the Machine Field’s spiritual qi first before trying to increase your strength. This way, we can arrange the spiritual gathering formation when you can absorb the most spiritual qi.”

Zhao Hao nodded and said, “Alright, then I’ll wait. However, you still need to prepare that potion. This way, we could avoid later troubles.”

Cai’er nodded, then she turned around and left. Zhao Hai put the matter of his promotion to the back of his mind as he continued to practice. By dinnertime, Zhao Hai went out of the Space. He reckons that people would bring him supper. But he didn’t expect that not long after he came out, a knock would come from his door. Sweeping using his spiritual force, it was actually Margaret.

This caused Zhao Hai to stare. Him and Margaret weren’t too familiar with each other. Their encounters with each other were minimal. If he were to count the times they had met, it wouldn’t reach ten. Margaret looking for him at this time caused Zhao Hai to be puzzled.

However, Zhao Hai still opened the door. Upon seeing Margaret, he pretended to be surprised as he said, “Instructor Margaret, why are you here?”

After seeing Zhao Hai, Margaret smiled faintly as she answered, “What? You don’t want me to come? It’s not good to cultivate inside your room every day. Good cultivation is a balance between hard work and relaxation. Follow me to the dining hall. The crew are there. You need to mingle with them.”

When he heard Margaret, Zhao Hai understood why she came to see him. Naturally, Zhao Hai wouldn’t reject the invitation, so he said, “Alright, then I’ll have to trouble Instructor.”

Margaret nodded, then he led Zhao Hai towards the dining hall. Zhao Hai also discovered that since he offered his help in the recent crisis, Margaret began to have changes in her attitude.

The two arrived at the dining hall. And sure enough, the spaceship’s crew was already inside. Seeing Zhao Hai arrive, they immediately welcomed him enthusiastically.

Zhao Hai also knew that these people were happy because they were able to preserve their lives. Even if they were paid highly, the risk they had to go through was also equally as high. Moreover, their strengths aren’t that great, they were just average people.

Regarding these people, finding a stable and high-paying job was something that brought them great joy and satisfaction. After all, in the Machine Field, they simply held little to no status.

Just like ordinary people, the crew also had families to feed. If they died, even if the Ashley Family provided their families with pension, their family’s living conditions would still drastically decline. Because of this, these people were very grateful to survive the recent ordeal.

Zhao Hai didn’t put too much air as he politely returned the crew’s greetings. Seeing Zhao Hai’s conduct, the crew were immediately won over. It didn’t take long before the Zhao Hai became one with whole group.

Margaret and Kirk sat on another table. This table was smaller, and those who were sitting with them were the ship’s first and second mates. In other words, sat on this table were people who had status.

Kirk looked at Zhao Hai’s conduct and couldn’t help but smile as he turned to Margaret and said, “Miss Margaret, it seems like an extraordinary fellow would be joining our Bone Symbol Camp. He also looks like someone who had killed other god-rank experts. Otherwise, he wouldn’t have been this calm.”

Kirk as well as his two mates were also from the Bone Symbol Camp. Just as stated before, this camp was structured differently compared to the other camps. Other camps would just recruit talented individuals and wouldn’t care about other people. The Bone Symbol Camp, on the other hand, would accept anyone as long as they show skill.

Margaret smiled and said, “Zhao Hai is truly special. You might not know, but he already has his own group in the academy. Moreover, these people are unlike those blind followers of young geniuses. Also, you’re right. It seems like this guy has slaughtered at least a million people in the lower realms.”

Kirk and the other two people from the Bone Symbol camp knew what killing a million people meant. So when they heard Margaret, their expression couldn’t help but change. The first mate commented, “Killing a million people? He doesn’t look like it.”

Margaret replied, “From what I saw, it’s possible that he had killed a million people. Before he entered the exam’s mining tunnel, he asked me if there would be problems if the Adam Academy’s six students die. But as he asked me, I couldn’t feel a sliver of killing intent. Additionally, his calm manner in the earlier crisis only appears on two types of people. The first type are those who are very confident in their strength. They don’t believe that the destruction of the ship would have any effects on them. The second type are those who don’t think seriously about human lives. I think Zhao Hai is the latter. Because of this, I believe that Zhao Hai had killed more than a million people.”

Kirk turned towards Zhao Hai who was currently chatting with the crew. No matter how he looked at it, Kirk couldn’t see Zhao Hai as someone who had killed a million people.

However, Kirk also knew that people had all sorts of mysterious means and secrets. He was just curious so he didn’t say anything.

On the other hand, Kirk’s second mate was more curious. He turned to Margaret and said, “Miss Margaret, how long has it been since Zhao Hai came to the academy? Why haven’t I heard of his name before?”

Margaret turned towards them and then lowered her voice as she said, “Zhao Hai just ascended a month ago. Also, you didn’t hear any of this. If others know that Zhao Hai became a level 1 Mage a month after ascending, then he will be in certain danger.”

Although Kirk and the others didn’t cultivate, after serving the ascender academy, they knew what being a level 1 Mage just a month after ascending represented. In all of their time serving the academy, this was the first time that they heard an achievement as great as this.

Margaret looked at Kirk and said, “You know our camp’s current situation. And you should be aware that Zhao Hai’s strength isn’t normal. His talent is very great. Not only was he able to become a level 1 mage before the exam, he also achieved skill in utilizing Magic Theory properly. His future development should be limitless. Because of this, we cannot reveal that he had only ascended for one month. We should tell everybody that he had ascended 5 months ago. If we don’t, not only do we need to be on guard against outside powers, we also need to be wary about the family’s other camps. Those fellows don’t want the Bone Symbol Camp to rise again.”

As a member of the Bone Symbol Camp, Kirk was aware of the infighting amongst the family’s camps. What Margaret said was correct. If other camps discover Zhao Hai’s special talent, they would certainly deal with him. Because of this, the three nodded, then Kirk said, “Miss Margaret, rest assured. We know how to keep a secret. The other camps have stepped on the Bone Symbol Camp all these years. Now that Zhao Hai is here, it’s natural that we would take care of him.”

Margaret nodded, then her eyes began to light up as she said, “Zhao Hai will certainly become a pillar of the Bone Symbol Camp. With his help, the camp would rise again.”

Kirk and the others agreed. If the Bone Symbol Camp wanted to rise, then they would need an expert at its head. But at this time, the camp had no experts that can assume command. The Bone Symbol Camp didn’t lack funds. The External Hall would certainly allocate funds to make the camps function. Moreover, they can also generate income on their own.

Although the Bone Symbol Camp didn’t have powerful experts, their ability to make money was second to none in the Ashley Family. However, the Bone Symbol camp also knew that increasing their ability to make money would only bring them trouble.

Because of this, the Bone Symbol Camp had always hoped for a powerful expert to join their ranks. But because of its deteriorating reputation, talented students didn’t choose the camp. This caused the camp to lack powerful experts. This was the Bone Symbol Camp’s weakest point.

After the meal, Zhao Hai returned to his room. It was already late into the night, therefore, Zhao Hai didn’t head out and instead he just entered the Space. And after practicing for a while, he took a rest.

The next morning, Zhao Hai went out of the Space and had his breakfast at the dining hall. Just as he was about to head out, Margaret and the crew arrived. Seeing that Zhao Hai was leaving, Margaret wrinkled her brow as she asked, “Zhao Hai, are you planning to head out?”

Zhao Hai stared for a moment before he answered, “Instructor, I haven’t explored Tyro planet before so I want to head out and see it for myself. I also want to give Dins and the others some gifts. I heard that mithril here is much cheaper compared to other places. Since mithril is very helpful for Mages, I want to buy some before I head back.”

Margaret frowned, “It’s dangerous outside. I suggest that you don’t go. Pirates may be watching and waiting for us to head out.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Instructor, it will be fine. I still have strength to fight back. You can rest assured that nothing will happen to me.”

Margaret shook her head. But after thinking that Zhao Hai had been inside his room all this time, she couldn’t help but feel embarrassed. So after a while, she said, “Alright, you can go. But I will come with you.”

Zhao Hai stared, then with a shy expression, he looked at Margaret and said, “Instructor, there’s no need. I can go by myself.”

Margaret coldly snorted and said, “No. Either I go with you or you’re not leaving.”

Zhao Hai looked awkwardly at Margaret. But in the end, he gave a helpless nod and agreed, “Alright. Right, since Instructor is going, why don’t the others come as well? If you see anything you like, just tell me and I’ll buy it for you as a gift.”

Zhao Hai’s offer made the crew cheer. Then all of them grouped up and walked out. Margaret looked at the crowd around Zhao Hai and couldn’t help but helplessly shake her head. She didn’t know if she should praise Zhao Hai for being generous or scold him for spending too much money.

Although it was true that mithril and mithril products were much cheaper in Tyro Planet, besides those, other items were much more expensive in comparison. Besides being a mining planet, Tyro Planet was also a tourism spot. And one major characteristic of a tourist spot was its inflated price on goods. It seems like Zhao Hai was going to bleed today.

Margaret quickly followed behind Zhao Hai and the others. Actually, Tyro Planet’s mining city wasn’t any different compared to other cities. Besides its houses being caves and not seeing the sun, the other facilities weren’t that different from other planets. And also, compared to other planets, the amount of mithril products here were indeed a lot more.

Along with the jolly crew of the ship, Zhao Hai walked on the city streets. They didn’t ride a vehicle and instead opted to walk on foot. There were a lot of shops in this street. Besides shops, there were also stalls selling wares. But since these stalls didn’t have any high-quality goods, Zhao Hai didn’t bother looking.

Then suddenly, Zhao Hai felt a few hostile gazes directed at them. Zhao Hai swept the area using his spiritual force and found out that the gazes came from a couple of Mages sitting in a small teahouse. Although they seem to be laid-back, their eyes wandered murderously towards Zhao Hai’s group from time to time.

Chapter 1105: Assassination!

Zhao Hai had experienced countless killings, so he was very sensitive when it came to killing intent. Therefore, upon sensing the killing intent directed at him, Zhao Hai knew that these people were the pirates.

Zhao Hai didn’t say anything, instead, she contacted Cai’er with his mind, “Cai’er, pay attention to those Mages in the teahouse. Record their faces and see if they’re the same as the pirates we met before.” Cai’er immediately complied.

After this exchange, Zhao Hai carried on and strolled with the ship’s crew. Then suddenly, Zhao Hai’s attention was taken by a magic staff in a nearby shop. Also, the ship’s sign looked like it had been there for many years, making the shop look ancient.

The signboard was made of wood, contrasting the other high-tech signboards of its neighbors. The signboard’s print was also very common, making it look like the ugly duckling among the group.

However, Zhao Hai was dazed by this sign board. This was because he could feel magic coming from the piece of wood. It seems like the signboard wasn’t made with simple methods.

Seeing Zhao Hai stop, the crew became confused. One of them looked at Zhao Hai and asked, “Zhao Hai? What are you staring at?”

Zhao Hai recovered. Then he looked at the others as he smiled and said, “Everyone, let me take a look at that shop for a moment. I want to buy some things for my friends back at the academy. Mithril is very cheap here, so I want to see what that shop has to offer.” The crew were originally invited by Zhao Hai to play. So upon hearing him, they immediately nodded and joined him in entering the shop.

The shop wasn’t big. So when Zhao Hai’s group of more than ten entered, they immediately made the place cramped.

Zhao Hai proceeded to examine the shop. It was very ordinary. It had wooden shelves and containers that looked like they were made a long time ago. They were also covered with glass, adding to their unique look. The staff displayed on these shelves and containers were also very plain. Beneath each staff was its name and then its price.

As soon as Zhao Hai’s group entered the shop, a robot quickly received them. The robot bowed and said, “Welcome. What can I help you with?”

The robot looked ordinary, just like the shop. Although it was a bit more advanced than TInkle, it still wasn’t advanced. Zhao Hai didn’t care as he replied, “I need several magic staffs. Let me see your catalogue.”

The robot immediately complied as it said, “Please wait a moment.” Then the robot went to one side of the store and took out a book from a cabinet. After handing the book over to Zhao Hai, it said, “All of our magic staff are listed here.”

Zhao Hao nodded, then he opened the book. Although it looked like a book, it was actually an electronic display. Once a page was opened, a projection of the magic staff would appear. Then a voice would be heard, introducing the staff’s functions as well as the magic formation recorded inside.

This kind of things was rare in the Machine Field. Zhao Hao flipped the book as he paired them with the numbers below the staffs on the cabinets. He was looking for staffs suited for Dins and the others.

Honestly, the mage staffs in this store were really good. All of the staff were made of wood that were suited for Mages to use. They were also engraved with five-layer formations for level 1 Mages and formations for level 2 Mages. The shop didn’t have staffs surpassing level 3. However, this selection still caught Zhao Hai’s eyes. After all, Dins and the others had yet to reach level 1. Giving them too advanced staffs wouldn’t be good.

Margaret stood at the back, observing Zhao Hai earnestly scanning through the staffs. She couldn’t help but sigh, she began to understand Zhao Hai less and less. A month after ascending, he was already a level 1 Mage. It can be said that he was a genius. It was normal for these kinds of people to be arrogant. However, Zhao Hai wasn’t arrogant at all. Not only did he befriend Old Mages like Dins and the others, he could also mingle with the ship’s crew. Such a person was truly rare.

Margaret couldn’t help but wonder what kind of place could train someone such as Zhao Hai. One must know that each young ascender from the lower realms were very talented individuals. They most likely had powerful influences supporting them back in the lower realm. Besides cultivating, all of their other needs were well taken care of. Because of this, these talents developed arrogant behaviours.

Zhao Hai was a genius among geniuses. Since he was able to ascend at a young age, this meant that he also had a huge background. However, Zhao Hai was experienced in battle. He also had well-developed social skills. Margaret even suspected Zhao Hai of killing more than a million people. Putting these facts together, it seems like Zhao Hai was different compared to the others of his kind.

Zhao Hai bought 15 level 1 staffs. After paying nearly twenty thousand machine coins, the group proceeded to walk out of the shop.

And just as they came out, Cai’er’s voice resounded inside Zhao Hai’s head, “Young Master, we’ve investigated those people. They were indeed the pirates that attacked the ship. There’s no mistaking it.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he stepped back two steps to Margaret’s side and said, “Instructor, the pirates that attacked us are close by. Moreover, we’ve already been surrounded. We need to see that our brothers are safe..”

Margaret stared, then her expression turned cold. She turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Are you sure?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, ”I’m very sure. I’m quite sensitive to killing intent. Moreover, their glares didn’t stop. Before we went into the shop, I saw a few Mages at a teashop. At that time, I thought that they looked like the people that attacked our ship. And now, I feel their murderous intent. It seems like they’re ready to take action.”

At this point, Margaret already had great trust towards Zhao Hai. So she immediately replied, “Alright, I’ll tell the crew to return.”

Zhao Hai shook his head and whispered, “We can’t just abruptly retreat. Otherwise, the pirates would make their move. We need to divert their attention. Instructor, as long as we guard the crew, it’ll be fine.”

Margaret nodded, she couldn’t help but raise her spiritual force. Zhao Hai looked around him and sneered. Then he turned to the crew and laughingly said, “Brothers, I managed to buy a lot of good staffs today. I want to celebrate. How about we drink at that bar over there?” Then he pointed at a roadside bar.

Although the crew couldn’t understand why Zhao Hai suddenly decided to have a drink, liquor was always welcomed. The crew didn’t become polite and just cheered as they ran towards the bar.

Upon seeing the crew running, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but laugh as he shouted, “You heard drinking and you ran faster than anyone I know. If I don’t follow behind, who would pay for your drinks?”

Knowing Zhao Hai was just having a playful banter, one of the crew replied, “We’ll just tell them to put the drinks on your tab. Brothers, let’s run faster. We must drink at least two bottles today!”

Zhao Hai pretended to be anxious as he ran after them towards the bar, saying, “Brothers, don’t drink too much. I might not be able to afford it all.” Then he showed the physical weakness of a Mage. Even when the crew had entered the bar, Zhao Hai still fell behind.

Looking at Zhao Hai’s acting, Margaret couldn’t help but commend him secretly. Zhao Hai’s words made the crew run faster and his acting was on point.

At this time, Zhao Hai suddenly cast a formation in front of him. Then a big sword flew out of the formation and went straight towards the bar’s second floor.

Just as the sword was about to hit the bar’s window, a barrier appeared and blocked Zhao Hai’s attack.

However, after releasing the sword, Zhao Hai followed up with a five-layer formation. A fiery spear emerged out of the formation and chased behind the sword and also hit the barrier.

One could see a faint silhouette of a person right behind the barrier. The person easily blocked the sword, but the fiery spear caught him off-guard. The fiery spear tore through the barrier as though it was paper and then stabbed the person behind it. The man screamed for a moment before the fiery spear exploded.

After the loud explosion, the person’s entire body was erased. However, what was strange was the fact that although the person was killed, and the bar’s window was damaged, nothing else was affected by Zhao Hai’s attack.

Zhao Hai didn’t stop. He released another five-layer formation. When the formation appeared, a burst of dark mist suddenly spread out, covering the entire street. One couldn’t even see their own fingers if they stretched it out.

Chapter 1106: Choosing A Battlefield

As the Dark Mist spread, Zhao Hai immediately flew towards Margaret’s side and whispered, “Instructor, I can feel their position and they can’t sense us. Once they enter the dark mist, we can deal with them.”

Margaret nodded. She also felt her own spiritual force being greatly suppressed. One must know that Margaret was a level 5 Mage. Her spiritual force was very strong. But in this dark mist, her spiritual force could only reach 500 meters.

Zhao Hai continued to whisper, “Instructor, come with me to the bar first. Let’s take the crew go to a safe place. My magic will last for a while. But if they use light magic, then the most it could last is ten minutes. We need to save the crew during that time before we can move on our own.”

Margaret agreed, then she said, “Ten minutes is enough. And don’t forget, Tyro Planet has guards. Since we just made a huge move, they would definitely be alarmed. Ten minutes is enough for them to rush over.”

Zhao hai nodded. Then he caught Margaret’s body and then led her towards the bar.

The people inside the bar were also aware of what just happened outside. Because of this, nobody went out. Some of them even hid below the tables.

The magic Zhao Hai used didn’t just cover the street, it shrouded the bar as well. However, this magic didn’t affect Zhao Hai. After Zhao Hai and Margaret entered the bar, he immediately let go of her hand and said, “Instructor, stay here while I go look for the others.”

Margaret, who has never been pulled by a man before, was now blushing. She just nodded as Zhao Hai went towards a table. Naturally, the crew were the ones drinking there. When they heard the commotion, they immediately hid under the table.

When Zhao Hai arrived at the table and saw the crew’s state, he couldn’t help but laugh. Then he knocked on the table and said, “Alright, you need to get out of here.” Then he waved his hand. A light quickly covered the table, dispersing the dark mist around the crew.

When the crew members heard Zhao Hai’s voice, they couldn’t help but stare. They looked up and saw Zhao Hai standing in front of them. After a short pause, the crew immediately jumped up.

Zhao Hai made a gesture to silence them and then whispered, “Listen to me, the pirates that attacked us are here. I just killed one of them. I’ll send someone to lead you out of this area. Remember, unless he disappears, you shouldn’t come out.” After he said that, Zhao Hai waved his hand and summoned a skeleton.

The crew knew that this wasn’t the time to talk, so they just nodded and followed the skeleton. Meanwhile, Zhao Hai’s body disappeared and went to Margaret’s side.

Margaret had already calmed down at this time. Although her spiritual force has been suppressed, she was still able to know what happened inside the bar. Naturally, she was able to see Zhao Hai’s action. When Zhao Hai returned, she immediately said, “There’s no visibility in the dark mist. Are they not going to attack?”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “They will. They are still outside the dark mist. Maybe they want us to think that they won’t attack. It would be more dangerous for us if the guards don’t arrive for some time. This way, the pirates can be more assured to take bolder actions.”

Margaret thought about what Zhao Hai said for a moment, then she said, “That’s impossible. Tyro Planet is supported by the three major groups. It isn’t that easy to bribe the guards of the three powers at the same time.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Then that means they used other methods to lure the guards away. Instructor, we need to find a way to deal with them. It would be good if we could break out of the encirclement.”

Margaret nodded, “Alright. But don’t you feel that their encirclement is quite tight?” Margaret couldn’t help but feel regret. She had been very negligent. On the entire ship, only she and Zhao Hai could use magic. The others were just ordinary people, they couldn’t provide any firepower.

Moreover, Margaret wasn’t a fool. They had been entangled with the pirates yet the guards had yet to arrive. This meant that the enemy had prepared themselves well. It seems like they planned to deal with the Ashley Family’s group today.

Upon thinking about this, Margaret turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Zhao Hai, I’m afraid that even if we break through, they still won’t let us go easily. At the earliest, the people from the family would arrive tomorrow. Before that time, we will be in constant danger.”

Zhao Hai thought for a moment before he said, “Instructor. I think we need to find a proper battlefield for us to fight in. Doing it in this city is certainly not good. We couldn’t move properly knowing that innocents might be caught in the crossfire. We would also be in trouble if the three powers look into the fight and see the damage we did to the city. Additionally, they have a lot of people surrounding us. We need an environment that is more complex and easier to hide in.”

Margaret agreed, “Aren’t you good at dark magic? Why don’t we enter a tunnel. That kind of environment should suit our needs.”

Upon hearing Margaret, Zhao Hai’s eyes shone. Then he immediately agreed, “Instructor, I just thought about a place. As long as we lure them there, I can guarantee that none of them would be able to return.”

When Margaret heard Zhao Hai, she couldn’t help but ask, “Are you thinking about the exam’s tunnel?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “The exam’s tunnel has a large amount of dark energy. If we enter there, we could use dark magic at full strength. And with my summoning magic, they will surely die.”

Margaret paused for a moment, then she frowned and asked, “But do you know the way to the tunnel? Moreover, that place is quite far from here. Will those people follow?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Of course they will. They want to kill us. So if we go to a remote place, they will be more than happy to follow. Most importantly, if we attract their attention, the crew will be safe. I reckon the Mage and Warriors attacking us wouldn’t make the crew their priority. Also, I was able to remember the path I went through when I took the exam. Instructor can trust me on this.”

Margaret nodded, “They wouldn’t attack the crew who can’t use magic. Alright, let’s head there.” She might not be aware of it, but Margaret had already began to blindly trust Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Alright. Follow me. Let’s break through their encirclement first. Then we’ll run straight towards the tunnel.” He didn’t wait for Margaret to respond as his body suddenly flew. Margaret followed closely behind.

Zhao Hai sped towards the people on the opposite side of the bar. At this time, Zhao Hai took out a magic staff. This staff wasn’t the blood ghost staff. Instead, it was a staff he just recently bought. It was a light element staff.

When Margaret saw Zhao Hai take out the light element staff, she couldn’t help but stare. Low-level light magic can be said to be the weakest of its rank. Only when it reaches higher levels would light magic be considered very powerful. So why did Zhao Hai take out a light element staff?

After taking the staff out, Zhao Hai turned to Margaret and said, “Instructor, in a while, make sure to close your eyes.”

Margaret finally understood what Zhao Hai wanted to do, she couldn’t help but secretly nod. She was already aware that Zhao Hai was an all-element Mage. However, Zhao Hai was still level one, which was the lowest level when it came to Magic Theory. Nevertheless, if Zhao Hai was skillful in his usage of magic, then he was someone that couldn’t be underestimated.

Magic Theory and lower realm magic were still somewhat related. In the lower realms, all-element Mages were very powerful even at lower levels. However, this was given that they were able to utilize their magic properly. They need to be able to discern which magic was appropriate to use at a certain time.

Even if a spell wasn’t strong, as long as it is used properly, it could still kill someone. And even if someone could use strong magic, if they didn’t know when to use it, then their efforts would just be wasted. Because of this, there was a saying among Mages, ‘There are no bad spells, only garbage Mages.’

At this time, the attackers were fully focused on the dark mist. A sudden eruption of light magic from the darkness would certainly disorientate them. Even if it was a low-level spell, the abrupt change in brightness would still blind them. And once they were blinded, they would panic, fully disturbing their encirclement. This would give Zhao Hai and Margaret an opportunity to escape.

It didn’t take long before the two arrived on the street. Margaret felt two hidden spiritual forces at an intersection nearby. It seems like two Mages were hidden near that place.

These two spiritual forces were very well hidden. Margaret even failed to notice them before. Even now, if she wasn’t concentrating, she wouldn’t have been able to see them.

This caused Margaret to be surprised. She was a level 5 Mage, a level most Mages wouldn’t reach in their lifetime. And now, there was Zhao Hai. Was his spiritual force stronger than her’s?

Without delaying, Zhao Hai waved the staff in his hand as he said, “Burst Light!” And with his voice, a five-layer formation suddenly appeared and then exploded. The explosion emitted an incomparably bright light. This turned everything around him into white. The two Mages who were waiting for them felt a stabbing pain in their eyes before their vision was completely blocked.

Chapter 1107: A Demon?

Zhao Hai didn’t make a move on the two Mages. He just said, “Let’s go.”

Then after he said that, Zhao Hai went to the alleys. If Zhao Hai was by himself, then he would’ve killed the two Mages with his sword. But since Margaret was with him, he cannot do that. He wasn’t prepared to reveal his cards yet.

While they were quickly flying on the street, Zhao Hai also released flying needles in order to scout the surrounding terrain. This way, they wouldn’t walk into a dead end.

The longer Margaret flew beside Zhao Hai, the more curious she became. She was able to see Zhao Hai suddenly turn to a corner from time to time. Although they were being chased by a large number of Mages and Warriors, they had never been stopped. Zhao Hai seems to be very familiar with the streets here.

While Margaret was thinking about this, she discovered that they were already outside the city; at the entrance of the mining tunnels. However, the entrance to the tunnel was covered by a fence which read ‘Examination tunnel. No entry.’

Margaret didn’t expect them to really reach this point. At this time, Zhao Hai waved his hand, releasing a spell that exploded the fence. Then he immediately flew in.

Without even the time to process her thoughts, Margaret also flew into the tunnel. However, Margaret could still feel that they were being pursued. She was also able to see that there weren’t any level 5 experts among them. The highest was only level 4.

Margaret’s strength was higher, but she wouldn’t dare go around and fight it out with them. This was because there were just too many of them. Margaret felt that their pursuers numbered no less than 50. And there weren’t just Mages, there were Warriors among them as well. And worst one being level 2. In this situation, if she did decide to fight, then she would be courting death.

Margaret followed Zhao Hai into the mine, with their pursuers closely behind. When they were in the city, the Mages and Warriors were afraid of destroying any buildings. But now, they didn’t have this concern anymore. So from time to time, magic and sword qi were being sent towards Zhao Hai and Margaret.

The two flew quickly. Also, since the tunnel wasn’t a straight line, the enemy had yet to overtake them.

The dark energy in the tunnel gradually became thicker. Although Zhao Hai had already mined the ghost mithril and taken Little Silver, there was still remnant dark energy in the tunnel. After all, after many years of accumulation, it wouldn’t disappear in such a short time.

However, it was clear that neither Zhao Hai nor the pursuers cared about this. They knew that this was the exam tunnel. And also, Tyro Planet’s examination site was well known to be fairly safe. Some of the pursuers had also taken their exams here. Because of this, they knew that there were no such dangers for them given their current strength.

Margaret kept following behind Zhao Hai’s figure all this time. To be honest, Margaret was forced to accept this arrangement. She had seen their pursuers, and she was now aware that the guards have been made unavailable. With so many people chasing them, this was definitely a trap.

If they fought in the city, then they might injure innocents or cause huge damage to property. When the time comes and the matter was solved, it was possible that the three powers would use this excuse to cause trouble to the Ashley Family. At the very least, they would not let off the Bone Symbol Camp. And Margaret didn’t want to pull the camp into this conflict.

Because of this, Margaret agreed to Zhao Hai’s plan on going to the tunnels. Not only would they ensure the crew’s safety, she would also have the space to annihilate these fellows. Even if she couldn’t kill them all, with the tunnel’s terrain, she could at least get rid of some of them.

The two quickly flew straight ahead. Their pursuers weren’t slow either. Both sides were separated by about 500 meters. It would be impossible to hide from the Mages and Warriors at this distance. As long as they stay close to Margaret and Zhao Hai, tracking magic can be used to follow them all the time. During times where they caught glimpses of Zhao Hai and Margaret, the pursuers couldn’t help but smirk.

Margaret was just following behind Zhao Hai at this point. She couldn’t recognize the tunnel anymore. She believed that if Zhao Hai left her here, then she might take a very long time to return.

At this time, Zhao Hai’s voice was heard, “Instructor, we’re arriving at the exam’s mining tunnel. Make sure to follow closely behind.” Margaret nodded.

When the two entered the dark tunnel, Zhao Hai immediately released dark magic. This dark magic not only made the dark mist in the tunnel thicker, it could also conceal their presence.

After releasing this magic, Zhao Hai quickly brought Margaret to hide in a nearby cave. Then they both stood there quietly.

Margaret kept still as she just stood there, looking at their pursuers arrive. As the Mages and Warriors entered, Margaret counted them all. There were actually 78!

Zhao Hai whispered, “Seventy-eight people. Forty Mages, Thirty-eight Warriors. Eighteen level 2’s, all of them Warriors. 20 Mages and 20 Warriors at level 3. And then 20 level 4 Mages. This isn’t a small force. Hmmm, that’s not correct, there are also two assassins. It seems like these people really want us dead.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Margaret couldn’t help but stare. She whispered, “Assassins? There are Assassins?” She failed to sense these Assassins. Now that she heard Zhao Hai, she couldn’t help but be shocked.

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Right, they’re about level 3. They almost evaded my notice. They’re quite strong.”

Margaret slowly wrinkled her brow, “What should we do now?”

Zhao Hai didn’t turn towards Margaret as he smiled faintly and said, “What do we do? Easy, make sure that these 80 people don’t run away. They will become members of my Undead Army.”

After that, Zhao Hai waved his hand. Then as he made his signal, a spatial rift appeared beside him. It didn’t take long before large quantities of Undead flooded out of the rift and charged forward.

What made Margaret stare was the fact that the Undead seem to be inexhaustible. She tried counting them all but soon found out that there were too many of them.

Margaret might not be surprised if it was just the number. The most important thing was the strength of these Undead. They were very strong. Although they were a bit worse than level 1 Mages, their strength couldn’t be said to be the worst in the Machine Field.

Levels in the Machine Field depended on Magic Theory. However, such classification was unfair to lower realm ascenders.

Ascenders from the lower realm hadn’t studied Magic Theory. Because of this, it was impossible for them to be level 1 Mages immediately. From Margaret’s estimation, lower realm ascenders should have at least level 3 spiritual force. It was only because they didn’t know Magic Theory that they weren’t classified as level 1.

If there was no Magic Theory, then there would be a lot of level 3 Mage and Warriors in the Machine Field. The natives would have no way of being stronger than ascenders. It can be said that Magic Theory was already biased against ascenders from the lower realms.

However, the world was unfair. You can’t blame anybody for being born in a lower realm. The heavens are blameless, this was a fact.

For Zhao Hai to release bordeling level 1 Undead was already a great feat.

People from the Machine Field didn’t fully neglect lower realm magic. After all, Magic Theory absorbed a lot from lower realm magic in order to be made. Therefore, Margaret had a clear understanding regarding lower realm magic. She knew that Mages from the lower realm could turn Undead into their summoned creatures. This method could also be used in the Machine Field. However, nobody used this method since the creatures summoned would be very weak. They were almost useless. A normal person in the Machine Field could casually destroy ten creatures summoned this way.

However, Zhao Hai’s summons had strength close to level 1 Mages. This caused Margaret to be startled. Not to say ordinary people, even those who had cultivated would be no match against these undead.

There were also 9 ranks in the Machine Field. However, they couldn’t be called true experts. Generally, people in these levels or lower were called apprentices; Mage Apprentice and Warrior Apprentice.

Only after breaking through beyond 9th rank could one become a level 1 Mage, a true Mage. Because of this, most level 1 Mages won’t pay attention to Apprentices.

However, this didn’t mean that they didn’t have any fighting strength. Compared to normal people, these Apprentices were still much better. This was especially true for 9th rank Apprentices. They were close to being level 1, so nobody looked down on their strength. If a level 4 Mage was surrounded by 100 9 ranks, then its possible they would be killed.

The biggest difference between Mage Apprentices and Mages was that Apprentices cannot practice Magic Theory. This didn’t mean that they weren’t allowed to study it, it was just that their spiritual force was insufficient. However, they were still able to study ordinary magic. And during this study, they would dabble in magic formations. This will help them in the future when they study Magic Theory.

It can be said that Apprentices were inferior to Ascenders when it came to spiritual force. However, Apprentices still had their own advantages. Compared to ascenders, they were more familiar with magic formations.

But in the end, spiritual force was the most important. Even if an apprentice was adept in magic formations, he still wouldn’t be able to reach level 1 if they lack the spiritual force needed. There were plenty of 9th ranks in the Machine Field that weren’t able to break through to level 1.

Because of this level division, Zhao Hai’s uncountable number of 9th rank Undead caused Margaret to be shocked.

Zhao Hai didn’t release a lot of Undead. He stopped when they reached 10 thousand. However, these Undead weren’t any ordinary Undead, all of them were wearing bone armor.

The Bone Armor Legion was Zhao Hai’s elite force in the Underworld. Upon arriving in the Machine Field, Zhao Hai wouldn’t dare to release ordinary Undead. This would just be sending the undead to their demise.

Currently, Zhao Hai’s Bone Armor Legion had reached thirty thousand. But this time, Zhao Hai only chose to release a third of them.

After releasing the Undead, Zhao Hai turned his head to Margaret and said, “Instructor, let’s go outside. So when we kill these people we would know where they came from.”

Margaret broke out of her shock, then she turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Zhao Hai, you brought all of these Undead from the lower realm? Did you make them?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Yes. I learned a secret method that can refine ordinary Undead into Advanced-level. All of these Undead are made by me.”

Margaret stared at Zhao Hai, her expression quite pale as she asked, “Are they people you killed?” Upon hearing Margaret, Zhao Hai nodded and said, “They are. But not all of them. There are many that can’t be used because I failed to refine them.”

Margaret’s expression turned paler. She looked at Zhao Hai and said, “How many people did you kill?”

Zhao Hai looked at Margaret’s expression and couldn’t help but smile faintly as he answered, “It would be best for you to not know.” After saying that, Zhao Hai went out of the cave. The Undead were already fighting against the Mages and Warriors.

Margaret looked at Zhao Hai’s departing back as her expression turned ugly. She believed Zhao Hai’s words. There were demonic characters in the lower realm that made undead by killing people. If such a person joins the Bone Symbol Camp, who knows if it was a blessing or a curse.

Chapter 1108: Fire Temple’s Zhang Family

Zhao Hai was calmly looking at the fight happening outside. He deliberately revealed that he had killed a lot of people, so he wasn’t surprised that Margaret knew. What he wanted to see was Margaret’s response.

Margaret was beside Zhao Hai. Although her eyes were directed at the fight inside the tunnel, one could see that her eyes were empty. It was obvious that her thoughts weren’t on the fight in front of her.

Zhao Hai’s words gave her quite the impact. She didn’t expect Zhao Hai to be so casual about his character. He was actually able to refine a lot of people into his summoned undead.

No matter which realm, such a person was called a demon. Even in the Devil Realm, there weren’t a lot of people like Zhao Hai.

When she thought of this, Margaret couldn’t help but turn her head towards Zhao Hai. At this time, Zhao Hai was focused on looking at the battlefield. His expression looked a little disturbed.

Margaret stared, then she hastily looked at the battlefield, thinking that the Undead might be having troubles dealing with the enemies.

But when she saw the situation, she gawked. This was because the undead were overpowering the pursuers. They were performing excellently. So why was Zhao Hai looking disturbed?

What Margaret didn’t know was that Zhao Hai didn’t treat Undead as mere tools. To him, they were living people who had their own identity. They were treated as Zhao Hai’s subordinates. Currently, Zhao Hai just felt the death of several hundred Undead. Because of this, his expression turned serious.

The fight didn’t last long. These Undead were Zhao Hai’s elite. In normal days, they would be in the Hell Space. They didn’t only cultivate, they also practiced battle formations and coordination. Because of this, the Mages and Warriors simply couldn’t do anything amidst the assault of the Undead.

In less than an hour, the 80 pursuers were completely eliminated. Margaret stared at the performance of the undead. The coordination between each Undead were simply fantastic. Even the Machine Field’s best army would have trouble mimicking such coordination.

With the fight finished, Zhao Hai waved his hand and received the Undead. The killed Undead were also taken back to be sent to the Hell Space and buried under the Bone Mountain. This has become a tradition among the Undead.

After receiving the Undead, Zhao Hai turned his attention to the corpses of the slain Mages and Warriors. After a short pause, Zhao Hai waved his hand and surrounded those bodies with black gas.

Zhao Hai’s didn’t use his ordinary black gas to turn these corpses into Undead. Instead, he added a 100-layer formation to amplify the effect.

Zhao Hai originally didn’t intend to go through so much trouble. He could just turn these bodies into Undead and then throw them into the Space. However, the scanner had analyzed this formation a long time ago. This was also the first 100-layer formation that Zhao Hai learned.

There wasn’t anything wrong with turning the corpses into Undead using Zhao Hai’s usual method. However, this formation wouldn’t only preserve the corpse’s intellect and memory, it could also minimize the loss of strength. For example, if a level 4 Mage were turned into an Undead using Zhao Hai’s old method, even if it was improved by the Space, it could only reach 9th rank strength. And in the Machine field, 8th or 9th rank Apprentices weren’t able to use Magic Theory.

But if he used this 100-layer formation, the Undead would keep their level 4 strength. This was why Zhao Hai’s settled on using this method. And since he didn’t want Margaret to see his 100-layer formation, he decided to cover himself with a thick dark mist.

Before long, Zhao Hai finished his magic. The dead Mages and Warriors were now standing, their weapons in their hands. Their strength had also been preserved. But since Zhao Hai didn’t want Margaret to know about his ability, he had the Undead be in their skeleton form.

Zhao Hai immediately interrogated the Undead. After getting the needed information, Zhao Hai turned to Margaret and said, “Instructor, does the Ashley Family have a grudge against the Fire Temple’s Zhang Family?”

When she heard Zhao Hai, Margaret couldn’t help but stare. Then her expression changed, “Fire Temple’s Zhang Family? They sent these people?” The Undead were in their skeleton form, so naturally they couldn’t talk. Zhao Hai communicated with them using his spiritual force. Margaret wasn’t able to hear anything.

Zhao Hai gave a nod and said, “They did. The Zhang Family’s target is you. Once they dealt with you, they would bring a calamity to the Adam Family. And once the Ashley Family and the Adam Family went to war, the Zhang Family would greatly benefit.”

Margaret coldly snorted and said, “Zhang Family, so it’s the Zhang Family. Good, good.”

Zhao Hai looked confused at Margaret’s reaction. Margaret looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Zhao Hai, I won’t hide anything from you. I’m actually the sixth daughter of the Ashely Family’s Current  Patriarch, Thunder Ashley. My mother was a lower realm ascender and married my father later on. However, my father didn’t treat mother well, causing mother to be depressed. When my mother ascended, she became a member of Bone Symbol Camp. And since I don’t want to join family struggles, I decided to join the Bone Symbol Camp as well and be a teacher at the academy. And when I was young, my father ordered me to marry the Zhang Family’s third son, Zhang Ming!”

When Zhao Hai’s heard this, his eyes couldn’t help but rise up as he said, “So the Ashley Family and the Zhang Family had a very good relationship?”

Margaret sneered and said, “Not only good, they’re known as our most faithful ally. I didn’t expect that this ally was actually the family’s biggest enemy.”

Zhao Hai looked at Margaret and said, “Instructor, what are you planning to do now?”

Margaret coldly snorted, “What else do I have to do? After I head back, I will immediately report this to father. Although he didn’t treat my mother well, he is still my father in the end. And I’m a member of the Ashley Family. If the family falls, then I won’t have a good life.”

Zhao Hai looked at Margaret and said, “Instructor, I suggest not telling your father about this yet. He wouldn’t believe you immediately. And even if you tell him, will he wage war with the Zhang Family? If your two families go to war, then only outsiders would benefit.”

Margaret stared, then she lightly frowned and said, “That’s true. But if I don’t tell him, then the Ashely Family wouldn’t be guarded against the Zhang Family.”

Zhao Hai also frowned. He knew that what Margaret said was true. But if they tell the Patriarch now, then the Ashely Family would be disadvantaged with the fallout.

Moreover, Margaret already said that her relationship with her father wasn’t good. Her father might not even believe the report.

But as a Patriarch, would he neglect this matter completely? Even if he didn’t believe it, he would still be wary of the Zhang Family. In this case, it would be good for the Ashley Family.

With this thought in mind, Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Reminding your father would be fine. But remember, you’re just reminding him. Don’t get too angry at the Zhang Family and make this matter known to everyone. The Ashley Family wouldn’t benefit if it wages war with the Zhang Family.”

When Margaret heard this, she couldn’t help but frown. Although her relationship with her father wasn’t very good, she knew her father well. The current Patriarch was a self-contained person. He wouldn’t easily listen to anyone else’s words. If she really told her father, then her father wouldn’t immediately believe it. And just like Zhao Hai said, they shouldn’t spread this matter.

Upon thinking about this, Margaret sighed and said, “Alright, I’ll deal with this matter. I won’t mention this matter to anyone.”

Zhao Hao nodded. When he saw Margaret’s expression, he knew that there were some underlying matters he was unaware of. However, these were things that were out of his hands.

Zhao Hai waved his hand and sent the Undead to the Space. However, there was no response from the Space, which surprised him.

In the past, when a strong Undead enters the Space, a prompt would always come up. But this time, after formidable Undead entered, there was nothing.

However, Zhao Hai changed his mind when he understood what was going on. Actually, this wasn’t the first time this has happened. Ever since he received Undead from the Underworld, the Space began to adjust.

For the Undead who haven’t reached demigod-level, the Space would automatically upgrade them. However, after they become demigods, they would have to rely on their efforts in order to progress.

This matter might also stem from the Space treating the Undead as their own independent race. In the past, the Space treated the Undead as robots, allowing the Undead to be upgraded.

Although it was a bit disappointing, Zhao Hai accepted the Space’s new way of handling the Undead. After all, he was the one who thought the Undead to be their own race. Therefore, he wasn’t opposed to the Spaces’ decision. In fact, it seems like the Space was adjusting to his own wishes.

Chapter 1109: The Guards Finally Arrive

Seeing Zhao Hai take his Undead back, Margaret began to relax. She can now affirm that Zhao Hai wasn’t the kind of person to kill people just to turn them into Undead. His current actions reflect what he did.

When Zhao Hai finished collecting his Undead, Margaret turned to look at him. It seems like Margaret was waiting for Zhao Hai to talk. Zhao Hai looked at Margaret and said, “Instructor, there seems to be 100 of them. 80 came after us and the rest went to the reception hotel. They’re planning on catching all of us in a net. Can the people in the hotel hold on?”

Upon hearing this, Margaret’s expression changed, then she said, “The reception should have some defenses of their own. But if the enemy has level 3 or level 4 Mages, they would find it difficult to defend. However, Sim is there. Although he isn’t very strong, he’s still a capable level 3 Mage. We should quickly head back.”

Zhao Hai thought for a moment and said, “Instructor, I have a spatial ability. We can use it to teleport back to the hotel. However, once we arrive, my strength would be completely drained. I won’t be able to help in dealing with the enemy.”

When Margaret heard him, her two eyes shone. Then she said, “Good, then let’s head back. Don’t worry about the enemy, I can deal with them.” Zhao Hai nodded, then he muttered some incantations before pointlessly waving his hands. Before long, a spatial passage appeared. Margaret followed closely behind after Zhao Hai entered. The next moment, the two were already inside the hotel.

As soon as they arrived, they immediately heard bursts of explosions coming from outside. Zhao Hai pretended to pale as he said, “Instructor, I need to adjust my breathing. I’ll leave this place to you.” Margaret nodded, then she turned around and went out. Before long, she arrived at the hall. Upon reaching the hall, Margaret knew where the explosions were coming from. The hotel actually had a defensive formation in place.

Defensive magic formations in the Machine Field were different than the ones back in the lower realms. In the Machine Field, defensive magic formations used crystals in order to operate. Because of this, the energy used in defending was much more powerful than defensive formations in the lower realms.

Upon seeing the crystal stones, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but stare. He didn’t expect the crystals inside the Space to be an important resource in the World of Cultivation.

Margaret looked at the shield that encircled the reception. Sim was standing behind it, occasionally firing spells towards the enemies outside. His appearance seemed to lack anxiety.

However, Margaret’s expression wasn’t very good. The fight in the reception lacked the presence of Tyro Planet’s guards. This meant that the people from Tyro Planet might have been bought.

Tyro Planet was an important mining site for mithril. The control of the three major powers over this place was quite strict. But now, attackers were in the city while the guards were nowhere to be found. This could mean that the guards were replaced, and that they were replaced by the enemy’s people.

If this was the case, then this action might not only involve the Fire Temple’s Zhang Family. The Zhang Family wasn’t powerful enough to accomplish this.

However, all of these things were just speculations inside Margaret’s head. She didn’t think too deeply into this matter. It was impossible for her to find out relevant information on her own.

After this thought, Margaret began to move. One must know that Margaret was a level 4 Mage. She might not like fighting and opted to teach and research magic formations, but she was still more skilled in using formations than most Mages.

If this was an ordinary fight, then Margaret might suffer a loss due to her inexperience. However, Margaret was in a defensive position, sending magic towards the opposing Mages. This was a different matter, she couldn’t be hit but she had all the avenues for attack. Naturally, it was the attackers who suffered losses.

The opposite party also discovered Margaret’s sudden appearance. Although they didn’t know how she was able to appear here, they knew that the assassination had failed.

Their main goal this time was to assassinate Margaret. They already surrounded the bar Margaret was in. They even prepared a back-up plan. If Margaret managed to break out of the encirclement, then she would definitely return to the reception. This was where another batch of ambushers would wait for her.

But unfortunately for them, the ordinary-looking Zhao Hai that they neglected completely ruined their plans. Instead of returning to the hotel, the two went to the mining tunnels instead.

With their main force pursuing the two into the mining tunnel, those left behind decided to assault the hotel in order to kill the ship’s crew. However, they failed to take into account the hotel’s defensive formation.

However, they weren’t worried. In their mind, it didn’t matter if they were stuck here. After all, their main goal was Margaret. As long as she was killed, the crew being alive or dead didn’t matter.

But now that Margaret appeared, they couldn’t help but panic. They didn’t know why Margaret was here, but they were aware that their operation had failed.

With the defensive formation in place as well as Margaret’s presence, assaulting the hotel was no longer possible. Moreover, they couldn’t attack for a long time. Although they had bribed this region’s garrison officer, if the guards took too long to respond, the garrison officer would get into trouble. With no time to change their strategy, the attackers were completely defeated.

The attackers looked at each other before their leader nodded and waved his hand. The attackers immediately withdrew from the scene. However, Margaret and the others didn’t take the defensive formation down. They didn’t know if an attack would come once more.

After seeing the enemies retreat, Sim went to Margaret and said, “Instructor Margaret, what just happened? Where is Zhao Hai?”

Sim had a very good impression of Zhao Hai. The kid had a good temper and wasn’t arrogant.

Margaret let out a long breath before replying, “Zhao Hai is fine. He’s just inside his room adjusting his breath. Are the crew fine?” Sim nodded and said, “They’re alright. However, some of them had yet to come back. They’re the ones Zhao Hai brought with him outside.”

Margaret thought about the skeleton that Zhao Hai had the crew follow. There shouldn’t be any problems on that side.

Margaret nodded and said, “They’re should be fine. Right, where’s Kirk?”

Sim replied, “He should be in his room. I told them to stay in their rooms and don’t come out.” Margaret nodded, then she turned and went towards the rooms.

Zhao Hai was also paying attention to what happened outside. Naturally, since he didn’t really need to settle his breathing, he could spare the effort to look at the scene. Seeing the attackers retreat, Zhao Hai felt relieved. Then he immediately informed the Undead leading the crew to head back. Meanwhile, he walked out of his room, still in his pale appearance.

Just as he came out, he immediately saw Margaret, then he asked, “Instructor, how is the situation below?”

Margaret looked at Zhao Hai, then she quickly replied, “Everything’s fine. The attackers had withdrawn. You can take a rest, there’s no need to worry.” Zhao Hai nodded, “That’s good. I just used too much energy. Meanwhile, I’ll immediately have the Undead lead the crew back.”

Margaret nodded, “I’m heading to Kirk’s room. You can come along.” Zhao Hai nodded, then he followed Margaret to Kirk’s room.

Zhao Hai knew that Margaret was now considering him as someone on her side. This was a welcome development, this meant that he could move more conveniently in the academy.

Kirk’s room wasn’t far from Zhao Hai’s. It didn’t take long before the two arrived outside. After knocking at the door twice, Margaret called out, “Captain Kirk, are you in? It’s Margaret.”

Just as her voice fell, the door immediately opened. Kirk looked at Margaret with pleasant surprise. He couldn’t help but feel glad as he said, “Miss Margaret, you’re back. Good, good. That’s fantastic. Mister Zhao Hai, you’re here as well? Good, this is good news.”

Margaret nodded, “Rest assured, there’s no need to worry anymore. Right, call the others and gather at the dining hall. It’s almost time for lunch, let everyone eat what they want.” Kirk nodded, then he proceeded to call the others.

At this time, a siren was heard. This siren was different than the ones back on Earth; this one was more incisive.

Then suddenly, Sim arrived and then said, “Miss Margaret, the guards are here. Do you want to see them?” Margaret’s expression quickly turned ugly. She just encountered three attacks today, yet the guards didn’t appear even once. And now that the matter had settled, they suddenly appeared. Margaret sneered before she turned and went downstairs.

Zhao Hai didn’t say anything and just followed behind Margaret. He knew that Margaret was about to say unpleasant words. However, he didn’t prevent Margaret from doing so. The Ashley Family isn’t a small influence in the Machine Field. Because of this, they need to have bearing. If they didn’t say anything about how the other party handled this matter, then they might appear weak to others.

Chapter 1110: Meatball Zhu Dachang!!

Just as Margaret and the others arrived at the hall, they suddenly heard a loud and arrogant voice, “Where is your manager? Get him out here! Let’s hear what he has to say.”

When Margaret heard this, her face turned uglier. She quickly walked towards the hall alongside Sim and Zhao Hai.

After arriving at the hall and seeing the guards, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but sigh. Just as he imagined, the leader of the guards was a fat, round-headed man. He was so fat that his neck was practically nonexistent. He had two small beady green eyes. His arms, body, and belly were round. He looked like a mascot for meatballs.

At this time, Sim took a step forward before giving the fat man a salute, “Garrison Officer Sir, what winds blew through you that you actually came to my broken place. You give me too much face.”

The meatball looked at Sim, his eyes actually lit up as he said, “Sim, you old bastard. You have some explaining to do. What just happened?”

Without even waiting for Sim to respond, Margaret interjected and said, “Who are you to ask us for an explanation? It is you who needs to answer to the Ashley Family.”

After hearing Margaret, the meatball man turned to look at her. His beady green eyes blinked before it glared with intensity. He looks like a hungry wolf that just found a defenseless lamb.

The meatball immediately answered, “Is the beautiful lady talking to me? Well, I am the garrison officer of the western district of this mining city. Zhu Dachang!”

“Hahaha”, upon hearing this name, Zhao Hai couldn’t stop himself from bursting with laughter. He looked at the meatball and said, “You’re actually called pig large intestine? Really? Hahaha. What a name!”

Margaret was also about to laugh, but she suppressed it to the point where her face was blushed. Zhu Dachang was speechless, his face turned red, then he said, “My name is Zhu Dachang, not pig large intestine! Kid, you’re courting death!”

Margaret just met the meatball’s threat with a cold snort. Then she said, “I don’t care if your name is Zhu Dachang or pig large intestine. Where were you when we were attacked? And now that those people retreated, you conveniently arrived. Are you surnamed Zhu or are you a real pig? You actually have the gall to ask us for an explanation?”

Zhu Dachang didn’t expect Margaret to be this impolite. He was stunned silly for a moment before he huffed repeatedly as he said, “You’re just an insignificant academy instructor. What gives you the courage to speak to me?” Upon hearing this Zhao Hai couldn’t help but sigh. He was now sure that the Zhang Family had bribed this meatball officer.

Zhao Hai coughed lightly and said, “Garrison officer, sir. Please allow me to interrupt. This is our academy’s Instructor Margaret. She is also the Ashley Family Patriarch’s sixth Miss. People just attempted to assassinate her. Has Sir thought about what would happen if the Ashley Family’s sixth Miss gets killed here? Will the Ashley Family let this matter go? Even if Sir has a backer, do they have the courage to offend the entire Ashley Family?” If he was speaking to a smart person, Zhao Hai might not have uttered these additional words. However, he needed to elaborate further so that Dachang would never miss any detail.

When Zhu Dachang heard Zhao Hai, his originally red face turned pale. Just like Zhao Hai said, he became the garrison officer because his brother-in-law was a Bishop of the Fire Temple. Although a Bishop wasn’t that powerful, he had enough pull to place Dachang in Tyro Planet to be the west district’s garrison officer.

Even if Dachang was as stupid as a pig, he still knew the Darkness Church’s Ashley Family. And they weren’t just a small force in the Machine Field. Although his brother-in-law was a Bishop, even he wouldn’t dare to make war with the Ashley Family.

With this thought in mind, Dachang couldn’t help but wipe a cold sweat. At the same time, he was cursing the person who bribed him. They didn’t tell him Margaret’s true status, they only stated that she was an academy Instructor. Because of this, he didn’t care about the repercussions. With Zhao Hai’s words, however, Dachang couldn’t help but be frightened.

Zhu Dachang wiped his cold sweat, then he turned to Margaret and with a stuttered voice, he said, “I have seen Miss Margaret. Miss Margaret, I truly apologize for not knowing that you’re here. What happened today was truly unfortunate. It happens to be the guard troop’s quarterly exercise. I ask Miss Margaret to forgive me for this mistake.”

Margaret coldly snorted, “Officed Zhu, no matter what happened, I was attacked here. You neglected your duties and that is a crime. So how can we solve this matter? Are you still asking me to compensate for what happened?”

Dachang quickly replied, “I wouldn’t dare. I just followed normal procedure and plan interrogate everyone on the scene. I wouldn’t dare let Miss Margaret suffer a loss. Miss Margaret, rest assured, after I head back, I will immediately find those responsible for today. We will definitely provide you with a satisfactory answer.” Zhao Hai nodded. Although the meatball officer was stupid, he wasn’t stupid enough to reveal anything. Moreover, his response and excuse was actually calculated.

Zhao Hai went to Margaret’s side and whispered, “Instructor, this is not the time to make another enemy.” Then he retreated after saying that.

Margaret pressed her anger down upon hearing Zhao Hai. Then she said ,”Since this is the case, I will not say anything. However, you need to give me an answer. Or else, the Ashley Family will make sure to investigate.”

Zhu Dachang wiped his sweat away and then said, “Yes, Yes. Miss Margaret can rest assured.” Margaret snorted before turning around and leaving. Naturally, Zhao Hai followed closely behind.

Dachang began to relax after Margaret left. As he wiped another batch of sweat, he turned to Sim and said, “Brother Sim, you protected Miss Margaret. For this, I must thank you. If I really allowed Miss Margaret to fall, then I’m truly finished.”

Sim smiled bitterly and said, “Sir Garrison Officer, even I’m unaware of Miss Margaret’s status. I just fulfilled my responsibilities here. Now that I think about it, it was quite scary. If Miss Margaret suffers an accident in my watch, then even my old bones won’t be able to appease the Ashley Family.”

As he wiped his sweat once more, Zhu Dachang said, “In any case, I need to thank you this time, brother. Alright, I need to head back and see which bastards decided to cause us trouble.” Then he ran out. Although he was unsightly, he wasn’t slow. In a blink of an eye, he disappeared into his car and before long, the vehicle was seen speeding out of the hotel.

Seeing Zhu Dachang escape, Sim sneered and muttered, “Thank me huh. Hmph. You think you can escape the Ashley Family’s retaliation? Stupid pig.”

After he said that, Sim left the hall. Before this event, Sim was truly unaware of Margaret’s status. If Zhao Hai didn’t say it, then he would’ve never thought that the common academy Instructor was actually the Ashley Family’s sixth Miss. With such an extraordinary status, an unimportant person like him couldn’t afford offending her.

Margaret quickly arrived at the dining hall. At this time, Kirk and the crew were already inside. After Margaret and Zhao Hai appeared, those who were nervous began to calm down.

At this time, Sim walked over to Margaret and said, “Miss Margaret, this old man is truly unaware of your status. Excuse me if I have ever offended you.”

Margaret shook her head and said, “Mister Sim, you don’t need to apologize. Instead, I need to thank you. If not for your help, the crew might have been in danger.”

As she said that, they suddenly heard footsteps. Margaret and Sim turned to look at the source. The crew that went with Zhao Hai had come back.

The crew were hidden by the skeleton in a small alley for two hours. Although they were afraid, the skeleton remained motionless so they didn’t dare to go out. Then after the skeleton left the alley, they knew that the danger has passed. Therefore, they immediately followed behind it and returned to the reception. Once it was in front of the hotel, the Undead vanished. And after they entered the hotel, they were informed by a robot to head towards the dining hall.

When Zhao Hai saw them enter, he smiled at them and ushered them over to the hall. And upon seeing that Zhao Hai and Margaret were safe, the crew felt relieved. They gave the two their salute before then entered the dining hall.

Seeing that Margaret was about to say something, Zhao Hai gave a nod before taking a seat.

Margaret looked at Zhao Hai and didn’t say anything to him. Although she looked favorably at him, she knew that it wouldn’t be good to be enthusiastic at this time.

After everyone had sat down, Margaret looked at everyone and said. “It has been a very dangerous day. Me and Zhao Hai were attacked outside, and even the hotel was sieged. Fortunately, with the help of Mister Sim, we were able to survive. Also, there’s no need to worry anymore. There are 100 attackers this time, 80 of them were killed by me and Zhao Hai in the mining tunnels. Moreover, the clan’s help would arrive tomorrow.”

Upon hearing Margaret, everyone cheered. However, Sim was actually startled. He had fought with the attackers, so he knew how strong they were. He didn’t expect there to be 100 of them all in all. This was equal to the strength of a small power. But what made Sim surprised even more was Margaret killing 80 of them.

Eighty level 3 to level 4 experts couldn’t be underestimated. Margaret was only a level 4 Mage while Zhao Hai was level 1. Sim was very curious about how the two were able to kill 80 experts.

Margaret waited for the others to calm down before she continued, “It has been a terrifying experience, but I expect that there shouldn’t be any danger from now on. I called everyone to the dining hall today so that we can enjoy a good meal and recover from the shock. Mister Sim, I have to trouble you. If you have anything delicious, please serve it.’

Sim laughed and said, “Today’s outcome is a joyful occasion. This is fate. This old man will take care of it. Everyone, wait for a moment.” Then immediately after he said that, Sim turned around and left.

Margaret turned to the others and said, “Alright, since we still need to wait for the dishes, I’ll have to ask everyone to have a couple of drinks. There’s no need to be polite. Captain Kirk, Zhao Hai, Mister Ken, Mister, Jing, please sit with me. I have something to say.”

Zhao Hai, Kirk, as well as the first and second mate sat at the table Margaret was gesturing towards. After everyone had sat down, Margaret said, “Today’s matter was too dangerous. I need to thank Mister Zhao Hai. If you weren’t here, then we might have suffered an accident.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Instructor is too polite. I’m now a member of the Ashley Family. Naturally, I will do my best to help. Also, if I don’t make a move on those people, then I would be the one who will perish.”

Margaret shook her head and said, “Even if you say that, I still need to thank you. If you weren’t here, then people would have died. You can rest assured, after you return to the academy, you will definitely be given the best grades. And once you enter the Bone Symbol Camp, you will be given the best treatment.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Then I’ll have to thank you, Instructor Margaret.”

Margaret nodded and said, “Zhao Hai, how long do you think you can get out of the academy? You should be getting more familiar with the density here, am I correct? It shouldn’t be long before you fully adapt.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Right. Just like Instructor said, I’m beginning to adjust to the Machine Field’s density. I should be finished in a couple of months.”

After hearing that, Margaret gave a nod and said, “When we return to the academy, I’ll be giving you some materials to read through. These are about the Bone Symbol Camp. I hope you can understand what it means to be in the camp.”

Just after she said that, robots arrived at the hall and began serving food. The atmosphere inside the dining hall immediately turned lively.

Chapter 1111: Killer Fatty Desbarres

Zhao Hai was currently sat inside the Space, looking at spaceships. The Ashley family sent 10 ships altogether.

Upon seeing these ships, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but recall what happened yesterday. They drank too much, he didn’t even know how he got to his room.

He drank a lot yesterday. The crew were drinking alcohol like maniacs. This might be because they had just escaped possible death. Each one of them offered Zhao Hai a toast. In the end, Zhao Hai lost count of how many glasses he drank.

Zhao Hai didn’t use his abilities to dispel the alcohol. Although it would be easy for him, he wanted to become friends with these people. So he just went along and got drunk.

After Zhao Hai was sent to his room, he was immediately hauled over to the Space by Caier. Then after being filled with spatial water, he sobered up.

Now was the day after the event. The Ashley Family’s reinforcements finally arrived. There were ten ships altogether, each one bigger than the academy ship.

Zhao Hai began to understand the Ashley Family’s strength after seeing these ships. Being able to send ten ships at a moment’s notice meant that the Ashley Family weren’t people that could be underestimated.

Because of the planet’s atmosphere, the ships had to slow down upon its descent. While this was happening, Zhao Hai observed the ships. Printed on their side were emblems depicting a skeleton covered in dark clouds. This seems to be the Ashley Family’s emblem.

After that, Zhao Hai measured the ships using his eyes. The ten ships were 500 meters long, 200 meters wide, and 100 meters high. They were shaped like a shuttle, possibly because they were made for speed.

Zhao Hai also inspected the crew manning the ten ships. There were 100 crewmen on each ship. And besides the crew, there were about 500 Mages and Warriors divided among the ten ships.

These Mages and Warriors spanned from level 1 to level 5. The majority of them were level 1 while the level 5’s numbered only ten. This manpower was already astonishing.

Leading this group was a fat man. Although he was thinner than Zhu Dachan, he was still larger than average people. He wore Mage robes and had a ferocious face. It made one think that he was a butcher.

Zhao Hai knew who this person was, he was the Bone Symbol Camp’s lord. Zhao Hai saw him in the pictures. However, when he saw the images, he couldn’t imagine how a ferocious looking man was leading the camp with the least amount of deaths. His actions were truly the reverse of his appearance.

Actually, Zhao Hai’s impression of this fatty was very good. Not only did he publicly state that the Bone Symbol Camp would eliminate brutal eliminations, he also stuck to his decision. This alone was a good reason for Zhao Hai to look at him in a favorable light.

Moreover, from the information found online, this fatty wasn’t only the Bone Symbol Camp’s Lord, he was also the Ashley Family’s External Hall Manager. It can be said that he had a high position in the family. Because of this status, nobody dared to make a move on the Bone Symbol Camp despite its declining status.

Besides being the manager of the External Hall, he also had another identity. He was a loyal servant to the Ashley Family’s current Patriarch, gaining the Patriarchs deep trust.

However, one shouldn’t discount him just because he was a kind Camp Lord that eliminated brutal elimination methods. In fact, it was well-known to Ashley Family’s enemies that he was actually a fierce butcher.

Killer Fatty Desbarres was a very famous character in the Machine Field, famed for being vicious and merciless to his enemies. His character seemed contradictory, but he was actually quite similar to Zhao Hai. He would be caring to his own side while merciless towards his enemies.

It was also because of this that the Ashley Family’s Patriarch was relieved having Margaret join the Bone Symbol Camp. The Patriarch believed that Desbarres wouldn’t place Margaret in any danger.

Naturally, all of these were connected together by Zhao Hai. It was impossible to see everything just by searching online. However, his assumptions shouldn’t be far from the truth.

This time, Desbarres actually came here in person. This meant that the Ashley Family was attaching great importance to this event. Seeing that the ships were about to break through the atmosphere, Zhao Hai closed the monitor and prepared to head out.

Just as he returned to his room, Zhao Hai immediately heard a knock. Zhao Hai quickly opened the door and saw Kirk on the other side. Upon seeing Zhao Hai, Kirk immediately said, “Little Hai, come with me quick. The reinforcements that the Young Lady asked for has arrived. Moreover, it is personally headed by the Camp Lord.”

Zhao Hai pretended to be shocked. Then he quickly nodded and followed behind Kirk. Before long, they arrived at the entrance hall. Margaret was waiting for them there along with Sim.

Seeing Zhao Hai arrive, Margaret nodded and said, “Zhao Hai, you’ll come with us to greet the Camp Lord.” Zhao Hai nodded. After that, Margaret and Sim went out of the hotel first, Kirk and Zhao Hai followed closely behind.

While the group’s car was approaching the spaceport, they could already hear the faint sound of spaceships. As they got out, they saw several huge ships coming down.

Once the ships stopped, a cabin door opened on one of them. Then a big and fat figure came out and walked towards Margaret, this was Killer Fatty Desbarres.

After seeing Margaret, Desbarres said, “Young Miss, are you alright? You scared me to death!” Then he inspected Margaret, afraid that she might be missing a part of her body or something.

Margaret smiled faintly and said, “Uncle, there’s no need to worry. I’m fine.”

At this time, Sim stepped forward and offered his greetings, “Sim Pujian has seen Manager Desbarres.”

Zhao Hai and Kirk also stepped forward and gave their salutes. Desbarred only gave Sim a nod before he turned to Zhao Hai and Kirk. Kirk also only received a nod from the Camp Lord. Meanwhile, Zhao Hai was being carefully sized up.

After Zhao Hai gave his salute, he proceeded to stand still. And although Desbarres was sizing him up, his expression didn’t move, he kept calm.

Some time passed, Desbarres suddenly laughed and said, “Good, good. Zhao Hai, I already heard about you. You’re a good lad. Right, let’s head back first before talking.” After he said that, he patted Zhao Hai’s shoulder.

Zhao Hai gave a short bow and said, “Thanks for the praise, Manager Desbarres.”

Desbarres waved his hand, causing the group to enter the vehicles and proceed towards the hotel. It was impossible for Zhao Hai and Kirk to ride with Desbarres. Because of this, they rode another car along with Sim.

After boarding the vehicle, Kirk looked at Zhao Hai and smiled, “Now that the lord has praised you, you’re future in the camp will certainly be bright. And with the Young MIss’ support, you will certainly become an important member of the camp. When that time comes, I’ll have to rely on you.”

Zhao Hai forced a smile and said, “I haven’t entered the camp yet. Moreover, there are still more exams I need to go through. Let’s talk about that when it happens.”

Kirk actually laughed, “You don’t have to take them all. With your current strength, you are already qualified to enter the camp. And with just a few words from the Camp Lord, you can be exempted from those exams. Just like what the Young Miss said, as long as you adapt to the Machine Field’s normal density of spiritual qi, you will immediately be summoned to the camp.”

They didn’t hide their conversation from Sim. After all, this wasn’t a secret. While they were talking, the car continued to speed towards the reception. Before long, they already arrived.

The group entered the entrance hall. Sim tactfully asked to be excused. Zhao Hai and Kirk also asked to be excused, but Margaret stopped Zhao Hai. Kirk was able to return.

After the three had taken a seat, Desbarres looked at Margaret and said, “Young Miss, what happened? Tell me everything.”

Margaret nodded, then she told everything from beginning to end. She described the end of the exam, the attack in outer space, up to the attack on the hotel as well as the pirates’ retreat.

Desbarres listened carefully. And once Margaret was finished, he let out a long breath and said, “That was close. You’re lucky that Zhao Hai is here. If not for him, you might have been in serious danger.”

Zhao Hai just smiled faintly and didn’t say anything. Desbarres turned to Margaret and said, “Young Miss, you can rest assured, I will make sure to investigate this matter thoroughly. No matter who it is, I will definitely bleed them dry.”

Margaret hesitate for a moment. She didn’t say that Zhao Hai managed to interrogate the attackers. Now that she heard Desbarres, she couldn’t help but think whether to tell him or not.

Desbarres was a man who had seen a lot. So after seeing Margaret’s expression, he knew that there were still things that had not been said. So he immediately asked, “Young Miss, do you know anything? Tell me.”

After hesitating, Margaret finally opened her mouth and said, “After the attackers in the mining tunnel were killed, Zhao Hai turned them into Undead. Then from the Undead’s mouth, we were able to discover that they’re from the Fire Temple’s Zhang Family.”

As soon as he heard Margaret, Desbarres couldn’t help but stare. Then he said, “Fire Temple’s Zhang Family? How is that possible?”

Then he turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Zhao Hai, are you really sure that they’re from the Zhang Family?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “I am. They told me that they’re people from the Zhang Family. The Undead can’t lie, so the information should be correct. Moreover, we killed 80 people this time. It shouldn’t be that hard to find some clues as to who sent those fellows.”

Desbarres nodded. He agreed with Zhao Hai’s idea. It was impossible to hide any traces of 80 people disappearing. As long as they looked, they would certainly find clues. With this thought in mind, Desbarres sneered and said, “Zhang Family, so it is the Zhang Family. Good, they’re quite ambitious.”

Then Desbarres turned to Margaret and said, “Young Miss, prepare to head back. The Old Master has placed great attention on this matter. It would be better if you see him as soon as possible.”

Chapter 1112: Treatment

Zhao Hai was currently sitting inside his room in the spaceship. This room was bigger than the one he had at the academy ship. Altogether, the room was 50 square meters. It was divided into the living room and the bedroom. The entire layout was the same as those seen on ordinary accommodations.

This room was inside The Dry Bone, Desbarres’ flagship. Zhao Hai was taken by Margaret to this ship while Kirk returned to his own.

Zhao Hao was only able to embark on the Dry Bone because of Margaret. After Desbarres saw Margaret, he didn’t delay for a moment and immediately had Margaret pack up to leave. But before they left, Margaret said that she wanted Zhao Hai to go with her to the Dry Bone. Otherwise, Zhao Hai would have been inside Kirk’s ship.

After Zhao Hai entered his room, he didn’t immediately enter the Space. Instead, he took his anti-surveillance device out to examine the room. Upon seeing that it wasn’t being monitored, he felt relieved.

However, he still didn’t enter the Space. There were a lot of powerful Mages inside the Dry Bone. These Mages would certainly pay attention to his room. If they managed to sweep his room with their spiritual force and found that he wasn’t inside, then he would be in trouble. Because of this, instead of entering the Space, Zhao Hai stayed inside his room and condensed Magic Formations.

At this point, Zhao Hai had no idea how many magic formations he had condensed. He now had very good control over his spiritual force, allowing him to condense a hundred formations at the same time. Such speed was quicker than before.

While he was condensing formations, Zhao Hai was also opening his computer. Actually, this action was merely a decoy. What was shown in his screen was the display from the Space’s monitor. Seen on it was Killer Fatty Desbarres’ room.

Desbarres wasn’t in his room at first, but instead he was giving instructions to the ship’s crew. But after the fleet departed, he returned to his room. Not long after Desbarres returned to his room, a knock was heard.

Desbarres stared, then he said, “Who is it?”

Margaret’s voice replied, “Uncle, it’s me.”

When he heard that it was Margaret, Desbarres immediately opened the door and asked her to come in. After Margaret had sat down, Desbarres had his robot pour her some tea before asking, “Young Miss, why did you come here? Do you have something to say?”

Margaret nodded and said, “Uncle, I’m here to tell you something about Zhao Hai.” Desbarres wasn’t the only one listening to her, Zhao Hai was also eavesdropping.

Desbarres looked at Margaret and said, “Young Miss, is something wrong with Zhao Hai? When I heard that you killed 80 experts back in Tyro Planet, I began to feel that something is not right. Is this related to him?”

Margaret nodded, then she said, “Actually, fighting in the tunnel was his idea. Moreover, I offered no help in killing the 80 Mages and Warriors. All of them were killed by Zhao Hai.” As soon as Desbarres heard this, he couldn’t help but be shocked. He knew that Zhao Hai was a level 1 Mage. How could a level 1 Mage deal with 80 level 2 to level 4 experts? How was that possible?

Margaret looked at Desbarres and said, “Zhao Hai is a Mage that specialize in Dark Magic Summoning. While in the lower realms, he was able to create ten thousand Undead. More importantly, these Undead all had the strength of rank 9 Apprentices. It was because of these 10 thousand Undead that he managed to kill all those Mages and Warriors. Then he turned all of them into Undead.”

As soon as he heard Margaret, Desbarres’ eyebrows couldn’t help but wrinkle, he said, “Young Miss, you mean Zhao Hai made those Undead in the lower realm? He killed more than ten thousand people?” Margaret nodded and said, “Last time, I asked him and he seems to recognize it. Not only did he confirm this, he also said that he has a secret method to refine Undead and turn them into these rank 9 Apprentices. In other words, he should have made much more than ten thousand undead.”

Desbarres smiled faintly and said, “I didn’t expect a young man of his age to be vicious. Hehe. Interesting. If he can hand over the method to refine the Undead, then it would be a great boost for the Ashley Family.”

Margaret saw Desbarres’ reaction and couldn’t help but angrily retort, “Uncle, do you understand what I’m saying? Zhao Hai could have possibly killed more than 1 million people in the lower realm. He’s a dangerous character. Is a person like him appropriate for the Bone Symbol Camp?”

When he heard Margaret, Desbarres laughed and said, “Young Miss, you’re thinking into this too much. Which ascender doesn’t have their hands stained with blood? Moreover, ascenders of that age are rare. Being able to ascend at a young age meant that they have a huge background. Even if someone has great talent, as long as they don’t experience bloodshed, then they wouldn’t be able to have the mindset required for ascension. Zhao Hai’s formidable strength and talent, along with his vicious and merciless nature, is what makes him a worthwhile person to nurture. Also, killing a lot of people don’t generally mean that they aren’t good people. And even if he is a dragon, the Ashley Family is a den of dragons itself. The Young Miss doesn’t need to worry.”

Margaret knit his brows, but in the end she nodded. Although he didn’t dabble too much on family matters, she was still aware of the Family’s strength. Not to mention Zhao Hai’s ten thousand rank 9 Apprentice Undead, even if he has a hundred thousand, the Ashley Family still wouldn’t be afraid of him. If you want to rear a dragon, then you need to have the skills to kill one. And the Ashely Family wasn’t afraid to kill a dragon!

Desbarres saw Margaret nod and then said, “From what I can see, there’s no point for Zhao Hai to return to the academy. How about we send him directly to the Bone Symbol Camp and have him adjust to the density of spiritual qi there. After he adapts to the density, we can immediately give him something to do.”

Margaret paused, then she frowned and said, “Uncle, isn’t this too soon? Moreover, is it really appropriate to take him away from the academy?”

Desbarres smiled faintly and said, “Young Miss, special people need special means for training. And since Zhao Hai is a unique person, there’s no need to train him using normal methods. There’s no need to worry about this. Right, Young Miss, accompany me to visit Zhao Hai. I want to see if he is willing to hand over the method to refine undead creatures. It would be a huge help for the family if we can get our hands on it.”

Margaret frowned for a moment before nodding. Although she didn’t have that good of a relationship with his father, she was still a member of the Ashley Family. Naturally, she needed to consider the family’s benefit.

After listening to their conversation and seeing that they were coming over, Zhao Hai proceeded to close the computer.

If he hadn’t been to the Underworld, then he wouldn’t have a method to refine high-ranked Undead. But after he entered the Underworld, with notes from the Lich as well as the rare herbs found there, Zhao Hai was able to summarize a method of refining ordinary Undead into high-ranked ones. Moreover, after some experimentation, the method succeeded. Although it wasn’t as fast as just sending the Undead to the Space, it was still a proven method. Moreover, with this, he could conceal the existence of the Space.

Not long after Zhao Hai closed the monitor, he heard a knock on his door. Zhao Hai didn’t ask who it was and just opened it.

Seeing that it was Desbarres and Margaret outside, Zhao Hai pretended to be startled. Then he invited them in and poured them a cup of tea.

Desbarres looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Alright, Zhao Hai, don’t be so busy. Take a seat. I have something to ask you.”

Zhao Hai pretended to be curious, so he sat down and asked, “Camp Lord, I’ll do my best to answer.”

Desbarres smiled and said, “I heard from the Young Miss that when you were attacked, you released a large amount of Undead. Moreover, these Undead were high-ranked ones. Is this correct?”

Zhao Hai acted frowning as he nodded and said, “That’s correct. In the lower realm, I was able to come by a method to refine ordinary Undead. That is why I have a lot of powerful minions.”

Desbarres nodded and said, “Is it possible for the Ashley Family to buy this method from you? If you decide to sell it to us, then the family would make sure that you won’t suffer a loss.”

Naturally, Zhao Hai couldn’t just immediately agree. Such action would make Desbarres suspicious. Instead, he made an awkward expression before forcing a smile and saying, “Camp Lord, it isn’t that I don’t want to hand over the method. But I’m afraid that you won’t be able to use it.”

When he heard Zhao Hai, Desbarres frowned. Then he asked, “Why wouldn’t I be able to use it?”

Zhao Hai smiled bitterly, then he waved his hand, taking sheepskin scrolls out. Then he placed them on the table and said, “Camp Lord, please take a look.” Desbarres took the scroll and read it carefully. He discovered that the scrolls had existed for a very long time. It seems like Zhao Hai was able to preserve it well that the prints were still visible.

The more he read, the more Desbarres was surprised. Then in the end he was shocked. Then he turned to Zhao Hai and asked, “Zhao Hai, where did you get this method?”

Zhao Hai forced a smile and said, “Back in the lower realms, I was being chased down. In the end I can only enter a forbidden region. There were a lot of Undead in this place and nobody dared to enter it. When I entered the region, I saw a very old Mage Tower. It was also inside that tower that I managed to get the herbs written on that method. Additionally, there’s a very strong density of dark energy present there. Therefore, I was able to succeed in making those powerful Undead. However, after I managed to escape that place, no matter where I went looking, I wasn’t able to see those herbs anymore. I also checked online after coming to the Machine Field and still wasn’t able to find those herbs. So even if I handed the method over, I’m afraid the Camp Lord would find it useless.”

Chapter 1113: Giving A Gift

When Desbarres heard Zhao Hai, he couldn’t help but laugh and said, “Kid, you’re really careful huh. You actually looked them up on the internet. However, you can rest assured. After you become a member of the Bone Symbol Camp, you will know that this isn’t a problem. Even if you cannot look up those herbs online, this doesn’t mean that the Bone Symbol Camp had no way of procuring them. If you give this method to us, you can skip the academy and directly join the camp. Moreover, I will give you the best allowance as well as ten million machine coins, a good house, car, and everything you will need to live your life here. If you don’t want robots to serve you, I can also give you two maids. What do you think?”

When Margaret heard Desbarres, she couldn’t help but feel anxious. She was afraid that Zhao Hai would really want female maids. She didn’t know why, but she felt uncomfortable hearing that Desbarres would provide Zhao Hai maids.

Upon hearing Desbarres, Zhao Hai was shocked. Then realization dawned on him. The sheepskin scroll did indeed record plants in the Underworld. However, he was in the World of Cultivation where treasures are abundant. It wouldn’t be impossible to collect the herbs written on the scroll.

However, Zhao Hai didn’t regret his decision. Firstly, the method on the scroll was already proven to work. And second, this method was completely useless to him. Using this method in order to gain benefits was a very good decision.

With this thought in mind, Zhao Hai immediately replied, “Since the Camp Lord says so, then I will accept your offer. However, I don’t want the maids. Having the robots serving me is already enough.”

Desbarres didn’t expect Zhao Hai to accept the offer immediately. Moreover, he didn’t hesitate to accept the reward. This caused Zhao Hai’s image to be elevated in Desbarres’ mind. The fat manager laughed happily and said, “Alright kid, since this is the case, there’s no need for you to return to the academy. You can go to the Bone Symbol Camp immediately and receive your payment. Remember this, kid, you’re now a member of the Bone Symbol Camp.”

Zhao Hai nodded. Desbarres proceeded to stand up and leave. Margaret also stood up. She gave Zhao Hai a look before following Desbarres.

Zhao Hai suddenly opened his mouth and said, “Instructor, wait a moment.”

Margaret stared. Desbarres stopped as well. Zhao Hai looked at Margaret and said, “Instructor, will you be going back to the academy? If you will, can you please take the magic staff I bought for Dins and the others with you?”

When Margaret heard that it was about this matter, she immediately nodded and said, “Alright, since I will be returning to the academy, I’ll hand them over to Dins and the others.”

Zhao Hai nodded and then waved his hand, taking the magic staffs out and handing them over to Margaret. Seeing Zhao Hai take out staff after staff, Desbarres couldn’t help but feel amazed as he said, “Kid, are you a wealthy lord or something? What other things did you take with you from the lower realm? Come on, let me see them.”

Zhao Hai wasn’t offended by Desbarres’ words. Instead, he couldn’t help but smile. Although Desbarres was quite rude, this also meant that he already had a certain trust towards Zhao Hai. Also, even if Desbarres wanted to make a move on Zhao Hai, he couldn’t since Margaret was here.

When she heard Desbarres, Margaret couldn’t help but frown and said, “Uncle, how can you be like this?”

Desbarres laughed out loud. After some time Zhao Hai laughed as well and said, “Camp Lord, now that you say it, I have some things I want to give you. I hope you won’t dislike them.”

Desbarres was just joking around. He was a famed character in the Machine Field, he had seen too many good things. So how could he covet things from a young ascender? He was merely teasing Zhao Hai. But after hearing the young man, Desbarres gawked. He couldn’t help but turn his head to Zhao Hai and saying, “Really? Good, good. Take them out and let me see.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly, then he waved his hand and took out two bottles of liquor. Then he handed them over to Desbarres, saying, “Camp Lord, these are liquor I brought from the lower realms. I saved them for a good occasion, so please have a taste.”

Desbarres expected Zhao Hai to give him money or treasures. He didn’t think Zhao Hai would give him two bottles of liquor. This caused him to look at Zhao Hai in a more favorable light. If Zhao Hai had given him money or some precious treasure, then that would make him too vulgar. With these two bottles of liquor, Desbarres’ appraisal of Zhao Hai became higher.

Desbarres laughed and said, “Alright, then I’ll accept them. Right, join me for a meal. Let’s drink this wine together.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “I wouldn’t dare disobey your order!” Desbarres laughed as he patted Zhao Hai’s shoulder. After that, he turned around and left. Margaret also gave Zhao Hai a nod before leaving.

When Zhao Hai saw the two leaving, he couldn’t help but smile. His experience in gaining favor was quite lacking. However, he had help. He asked Laura to help him out. Laura was a skilled businesswoman, a profession where gaining favor was essential. What to send and who to send to needed to be carefully considered. Laura was also very skilled in this aspect.

Zhao Hai went according to what Laura said and gave Desbarres two bottles of liquor. Seeing Desbarres laugh, Zhao Hai was very glad. Having Laura and the others was truly a blessing to him.

Zhao Hai didn’t go to the Space and just stayed in his own room, condensing magic formations. He was taking less and less time to explore lately. He looked like a cultivating madman. However, such actions only made Desbarres and the others relieved.

This isn’t to say that Zhao Hai was doing this for the Ashley Family. This was Zhao Hai’s nature. He didn’t like to attract too much attention, especially when his strength was still lacking. Otherwise, he would only attract unwanted trouble.

There were just too many magic formations in the Machine Field. Moreover, these magic formations weren’t just limited to ones in the Machine Field. The Cultivation Realm also shared some similar formations with Magic Theory. Because of this, even if Zhao Hai was condensing formations every day, he still didn’t know when he would be done.

However, his current accomplishments still made Zhao Hai happy. The magic formation sets in his mind were increasing. At this point, 100-layer formation sets that Zhao Hai could use had numbered over a thousand. The other formation sets were even more numerous. If one was a normal Mage, then even if they had these formation sets, they still wouldn’t be able to use them. It was impossible for any other Mage to learn all-element formation sets. They could only use formations that belonged to the elements that they were proficient in. It was just like how a warrior couldn’t master all of the techniques in the world. He could only learn those techniques that were compatible with him.

In the Machine Field, the level of a Mage didn’t rely on how many formations they mastered. Instead, levels were determined by how many layers a Mage could support. Even if you condensed a 5 or 10-layered formation, you would still be a level 2 Mage. And even if you grasped a 50 layer formation, you were still a level 3 Mage.

However, Zhao Hai’s situation was different. He can use the Space to cast these formations. And this wasn’t his only advantage. His advantage in fighting against an enemy was also very huge. He could use the most appropriate formation set during a fight. This would allow him to always gain momentum in every encounter.

Although Mage fights looked different than Warrior fights, they were essentially the same. The only thing that differed between the two were their styles. An example of this would be a straight palm attack. One could choose to defend against it or just counter-attack. Mages were also the same. If the enemy used an ice cone to attack, one could choose to use a shield to block or instead send a spell to counter-attack. All of these decisions relied on a person’s mindset. It was also impossible for a person to be fully calm during these encounters. In this case, experience would play a huge part.

But things were different for Zhao Hai. The Space could calculate the most advantageous way to fight. This would allow him to use the most appropriate method to attack. This would also allow Zhao Hai to be in the upper hand in most fights he would be in.

This didn’t mean that Zhao Hai was under the Space’s control. The Space was just used as a tool. The Space just provided Zhao Hai with these techniques. To Zhao Hai, the Space was a tool, the most convenient tool there was.

Zhao Hai practiced up until mealtime. He didn’t go out of his room at all. At this moment, someone knocked on his door. Zhao Hai opened the door and saw a robot on the other side. This robot looks like a Daoist. It’s body was covered with biochemical skin. However, it was bald. It also had a serial number on its forehead, informing people that it was a robot.

The robot bowed to Zhao Hai and said, “Mister Zhao Hai, the Camp Lord asks for your presence in the restaurant.” Zhao Hai nodded and followed the robot to the restaurant.

The Dry Bone was a medium-sized ship. There were more than 100 people on board. With the addition of Mages, there were only about 200 people inside. Besides the compartments meant for cabins, weapons and ammunition, there was still ample space inside the ship. Because of this, there were things like restaurants, bars, entertainment areas, and other recreational areas inside the ship.

One must know that ships were usually travelling for very long distances. Travelling in Space for several months was a very common occurrence. Therefore, the crew needed places for entertainment. Otherwise, people would burn out from the stress.

The ship’s restaurant wasn’t well-decorated. It was only a white room without any side halls. It can be described as a huge cafeteria.

Although it was already time for eating, there were only a few people inside. Most of the crew were still working, they didn’t have the time to spend at the restaurant.

When Zhao Hai entered the restaurant with the robot, Desbarres immediately saw him. He waved to Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, here!’ Zhao Hai proceeded to go over along with the robot.

The table was quite huge, enough for ten people to sit beside it. At this time, nine of them were occupied. The only free spot was beside Desbarres.

Also sitting on Desbarres side was Margaret. She was left of Desbarres while Zhao Hai was supposed to be on the right.

Zhao Hai didn’t become too polite as he quickly approached and gave a salute, “I have seen the Camp Lord.”

Desbarres laughed and said, “Alright, don’t be overly polite. Take a seat. These people are from my Bone Symbol Camp. Later on, all of you will be working together.”

Zhao Hai bowed towards the others and said, “Zhao Hai has seen everybody. Please look after me in the future.”

As he gave his bow, Zhao Hai saw that four of the people here were Mages while the other four were Warriors. Although they didn’t carry any weapons, they were full of vigor. One could see that they weren’t weak.

Zhao Hai also saw that the people in front of him were level 5. Whether they be Mages or Warriors, level 5 strength was already considered as an expert in the World of Cultivation.

When they saw Zhao Hai giving them a salute, the others immediately returned the gesture. They knew that Desbarres had a high evaluation of this young man judging by his sitting position. Moreover, they also knew that Zhao Hai was a genius. He was the hope of the Bone Symbol Camp. Therefore, they were being polite to him.

After exchanging greetings, Zhao Hai sat down. Seeing Zhao Hai salute the others, Desbarres was very satisfied. He heard that even if Zhao Hai was a genius, he wasn’t arrogant at all. But it was better to see it firsthand.

Once Zhao Hai had settled down, Desbarres smiled and said, “Our main duty is fetching the Young Miss. We’ve already accomplished our duty. Additionally, Zhao Hai has officially entered the Bone Symbol Camp. This is a cause for celebration. And it just so happens that Little Hai had saved some liquor from the lower realms for me. It seems like we’ll be tasting something new today.” After he said that. Desbarres laughed.

As soon as the others heard him, they couldn’t help but laugh as well. Zhao Hai looked at Desbarres and said, “Camp Lord, actually, I can bring more than those two bottles of wine. Those two bottles aren’t enough for all of us to drink. I’ll take out some more for us. These aren’t as good, but please do have a taste.” After he said that, he took out more bottles of wine. Just by looking at the bottles, one could see that they weren’t as good as the ones given to Desbarres.

Zhao Hai gave Desbarres liquor bottles made with crystal. They looked beautiful. However, the bottles he took out were made out of simple glass.

Chapter 1114: Tell Me The Truth

Desbarres didn’t say anything. Instead, he just enjoyed the event. Moreover, leaders were supposed to receive better gifts compared to others. Even if it was the same gift, it needs to be shown that it was still unique.

Naturally, Desbarres wasn’t excused from this rule. Seeing that the wines Zhao Hai took out were different from what were given to him, Desbarres felt refreshed. He laughed happily and said, “Kid, you seem to have a lot of wine. It seems like you’re quite the drinker in the lower realm. Quick, pour us a cup.”

Zhao Hai complied. He opened the bottle and then poured everyone a glass. Naturally, this wine was made inside the Space. He was able to find out that people in the Machine Field didn’t have much liquor to choose from. What they drank was a version of fruit wine. Although the taste was good, it wasn’t easy to get drunk off of it.

 After Zhao Hai poured everyone a glass of wine, he didn’t make an address or something. Instead, he turned to look at Desbarres. Seeing Zhao Hai’s action, Desbarres’ smile turned wider. He secretly commented about Zhao Hai’s tactfulness. Generally, the first person who would propose a toast at the table would be the head of the family, the person with the highest status. And in this situation, even if this wasn’t a family, Desbarres was still the person who needs to raise the glass first.

Although Margaret technically had a higher status than Desbarres, she was a woman. In this case, the one who should propose a toast should be Desbarres.

Desbarres expected Zhao Hai to give the toast. However, Zhao Hai actually turned to look at him. Naturally, this meant that Zhao Hai was waiting for him to make the toast. This made Desbarres appreciate Zhao Hai even more.

Desbarres took his wine glass, looked at everyone and said, “Our operation this time is mainly to retrieve the Young Miss. However, we’re also here to show those people that our Bone Symbol Camp couldn’t be underestimated. We’re showing them that we aren’t afraid of war. Anyone who dares to step on the Bone Symbol Camp’s dignity will be put to death! I know that everyone has been feeling suffocated in the past few years. However, this isn’t the time for the Bone Symbol Camp to fall. As long as the conditions are ripe, the Bone Symbol Camp shall rise again! The whole realm will know and fear the banner of the Bone Symbol Camp!”

Desbarres knew that the overall strength of the Bone Symbol Camp was very good. However, what it lacked the most was a powerful expert. Most camps would have level 6 or level 7 Experts as deterrent forces. They were far stronger than a thousand ordinary experts. They were like nuclear bombs, but much more feared.

However, the current strongest expert in the camp was Desbarres. His strength was quite powerful, achieving level 6. He also reached the peak of his level by being able to use a thousand-layer formation. However, if he wanted to use his formations, he would need a long time to prepare. He gained his title “Killer Fatty” not because of his strength but because he killed his enemies using calculations and plots.

After Desbarres found out about Zhao Hai’s talent, he immediately regarded him as the camp’s hope. He needed to concentrate the camp’s efforts into cultivating Zhao Hai. This would enable the Bone Symbol Camp to rampage through the Machine Field once more.

Because of this, Desbarres had the confidence to declare the future rise of the Bone Symbol Camp. The people sitting by the table were also old members of the camp. Naturally, they understood what Desbarres meant. Everyone raised their glasses and cheered, “The Bone Banner approaches, the Bone Banner will be seen everywhere!” Desbarres laughed out loud and said, “Good, let’s drink!” Then he consumed the entire glass of wine.

“Drink!” Everyone simultaneously held their glasses and drank the wine in one go. But since they haven’t drank this kind of wine, they weren’t aware of how strong it was. The moment they drank the entire glass, they immediately felt the path from their throat to their stomach burn as though it was on fire.

There were some who couldn’t bear the smell of alcohol, there were also some who immediately coughed repeatedly. Some were even choked to tears. At this time, Desbarres let out a long breath smelling of alcohol and said, “Hah! This is good wine. It’s strong enough for me.”

The Warriors among the group had the same reaction as Desbarres. Upon drinking the wine, they couldn’t help but applaud its strength and fragrance.

They didn’t need Zhao Hai to pour them another glass and just poured a glass on their own. After a while, the atmosphere of the table turned warmer.

But Margaret, who was on the left side, couldn’t help but hold her stomach upon drinking her first glass of wine. Then she stood up and ran away.

The proceeding meal went greatly. Desbarres and others’ capacity for alcohol was evidently better than Kirk and the others. Everyone drank a lot.

However, Zhao Hai didn’t drink a lot. He drank a few cups of spatial water beforehand. And even if he drank some wine, he didn’t consume too much. This way, the outcome with drinking with Desbarres and the others wouldn’t be the same as drinking with Kirk’s group.

Kirk and the others were just ordinary people. So if he drank with them and pass out, they would just treat it as normal.

On the other hand, if he drank too much and passed out while being with Desbarres and the others, then they might think that he was weak. They wouldn’t feel secure with a person who couldn’t handle liquor.

Finally, Desbarres and the others passed out on top of the table. Zhao Hai helped them return to their rooms before he went to his own room. Then he continued to practice.

The next day, when Zhao Hai appeared in the restaurant, everyone he knew and even those who he didn’t know gave him a smile. And as he sat down to eat, Desbarres entered.

One has to recognize that the wine made by the Space was very high quality. Therefore, even if Desbarres and the others passed out from drinking too much, they didn’t suffer from a hangover. Moreover, spatial water was used as the wine was created. Because of this, not only would the drinker not feel a hangover, they would instead feel more refreshed the next day.

Seeing Desbarres enter the restaurant clearly full of energy, everyone inside couldn’t help but gawk. Desbarres noticed that Zhao Hai was about to eat a meal and his two eyes couldn’t help but shine. He laughed and said, “Little Hai, you young people really know how to drink. You actually drank with us until we passed out. Hahaha”

Zhao Hai smiled and gave Desbarres a salute. Desbarres, laughed once more and said, “Come eat with me. That was the greatest drinking session I’ve been in. Your wine is very satisfying.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Camp Lord, if you want, I can hand over the formula so that you can make it yourself. Then we could share it with our brothers. We can also sell it to increase the Bone Symbol Camp’s income.”

As soon as he heard Zhao Hai, Desbarres couldn’t help but pat his shoulder and said, “Good. Little Hai, now that you’re a member of the Bone Symbol camp, you can rest assured. When we start selling this wine, I’ll make sure that you’ll have one-fifth of its profits.”

When he heard Desbarres, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but stare. Then he embarrassingly replied, “Camp Lord, that wouldn’t be good. I only handed over the formula…”

Desbarres waved his hand and said, “Stop right there, you don’t know how much your formula is worth. Rest assured, the Bone Symbol Camp would never treat our members unjustly. You don’t know, but the robots made by that kid Qi Yi have been mass produced by the camp’s factories and sold outside. He also gets one-fifth of the profits. This is the rule of our Bone Symbol Camp.”

Hearing Desbarres, Zhao Hai had no way to decline. So he nodded and said, “Alright, I will accept it. But if our brothers need me to do anything, please tell me so that I can offer some help.”

Desbarres patted Zhao Hai’s shoulder. At this time, a robot came with Desbarres’ meal in hand. Then the two proceeded to silently enjoy their meal.

After having eaten his meal, Zhao Hai was about to return to his room before Desbarres stopped him. Then after going to Zhao Hai’s room, Desbarres looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Zhao Hai, tell me the truth. Can you deal with people with higher levels?”

Zhao Hai thought for a moment and said, “Camp Lord, I think I’ll have no problem dealing with level 4 Experts. This is because in addition to being a level 4 Mage, I’m also a Warrior. I can wield a sword and attack like a Warrior. With my Undead and sword, I should be able to exterminate level 4 Experts.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Desbarres actually stared for a moment. Then he looked at Zhao Hai and said, “You’re a warrior as well? You study battle qi in the lower realms?”

Zhao Hai nodded, “I did. I just chose to ascend in a Mage Continent because I thought that Mages would be more valuable after I ascend. Therefore, I chose to ascend as a Mage.”

When he heard Zhao Hai’s reply, Desbarres laughed and said, “That’s good, fantastic. I can understand your decision. Rest assured, the Bone Symbol Camp will make sure to properly cultivate you. Have you been using formations you found online? The Bone Symbol Camp has secret formations and formation sets that haven’t been released to the public. You will have access to all of those. Moreover, I will make you a weapon suitable for you. We’ll also provide you with everything you need so that you can grow into an expert as soon as possible. This way, the Bone Symbol Camp would rise sooner!”

If someone else said that, Zhao Hai might feel something off. However, since it was Desbarres, Zhao Hai wasn’t offended. This was because Desbarres wasn’t doing it for himself, he was doing it for the Bone Symbol Camp and the Ashley Family.

To be honest, Zhao Hai didn’t have any sense of belonging to the Ashley Family. However, he actually had a favorable impression regarding the Bone Symbol Camp. The one who approached him from the very beginning was Margaret. And up to the present, the Bone Symbol Camp had always gained Zhao Hai’s favor. Zhao Hai liked the Bone Symbol Camp’s people since they weren’t plotting against each other in order to gain benefits. Everyone had the same goal, and that was to make the Bone Symbol Camp rise. Everyone made sacrifices in order to meet this goal. This was what moved Zhao Hai the most.

Chapter 1115: External Hall’s Eight Camps

Zhao Hai has the Space, so he didn’t care about gaining something like authority. Additionally, he has a very good family. There was no reason for him to be sad.

However, humans were group animals. And after ascended to the Machine Field, the Bone Symbol Camp had been really good to him. Although he handed over some benefits, those things weren’t useful to Zhao Hai in the first place. Now, Desbarres was more willing to provide him with benefits, which was good for Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai also knew that huge families would have their own secrets. And these secrets would be very useful to him.

Desbarres saw that Zhao Hai had not spoken, so he couldn’t help but ask, “Little Hai? Is something wrong?”

Zhao Hai stared, then he shook his head and said, “There’s no problem. But Camp Lord, I have to ask for your help. I have two robots back in the Academy. Please help me to transport them to the camp. One of those two robots is made by Qi Yi. I also see Tinkle to be very convenient.”

Desbarres thought that Zhao Hai had some misgivings, so when he heard Zhao Hai, he laughed and said, “This isn’t a problem. That kid Qi Yi might not be good at anything other than tinkering with robots, but he’s really talented. Rest assured, after you adapt to the density of spiritual qi, everything you need will be taken care of.”

Zhao Hai nodded. Seeing Zhao Hai agree, Desbarres said, “Good, then go and take a rest. We’ll be close to the Bone Symbol Camp tomorrow.” Then he stood up and proceeded to leave. Zhao Hai also stood up and escorted him out.

Zhao Hai spent the rest of his day condensing formations in his room. He didn’t expect a simple academy exam to spiral into his present situation. Moreover, he was even able to prematurely enter the Bone Symbol Camp.

Recalling the experience, Zhao Hai wasn’t able to see anything improper. Although he showcased his terrifying ability, his true strength was still hidden. This was very important for him.

And Zhao Hai also needed to do this. When it came to the Machine Field, only when one shows off their strength would they get attention and benefits.

Imagine if Zhao Hai didn’t become a level 1 Mage just one month after ascending. If his strength wasn’t as strong as it is right now, if he was like Dins and the others who were old and had no potential, would Desbarres still be polite to him? Will the Bone Symbol Camp allocate materials so that he could cultivate? Certainly not.

Also, if other camps hear that Zhao Hai had the wine formula as well as the means to refine high-level undead, then they would definitely try and eliminate him. The Machine Field wasn’t a simple place. It was precisely because of this that Zhao Hai was careful in revealing his capabilities. Telling Desbarres that he was both a Mage and a Warrior was on purpose.

Zhao Hai discovered that the real essence of the Machine Field were the secrets of the various powers. However, those secrets could only be passed on to a family’s loyal members. Even those inside the family would find it hard to get access to restricted magic formations and formation sets, not to say ascenders. Therefore, Zhao Hai revealed that he was also a Warrior to Desbarres so that the Camp Lord would place more importance to him. Only then would Zhao Hai gain the qualifications to learn these restricted secrets.

The day quickly passed by. Besides inviting Zhao Hai over for dinner, Desbarres also brought Zhao Hai to the entertainment area to play around for a while.

This entertainment area was for the crew to relax in. There were plenty of fun things to do inside the huge iron hall.

After playing around for a while, Zhao Hai talked to Desbarres and then returned to his room. Regarding Zhao Hai’s actions, Desbarres didn’t say anything. In his mind, Zhao Hai was a person who was infatuated with cultivation. Otherwise, his strength wouldn’t have reached this high in such a short time.

Nothing noteworthy happened that night. The next day was the same as the previous. He had breakfast with Desbarres and was told to prepare his things. They might arrive at the Bone Symbol Camp by evening’s time.

Zhao Hai nodded and returned to his room. Then he investigated the Bone Symbol Camp’s situation. He was able to know the location of the camp’s main base. Zhao Hai also discovered that the ascender academy was quite far from the camp’s base.

The city where the ascender academy was located was called Auspicious Cloud City. This was a city managed by the Ashley Family. About ten thousand li south of the city was a huge remote landmass. This landmass wasn’t any smaller than a continent. Altogether, the island was more than three million square kilometers. This island was the main city of the Ashley Family, named Lofty Demon City.

The entire city occupied the whole island. The island’s name was Lofty Demon Island. Surrounding the big island were eight smaller islands. These eight islands looked like soldiers guarding Lofty Demon Island. Stationed on these islands were the Ashley Family’s eight camps of the External Hall.

The eight camps had names that were themed with bones or ghosts. The Bone Symbol Camp was one of the four camps with bone in their name.

The planet where the Ashley Family was stationed at was called Dark Magic Planet. The entire planet was the Ashley Family’s domain, their supreme headquarters.

There were more than ten thousand cities on this planet, with a population surpassing 10 billion. As for ascension points, there were more than a hundred of them. The area where Auspicious Cloud City was located was under the jurisdiction of the Bone Symbol Camp. The lands surrounding it also belonged to the camp. With the decline of the Bone Symbol Camp, the other camps began to target these lands. However, since these places were under Desbarres, they didn’t dare to be excessive. The least they could do was to poach talents away from the camp.

Although the eight camps of the External Hall were all under the Ashley Family, this didn’t mean that all of them had good relationships with each other. Conversely, the relationship between the eight camps wasn’t too good. This was because of the system of competition that the Ashley Family set up. There would be competitions between the eight camps each year. The financial support of each camp relied on the results of these competitions. Control over ascension points and recruitment also hinged on the competition.

Besides these things, it was also a matter of status. Each year, people on other camps want to be a step above the others. Those below would treat those above as their elder brothers.

The Bone Symbol Camp haven’t been in a good state in recent years. Although they weren’t at the bottom of the competition, they hovered at sixth or seventh place. When they see the other camps, they have to give a salute. Who wouldn’t be embarrassed with this?

The Bone Symbol Camp didn’t lack money. The robots that Qi Yi made already brought huge profits to the camp. Because of this, even if the family hadn’t been giving that much money to the camp, the camp was still quite rich. What the camp needed the most was status.

It can be said that the Ashley Family was a very famous existence in the Machine Field. One family controlling an entire planet was quite rare in the realm.

There were a bit more than 1000 livable planets in the Machine Field. Moreover, these 1000 planets were divided by the three major powers. And in these major powers were smaller powers. If each of these smaller powers wanted a planet of their own, then even 10 thousand planets wouldn’t be enough. Therefore, most planets were controlled by an alliance. Groups like the Ashley Family that controlled an entire planet were rarely seen.

After understanding the strength of the Ashley Family, Zhao Hai knew that they really weren’t simple. Controlling an entire planet despite there being only more than 1000 planets in the realm was a huge accomplishment.

Before long, the fleet arrived at Dark Magic Planet’s outer space base. All in all, the Ashley Family had four outer space bases. These bases were used to protect the planet’s safety. The base they were in had ten large-class ships, more than 100 medium-class spaceships as well as countless small ships.

Although the Dry Bone was a medium-class ship, it was generally used for reconnaissance duty, something that smaller ships would do. Because of this, the Dry Bone was able to enter planets. As for large and other medium ships, they weren’t permitted to enter. This was due to the disturbance that they would cause upon entering the atmosphere. It was very possible for them to cause natural disasters. Generally, only smaller ships could enter a planet.

With Desbarres being the Patriarch’s trusted subordinate, he was able to move ten ships without reporting. Although the Dry Bone was on the smaller side among medium-class ships, even to the point where it can enter a planet and do tasks that only smaller ships would do, it was still a medium-class ship to its core. Its combat power was much stronger than small ships. And since it was made for scouting, its speed was extremely fast. This was the reason why Desbarres used it to fetch Margaret.

But even with the Dry Bone’s properties, it still wasn’t allowed to enter Dark Magic Planet. The only thing they could do was leave the ship on the outer space base and then transfer on smaller ships before entering the planet.

Back when Zhao Hai headed towards Tyro Planet for the exam, he wasn’t able to see these outer space bases. This was because there was no need for them to go to these places. The academy’s ship was a small-class ship. They could use another route to enter and leave the planet. Because of this, Zhao Hai wasn’t able to see these bases.

But this time, they needed to stop on a base in order to transfer ships. Therefore, Zhao Hai was able to look at these outer space bases. Zhao Hai stared at the sight. He didn’t expect these bases to be so enormous. The entire base looked like a floating metropolis. Besides the base itself, it was surrounded by innumerable satellite ports. Ships were seen everywhere, coming in and out of the base.

Chapter 1116: Bone Symbol Camp

When the ship stopped, Desbarres brought Zhao Hai and disembarked. When they went out of the ship, Zhao Hai discovered that they were now walking on an airlocked corridor. People could use this passage to safely get into the base.

After passing through the corridor, they arrived at a platform. This platform was also airlocked. The environment inside it was the same as the spaceship. There were several vehicles stopped at the platform. Desbarres took Margaret and Zhao Hai to ride one of them.

As they sat inside the car, Desbarres turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, we need to quickly head back to the family, so we wouldn’t be able to stay here for long. But next time, I will definitely take you to play around this base.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Camp Lord is too polite. I also want to head back so that I can continue practicing.”

Desbarres smiled and said, “Don’t think about practicing all the time. Your training speed is fast enough. Being able to use five-layer formations in such a short time is already a good accomplishment.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and didn’t say anything. Desbarres didn’t persuade Zhao Hai further either. He had spent most of his life in the Ashley Family and had seen all kinds of people. Cultivating madmen like Zhao Hai were among these people. And as long as they don’t die in the future, they would definitely become famous experts of the realm.

The car quickly flew through the base. And before long, they were already on another port where a smaller ship was waiting for them.

There were a few people standing at the door of the ship. All of them were dressed in their uniforms. The uniforms were in one-piece with the upper and lower body connected together. It seems like they were made out of leather. It had a tight design, looking quite good.

When Desbarres’ group of three got out of the vehicle, the person at the lead immediately said, “We have seen the manager. The ship has been prepared.”

Desbarres nodded. Then he said, “Good, help me express my thanks to your chief. I’m in a hurry and don’t have time to see him.” The man didn’t dare stop Desbarres.

At this time, Desbarres embarked on the ship along with Margaret, Zhao Hai, 30 Mages and 20 Warriors.

This time, Zhao Hai didn’t go to a room inside the ship. It would only take a short time for this small ship to reach the planet’s surface. Therefore, Zhao Hai spent the time inside the command hall along with Desbarres.

Naturally, there was a captain taking command of the ship. So Zhao Hai and the others just stood in the hall and looked through the displays in order to look at the scenery outside.

When the ship entered the atmosphere, Desbarres let out a long breath. Then he turned to look at Zhao Hai and said, “We’ll be sending you to the camp first to get settled down. After that, I will deliver the young miss to the family. I already gave word to the people back in the camp. They will give you a good room that will allow you to adapt to the Machine Field’s spiritual qi. However, don’t adapt to the density too fast, or else you’ll get corrupted. You need to gradually adapt.”

Zhao Hai nodded. On the other hand, the Mages behind them felt their hearts stir. Although Desbarres had been very good to everyone in the Bone Symbol Camp, they had never seen their Camp Lord take care of someone like he did with Zhao Hai.

Desbarres didn’t tell anyone else about Zhao Hai being both a Mage and a Warrior. When Zhao Hai told him this information, Desbarres decided to block it from spreading. In his opinion, being both a Warrior and a Mage was Zhao Hai’s trump card. But what he didn’t know was that Zhao Hai had much more terrifying secrets.

At this time, Zhao Hai saw nine islands arranged in a squarish manner on the ship’s computer. The middle island was much bigger than the eight surrounding it. The surrounding islands looked like it was guarding the middle landmass.

Desbarres pointed at an island and said, “There is Bone Symbol Island where the Bone Symbol Camp is. Currently, the camp has more 4000 Mages and more than 6000 Warriors. The weakest is level 1 while the strongest reached level 5. In addition to the camp itself, there are also two residential areas as well as eight training regions in the island. While you get settled in the island, I will send the Young Miss home. I will certainly come back as soon as possible.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Camp Lord can relax. I don’t have a lot of demands anyway. After I reach the camp, I will immediately practice. I won’t be doing anything else in a short time.”

Desbarres nodded and said, “I already told them to not make any mistakes. Alright, let’s prepare to head down.” The ship had already reached the Bone Symbol Camp’s airspace. It was now slowly descending into the camp.

The Bone Symbol Camp also had their own port. However, it wasn’t very large. Its main use was to accommodate small ships that brought supplies from the outer space base as well as the other islands. Because of this, the port doesn’t need to be too big.

Zhao Hai used this period of time to observe the camp’s headquarters. Although it was called a camp, it was actually a very high building. From his estimation, Zhao Hai reckoned that it was about 200 floors high, exceeding a kilometer tall. Its surface area also reached about ten thousand square meters. The entire building was tower-shaped with glass windows. It actually looked very beautiful.

Zhao Hai didn’t expect the camp to have a very advanced building. It was not what he expected.

At this time, the ship had safely landed on the ground. Desbarres brought Zhao Hai as well as the Mages and Warriors out of the ship.

There were members of the Bone Symbol Camp waiting for them outside. Desbarres looked at Tao Wang who was standing at the front and said, “Tao Wang, Zhao Hai has already joined the camp. Have you arranged his things?”

Tao Wang nodded and said, “Camp Lord, you can rest assured, everything has been prepared.”

It was obvious that Desbarres trusted Tao Wang. So he nodded then turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, go follow Tao Wang while I send the Young Miss home. If you need anything, just ask Tao Wang.”

Zhao Hao nodded and gave Tao Wang a salute. Then Desbarres turned around and re-entered the ship. He would be heading to Lofty Demon Island.

Seeing the ship fly away, Tao Wang turned to look at everyone and said, “Alright, all of you should get going. Little Hai, come with me. I’ll lead you to your place.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Thank you, Big Brother Tao.” Tao Wang smiled and said, “There’s no need to be polite. We’re already camp brothers. Let’s go.” Then after he said that, he led Zhao Hai into the building. The building’s first floor was a very large hall. There were dining rooms and resting areas on the side. But the biggest attraction on this hall was the huge electronic wall, showing all kinds of information.

Tao Wang said to Zhao Hai, “Besides the funds the family gives each year, the camp is pretty much self sufficient. The family would also post tasks for the camps to accomplish. These tasks would be sent through the internal network. We can complete these tasks in order to gain more money. So every year, there would be a lot of people who are idling here to pick tasks. Additionally, we take the funds allocated by the family and distribute them to the members as wages. However, for those who want to practice, this wage is simply not enough. Because of this, the camp needed to create its own wealth.”

Zhao Hao nodded at Tao Wang’s words. Although the Ashley Family supported the camps, this didn’t mean that the family would shoulder all of their expenses. Every year, the money provided by the family was always limited. So each camp needed to think of ways to make money on their own.

Tao Wang continued, “These tasks aren’t only on Dark Magic Planet, there are some that were on other planets. If you want to accomplish this task, then you can only use a ship. And if you want to get there faster, then you will have to use a transmission formation. However, the transmission formation’s fee is higher. If the task is issued by the family, then the costs would be subsidized. Otherwise, we would need to pay for it with our own money.” While he said that, Tao Wang and Zhao Hai went inside an elevator. Then Tao Wang pressed the number for the 180th floor.

After he pressed the button, Tao Wang turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Actually, our camp is similar to the academy. The first floor has the restaurant. There are also places for practicing and other things. The building also has a market where people run their own shops. This is also where people trade for goods. The tasks we do usually don’t just include monetary compensation. Sometimes, people would unearth treasures. You can go to the marketplace and trade them for some money. Naturally, you can contribute these treasures to the family. The family would certainly make sure that you would not be treated unjustly.”

Zhao Hao nodded. He understood that the External Hall’s camps were actually just the family’s exclusive mercenaries. They would receive remuneration in exchange for accomplishing tasks given out by the family.

A huge family’s development not only depended on their experts and powerful ships. They also need to work on other aspects such as their foundation.

The External Hall plays an essential duty for this aspect. Although the people in the External Hall weren’t individually strong, their overall strength wasn’t bad. They were equal to an army. The External Hall was an army that doesn’t need too much money to function. And at the same time, they could also provide the family with benefits.

For example, an External Hall Mage could dig up a valuable ore during their time outside. If they didn’t have any uses for this ore, then they could sell it off to other people. However, this exposes them to the possibility of being robbed and killed. Because of this, their best choice was to sell the ore to the family in exchange for something of equal value. Naturally, they could also keep them for their own use. When they were strong enough in the future, they could use the ore. But before that happens, if someone knew what they had, then they would definitely be in danger.

This ore might very likely be an indispensable piece for a powerful weapon. If the family gets their hands on it, then they could make a weapon that would help the family increase their strength.

With this setup, the family would acquire a lot of good items. And during wars, these manufactured weapons might play a critical role. A weapon’s value was very difficult to estimate, especially in the World of Cultivation. There were some average powers in the World of Cultivation that rose into prominence just because they had an extremely powerful weapon in hand. Ordinary people wouldn’t dare to provoke them. This was akin to a country having their own nuclear arsenal.

It was because of this that the family allowed the camp to post their own tasks for their members. This way, the External Hall’s members would bring them more benefits.

Tao Wang proceeded to introduce Zhao Hai to the camp’s situation. The market was divided into two floors, one on the 100th floor and the other on the 105th floor. The market on the 100th floor was a mall opened by the Ashley Family. This was where potions and goods for Mages and Warriors were sold. Moreover, the prices here were cheaper than the markets outside.

On the other hand, the market on the 105th floor was the trading floor. People from the camp go there to trade. Mages that obtained magic swords would trade it since it was useless for them. Meanwhile, a Warrior that needed items like magic swords would find it on this floor.

When he heard this, Zhao Hai’s eyes shone. He didn’t expect a trading floor to exist here. This will certainly provide him with a lot of items for the Space. At the same time, he could use the Processing Machine to make items that he could trade for.

At this time, the elevator sounded out with a ding. When the elevator doors opened, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but stare. This was because he didn’t expect this floor to look like his. The floor was very tall at about ten meters high. There were also some ornamental trees planted on the ground as well as some grasses. Most importantly, the rooms here didn’t look like the other places. Each accommodation had its own yard, just like a villa. They looked very elegant.

Looking at Zhao Hai’s reaction, Tao Wang smiled and said, “Normally, this place is reserved for people level 4 and above. However, the Camp Lord specifically instructed me to prepare a spot for you. Let’s go, I’ll show you to your house.”

Zhao Hai was somewhat touched. He was no doubt treated specially. Although he hadn’t seen the other floors, he knew that the other rooms weren’t as good as the ones on this floor. Zhao Hai felt that only level 5 experts deserve spots on this floor.

Chapter 1117: A Little Gift

Zhao Hai felt that it was unfair. However, this unfairness wasn’t for him, but for other people in the camp.

He was a newcomer to the camp, and the strength he revealed so far was only level 1. In this case, him living in a villa meant for level 4 experts was unfair to the other people in the camp.

With this thought in mind, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but look at Tao Wang, “Big Brother, this isn’t good. If I live here, what would other people think? I think I should live in the lower floors.”

Tao Wang smiled and said, “Rest assured, those fellows wouldn’t think bad of you. Don’t underestimate those guys. Every one of them are rich. Don’t forget that besides this building, there are also two residential areas in the island. Those who wanted to live in villas would have already bought their own. Also, since the Camp Lord wanted you to live here, nobody would dare say anything.”

Zhao Hai smiled bitterly and said, “Then I’ll have to thank Big Brother Tao. Big Brother, this little brother just ascended from the lower realms. So I don’t have a lot of precious things. The only thing I can gift you are these two bottles of wine. These are the most valuable things I have right now. I also gave the Camp Lord two bottles of this wine. Please have a taste. Also, please have everyone in the camp have a taste of the wine. If they like the flavor, then our Bone Symbol Camp might open our own winery. I’ve also given the formula for this wine to the Camp Lord.”

After he said that, Zhao Hai waved his hand and took two bottles of wine out as well as a spatial bag. Spatial bags weren’t rare in the Machine Field. One could easily buy one as long as they practice at a certain level. Therefore, Zhao Hai wasn’t afraid of taking one out.

Tao Wang understood what Zhao Hai wanted to convey. But regarding Zhao Hai’s respectful manner, he happily received the gift. He received the two bottles as well as the spatial bag and said, “Alright. This Big Brother doesn’t have a lot of hobbies besides drinking. I’ll have a taste of your wine when I head back. I’ll also send these wines to everyone. Don’t worry, I’ll tell them that these came from you.”

Zhao Hai laughed and said, “Big Brother Tao is too polite. Come drink with me later. Right, I also have two other kinds of liquor. Take it back and have a taste.” After that, Zhao Hai took out another two containers and handed them over to Tao Wang.

Tao Wang wasn’t polite and stored the two containers into his own spatial item. Then he smiled and said, “Let’s go and take a look at your house. We’ll have a drink after you get settled.” Then he led Zhao Hai along.

Zhao Hai’s villa wasn’t near the elevator. He was placed in the floor’s best location. This location was beside a window, allowing its occupant to see the scenery outside.

Zhao Hai inspected his place. He didn’t have much requests for his accommodation. As long as it was livable, then it was already good. The whole villa was divided into two floors. The land area of the villa was less than 100 square meters. There was also a small garden outside. The other villas on this floor were constructed the same way.

Tao Wang carefully introduced Zhao Hai to the villa. Although the house was very small, it was fully equipped. It even had a kitchen installed.

The upper floor had three bedrooms while the lower floor had the kitchen, living room, and bathroom.

After showing Zhao Hai the house, Tao Wang said, “Little Hai, although this house is quite small. You can rest assured. The Camp Lord has already prepared a good villa for you. As long as you get used to the Machine Field’s density of spiritual qi, you can immediately move to that villa.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “There’s really no need to bother, this place is already good. Right, Big Brother Tao, can I use the kitchen here instead of going to the cafeteria below?”

Tao Wang smiled and said, “Of course you can. If you don’t want to prepare your own food, I can buy you some robots that can cook for you. You don’t need to worry about payment. The Camp Lord already made sure that you get everything you want.”

Zhao Hai replied, “Brother Tao, I already have robots left them behind in the academy. I’ve already asked the Camp Lord to fetch them for me. Please help me deliver those robots here. As for other requests, my main task here is to adapt to the spiritual qi as soon as possible. As long as I can adapt to the spiritual qi, then everything is fine.”

Tao Wang laughed and said, “This kid. Alright, then I will get you some food for now. You will also get your food delivered regularly. The Camp Lord wants to make sure that you won’t get burdened with pointless stuff.” Then after he said that, he left with a laugh.

Zhao Hai knew that Tao Wang was joking with him. So he just smiled and familiarized himself with the villa. He went to his room and took out the anti-monitoring device. After seeing that there weren’t any surveillance device inside, he felt relieved.

However, he didn’t enter the Space. He knew that Desbarres might come later on. So instead of returning to the Space, he sat down and condensed more formations.

After two hours, the sound of a car was heard outside the villa. Then quickly after that, Tao Wang’s voice was heard, “Little Hai, Little Hai, are you there? Come here quickly.” Zhao Hai went out of his villa and saw Desbarres and Tao Wang outside. Besides the two, nobody else was present.

Zhao Hai quickly opened the door and asked the two to come in. Zhao Hai also discovered that Tao Wang was bringing several bags which seemed to contain things.

Tao Wang wasn’t too polite as he directly went to to the villa’s dining room. Then he put the bags down and took out its contents. What was inside were few meal boxes with food inside.

Looking at Zhao Hai’s dazed expression, Desbarres laughed and said, “Little Hai, since it’s your first day in the camp, I brought Tao Wang here to drink. So how about sharing a few cups with us?”

Zhao Hai replied, “Since the Camp Lord wants someone to drink with, then I will naturally comply. It’s a pity that you brought me food. Otherwise, I would’ve prepared you some food myself.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Tao Wang suddenly smiled. Then he gave Zhao Hai’s spatial bag back to him and said, “Little Hai, I already took the liquor inside and replaced it with food ingredients. If you want to make some food, then you can feel free to do so.”

Desbarres and Tao Wang thought that Zhao Hai was boasting. In their opinion, a cultivating genius like Zhao Hai must have certainly focused his efforts on cultivating. In this case, how could he possibly know how to prepare food?

Zhao Hai didn’t care about what the two thought. The thing in his mind right now was what Tao Wang just said. Then out of curiosity, he took his spatial bag and looked inside. And just like Tao Wang said, there were ingredients inside. There was meat, eggs, vegetables, and other things needed for cooking.

Zhao Hai looked at the ingredients and then looked at the food that Tao Wang and Desbarres brought. There were fried chicken, fries and so on. There weren’t any special food. To be honest, Zhao Hai truly wanted to drink. But he couldn’t enjoy his drink with these foods.

When he drank inside the Space, he would have liquor and food prepared by Meg. At this point, Meg’s cooking was a bit inferior if not on par with a master chef. And since Zhao Hai wanted country cooking, Meg prepared chinese cuisine for him.

And because of this, Zhao Hai had developed a particular taste. At this point, he couldn’t eat common dishes. Therefore, Zhao Hai took out some fish and vegetables and then proceeded to cook.

Seeing Zhao Hai’s skillful actions, Desbarres and Tao Wang couldn’t help but stare. They didn’t expect Zhao Hai to actually know how to cook.

Before long, Zhao Hai completed two dishes. One of them was a cold dish, which was a home-cooked dish of Pu Ai. The other dish was a hot dish which was made with fish. Zhao Hai placed these two dishes on the table amidst Desbarres’ and Tao Wang’s surprise.

It must be said that even if the World of Cultivation was much stronger than Earth, it was still inferior to Earth in terms of cuisine.

In the World of Cultivation, everyone gave full priority to cultivation. Even if they had the same ingredients as back on Earth, they still wouldn’t spend the time to research how to make better dishes. If people from the World of Cultivation had the time to research dishes, they might as well use it to research formations or other things related to getting stronger.

Because of this mindset, the entire World of Cultivation didn’t have any deep understanding of cuisine. What people generally ate were simple dishes.

Home-made dishes like cold dishes didn’t look any special. The hot fish dish, on the other hand, looked like it took a lot of work to prepare. Desbarres and Tao Wang were dumbfounded by the skills they witnessed.

In the past, when Zhao Hai was eating at the academy’s cafeteria, he discovered that the dishes there weren’t much to talk about. And after accessing the internet, he finally knew the level of cuisine here. Therefore, he decided to show off some cooking skills. It must be said that his cooking skill was only inferior to Meg’s.

Desbarres looked at the two dishes and said, “Little Hai, did you just cook these two dishes? Where did you learn to cook?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “I studied it back home. Have a taste.”

Tao Wang took some chopsticks and proceeded to eat.

Chapter 1118: Level Up, Stellar Body Tempering Technique!

The people in the Bone Symbol Camp were aware that a new member had joined them. And that this new member was assigned a villa in the place where level 4 Experts live in. Although there was no point for them to go to the floor where the villas were, some of them still read about the floor. And when they heard the news, they couldn’t help but feel uncomfortable.

Moreover, this new member seems to be a mystery. In addition to the time where he asked Tao Wang to give the members some wine, this person never appeared in the camp. It has been two months since then. And the number of people who had seen this new member could be counted on one hand.

It was also found out that in addition to not exploring the camp, this person doesn’t leave his room most of the time. He would stay inside his villa every day. Besides his two robots as well as Tao Wang and the Camp Lord, nobody had ever gone to his villa. Also, Tao Wang and the Camp Lord were often seen visiting his villa once or twice a week. In the past two months, the two had visited the villa twenty times.

Also, every time Tao Wang and the Camp Lord left the villa, both of them would be red-faced, obviously drunk. This made the members of the camp even more curious about the person in the villa.

What the people in the camp didn’t know was that Tao Wang and Desbarres didn’t only visit Zhao Hai to drink. They were also monitoring how Zhao Hai was adapting to the spiritual qi.

Seeing the rate of Zhao Hai’s adaptation, Desbarres and Tao Wang were ecstatic. Others would take one year before adjusting to the density of spiritual qi, but Zhao Hai only took one month.

However, Tao Wang and Desbarres were clueless about something else. Besides adapting to the Machine Field’s density of spiritual qi, Zhao Hai’s strength had also experienced a breakthrough.

Zhao Hai had already adapted to the spiritual qi density a month after entering the Bone Symbol Camp. Moreover, he felt that he was going to break through. Because of this, he looked for a chance to go out of the camp and look for a desolate place. Then he arranged a spirit gathering formation and attempted to break through. The Myriad Stellar Transformations Yin-Yang Art’s piritual qi requirement for breaking through from the first layer to the second layer was simply terrifying.

After breaking through to the second layer, Zhao Hai’s spiritual force underwent a huge enhancement. Originally, the most he was able to use were hundred-layer formation sets. But after this breakthrough, he was now able to use one thousand-layer formations. This made him equivalent to a level 6 Mage.

This breakthrough didn’t only improve Zhao Hai’s strength. The second layer of the Stellar Transformations Art gave him a technique. The technique was a set of fist martial arts with an unusual name, Stellar Body Tempering Technique!

The fist technique with a peculiar name made Zhao Hai very curious. In the beginning, he thought that this set of fist techniques wouldn’t have any use to him. After all, he had additional abilities that made his body beyond what most people had. His crystal body as well as his ability to become liquid metal was already very good. He thinks that this set of techniques was a bit weak!

But after he carefully looked through the Stellar Body Tempering Technique, he began to take it seriously. The contents of the book was too formidable!

The technique would let the user absorb the strength of the stars into their body. And this absorption didn’t mean on the meridians or the skeleton. This was actually tempering on a cellular level.

According to the Stellar Body Tempering Technique, every human cell was a place to store energy. They were dependent and independent of each other in certain aspects. The Stellar Body Tempering Technique leads the power of the stars into a person’s body, making it more sturdy and allowing it to store energy. As long as one can persist on practicing, eventually, each cell of a person would attain the power of a star. When that time comes, they would truthfully be unparalleled under the heavens.

This technique was unprecedented. It was like those heaven defying methods from the novels Zhao Hai read before. If it wasn’t in his hands right now, then Zhao Hai might think that this method was too perfect to exist.

However, after seeing this technique, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but hesitate. Did a perfect technique really drop into his hands out of thin air? It doesn’t look like it.

By the end of the technique, its weakness was pointed out. And just like any body tempering technique, its disadvantage was the pain!

This body tempering technique requires one to use their own spiritual force to move the power of the stars and introduce it to their body. The power of the stars doesn’t temper the flesh, the blood, nor the bones, but a person’s cells, every cell in the body!

When practicing the Stellar Body Tempering Technique, one needed the ability to separate their consciousness and body. Otherwise, they would be in danger!

This separation between consciousness and body meant that one’s spirit was separated from their physical body. It was similar to a soul leaving the body, but not exactly the same. When one’s soul left their body, their body couldn’t move. However, the separation of consciousness and the body only meant that one’s mental intent was outside the body. In other words, while being outside the body, ones’ consciousness could still control their body as though it was a puppet.

Although the Stellar Body Tempering Technique explicitly wrote the dangers of using it, Zhao Hai still practice it. He now felt that the technique would be a great use to him.

Zhao Hai thought that with his crystal body as well as his ability to become liquid metal, this body tempering technique shouldn’t hurt as much. However, he soon discovered that he made a mistake, a very huge mistake.

His body had multiple divergent abilities. HIs crystal body made his body incomparably hard, meanwhile, his liquid metal body made his body like mercury.

But because of this, Zhao Hai’s pain was elevated when practicing. If other people’s cells were like pieces of bread as it underwent the technique, then Zhao Hai’s cells were akin to iron balls. Tempering this iron ball made it red hot, and as it was repeatedly hammered, this iron ball would eventually turn into a refined steel ball.

When Zhao Hai began practicing the technique, he began to understand why one would need to separate their consciousness from their body during tempering. Unless one separates their consciousness from their body, they would experience soul-wrenching pain, endangering their mental state.

Upon directing the power of the stars to temper his body, Zhao Hai felt his every cell in his body burning from pain much worse than being burned alive. He wasn’t able to issue a punch before he fainted on the spot.

After he stopped practicing the technique, Zhao Hai began to think about how to succeed in practicing it. Separating his consciousness while controlling his body shouldn’t be difficult. He could have his consciousness fly out of his body and have Cai’er possess it. However, Zhao Hai didn’t do this. This was because he felt that achieving mastery on this process would provide him with a great advantage.

Zhao Hai used five days to fully achieve the separation between consciousness and body. But it still had to be said that he had Cai’er’s help with this. He would have Cai’er control his body in order to feel the separation. Then he would slowly control his body with his own thought until he was able to fully use it.

After achieving this step, Zhao Hai began practicing the Stellar Body Tempering Technique. This time, he succeeded with his consciousness in the air while controlling his body. He began to control his body to execute a punch, and this time he didn’t even feel a little pain.

This was where Zhao Hai began truly learning the Stellar Body Tempering Technique. However, practicing this method couldn’t be done for days on end. At most, Zhao Hai can separate his consciousness for two hours each day. This was also his limit in practicing the fist techniques.

Now, Zhao Hai’s daily schedule included practicing the Stellar Body Tempering Technique. Just as expected, this technique was really useful for him. After he began practicing the technique, his crystallization and liquefaction had been perfectly integrated to his body. In the past, when he used his crystal form, his body would become like crystal. And although he hadn’t used it in a fight, he saw that his liquid metal form would make him indistinguishable compared to a normal human form.

But now, when Zhao Hai used these two forms, his body wouldn’t undergo a drastic change. Although it would change his form a little, one could still see that it was Zhao Hai. Moreover, his body can now be as hard as diamond and also as soft as a mountain stream.

The advantages of the Stellar Transformations Body Tempering Technique didn’t stop here. It also had a huge benefit to Zhao Hai’s spiritual force. At the same time, his absorption of spiritual qi in practicing the Stellar Transformation Yin-Yang art had become much smoother and quicker.

Besides these harvests, in the past two months, Zhao Hai had also received the secret formation sets of the Bone Symbol Camp. When Zhao Hai opened the file, he saw that there were about 100 thousand formations inside. Using these two months, Zhao Hai was able to condense these formations. Now that Zhao Hai had broken through, he could easily condense ten thousand magic formations at the same time. His speed had become extremely shocking.

Not to mention the Bone Symbol Camp’s formations, even the entire Machine Field’s public collection of formations had already been condensed. At this point, the number of formation sets that Zhao Hai can use had reached an insane and uncountable amount.

But even if this was the case, Zhao Hai didn’t think that he was unparalleled. This was simply impossible. He was clear that Mages in the Machine Field still fell short compared to other people in the World of Cultivation. In the other 5 realms, their strongest weapons were the people themselves. But in the Machine Field, their strongest weapons were battleships.

Because of this, while Zhao Hai was still condensing formations, the majority of his effort was practicing the Stellar Body Tempering Technique. Although he could only practice for two hours every day, Zhao Hai could still visualize how the fist techniques were used. The more he visualized, the more he felt the novelty of this technique.

There were two ways to use this set of fist techniques. One was to supplement the tempering of the body itself. Using the set of fist techniques to temper the body would allow the tempering to be done with twice the results and half the effort.

But the other way to use the fist technique was to use the Stellar Transformations Art to enhance it. This would make the fist technique a top-level technique against enemies.

Zhao Hai’s Stellar Transformations Yin-Yang Art had now reached the second rank of the second layer. Each layer of the art was divided into 9 ranks. Before this breakthrough, Zhao Hai was stuck at the first layer, ninth rank. And now that he had broken through, he immediately barreled through to the second rank of the second layer. One could see how hard it was to break through from layer to layer.

Besides his cultivation level being promoted, the Space had also leveled up. Zhao Hai’s Space was now level 150. Moreover, the spiritual qi of the Space had become equal to the Machine Field. And because of the Hundred Spirit Tree and the Tree of Life, the level was beginning to surpass the Machine Field.

The reason of the Space’s upgrade was the increase of the spiritual qi density. As Zhao Hai adapted to the Machine Field’s spiritual qi, the Space was also undergoing changes. As Zhao Hai’s adaptation improved, the Space’s level increased as well. And in the end, the Space stopped at level 150.

Naturally, it was impossible for there to be no benefits when the Space reached this level. The Space had recognized the Machine Field’s spiritual qi to be medium-grade. So now, Zhao Hai can purchase medium-grade Cultivation Backgrounds as well as Science and Technology Backgrounds. As for Magic Backgrounds, Zhao Hai could now purchase advanced-level ones.

One shouldn’t underestimate these backgrounds. Zhao Hai had benefited a lot with this upgrade. The science and technology background now allowed him to make mechs and battleships. As for the Cultivation backgrounds, high-ranked herbs can now be planted there. It even reached the point where the backgrounds can produce magical treasures.

It was because of all of these developments that Zhao Hai stayed inside his villa for two straight months. He was continuously practicing in the Space.

Chapter 1119: Six Realms Beginner Competition

Although the people in the Bone Symbol Camp were very curious about Zhao Hai, nobody actually said anything about his treatment. This was because his arrangement was given by the Camp Lord himself.

The Bone Symbol Camp was a very united group. Every member of the camp was very respectful of Desbarres. Therefore, when Zhao Hai was arranged to live in the level 4 area, nobody made a bad comment. Instead, everyone hoped that Zhao Hai could make accomplishments soon. This way, the Bone Symbol Camp could rise.

The people from the Bone Symbol Camp were also not strangers to Zhao Hai’s progress. They knew that Zhao Hai had just ascended for a month before being taken to the Bone Symbol Camp. And in the past two months, Zhao Hai had been adapting to the spiritual qi of the Machine Field.

When they first heard about Zhao Hai, the people in the Bone Symbol Camp couldn’t help but feel their blood boil. Zhao Hai being invited over to the camp a month after ascending was enough to show his talent. The people in the camp knew that their own talents weren’t that good. The current strongest expert in the camp was at level 5. They simply had no superiority over the other camps. Because of this, they want Zhao Hai to progress quicker. This way, he could make the Bone Symbol Camp raise their heads high once more.

In the beginning, when the people from the Bone Symbol Camp saw that Zhao Hai was quite fast in adapting to the spiritual qi density, they couldn’t help but get worried. They were afraid that since Zhao Hai was getting preferential treatment, then he would become arrogant and complacent. But in the end, this thought quickly vanished.

Seeing Zhao Hai not leave his villa for two months made people shut up. And in place of worry, their feelings were replaced by anticipation.

It was common for Mages to close up for practice, but this would only take a few days. This was because they would need to take a few walks in order to unwind. Not only would stress not offer any advantages, it would also affect their mental state. And an unsteady mental state was detrimental to cultivation.

Generally, those who cultivate for extended periods of time were cultivators from the Cultivation Realm. They had methods that had high requirements when it came to mental states. Closing up for a long time was a method of training their mental state. By closing up for a long time, they would be able to polish their mental states. In turn, this would benefit their cultivation.

However, those cultivators had different methods compared to Mages. Although they didn’t want to, Mages had to recognize that their training methods were inferior to that of cultivators.

Now, Zhao Hai had grinded for two straight months. His mental state truly left the people from the Bone Symbol Camp ashamed.

Although it can be said that Desbarres and Tao Wang were often looking after him, achieving this point wasn’t easy. But what they didn’t know was that Zhao Hai spent the majority of his time inside the Space. He didn’t stay outside for a long time.

Two months had passed but Zhao Hai had yet to come out. However, the people from the Bone Symbol Camp didn’t have the time to think about him at this time. This was because the pentennial Six Realms Beginner Competition was approaching.

This so-called beginner competition was actually a life and death battle. This battle was held every 5 years. Only those who ascended in the last five years could participate in it. And people from the World of Cultivation were barred from entering.

This competition has been held more than 100 times. The goal for this competition wasn’t just for comparing skills, it was also resource allocation.

Although the World of Cultivation was seen as a huge treasure trove for resources, the true treasures of this world was actually very limited. Take ghost mithril, for example. One might see that Zhao Hai managed to mine a lot from Tyro Planet. However, if these ores were divided to those who needed it, then only a small number of people would be able to get their hands on the ore.

Things like the ghost mithril ore were very important for experts. This was because one’s cultivation would be improved once they get their hands on it. This was especially true for

those who practice Magic Theory.

Because of this, competition for resources among the people in the World of Cultivation went non-stop.

There were no obvious territorial lines between the six realms in the World of Cultivation. And in the borders between two powers, there were grey areas that both territories manage. However, there was actually no control over them. And the planets in these grey areas would sometimes have things that everyone needed.

In order to compete for these resources, people from the six realms fought repeatedly. Casualties in these fights were innumerable. In the end, the higher ups of the six realms knew that this couldn’t continue. Therefore, the six realms reached a consensus to hold an event every year for ascenders. The ones permitted to join this event were only those who ascended in the past five years. This way the participants wouldn’t be too strong. Additionally, if they died, then the loss wouldn’t be too big and no group would be seriously damaged.

Those who won the competition would have more jurisdiction over these grey areas for five years. And then five years later, another competition would be held in order to decide who would control these areas for the next five years.

And to those ascenders who attended the competition, the people from the six realms would make sure that they weren’t treated unjustly. Not only would these people obtain rich rewards, their influence and advantages would also increase. Some were even given a high-value mine. It can be said that the beginner competition wasn’t just a way for the six realms to establish borders, it was also a way for newcomers to become famous in a very short time.

Each time the Six Realm Beginner Competition happened, geniuses would come out of the woodwork. Although these people were from the lower realms and had ascended for no longer than 5 years, their cultivation levels were actually quite good. Some had even developed to become experts.

The competition was also a grand event where major forces compete for their interests. Although there would be countless loses and injuries, for the major powers, the gains far outweigh the losses.

As time passed, the Six Realm Beginner Competition became not just about vying for resources. It also became an event for realms to showcase their strength. So every time the beginner competition happened, everyone paid it attention.

And now, even if there was still a year left before the beginner competition, the qualifiers for the competition had already begun. All the forces in the six realms were beginning to compete on who would participate in the competition. The top 100 in the qualifiers of each realm would go to join the beginner competition.

Because of the rule that ascenders were the only ones allowed to enter the competition, the major influences of each realm didn’t have the means to participate. Take the Ashley Family, for example, their key forces were all members of their family. And thus, these members were natives to the Machine Field, with almost no ascender among their ranks. And even if ascenders managed to join their core forces, these ascenders couldn’t join since they had ascended for more than five years. Therefore, the core of each family had no way of joining the competition.

Therefore, in the Machine Feild, those who attended the beginner competition were certainly from External Halls. This was because, besides the few family members joining, each External Hall were made up of ascenders.

There were plenty of ascenders in the Bone Symbol Camp that had the qualifications to join the competition. However, they weren’t strong. The strongest among them was no more than level 2. And those who were thinking of joining the competition were very little.

This situation didn’t stop the Bone Symbol Camp’s members from paying attention to the Six Realm Beginner Competition; especially those who had the requirements to attend. Although they weren’t strong, they still thought that they had the chance.

Zhao Hai was completely unaware of this matter. He just ascended to the Machine Field. And in addition to his time practicing, the times he accessed the net was very minimal. Therefore, he managed to miss information about this huge event.

Moreover, Desbarres and Tao Wang didn’t inform Zhao Hai about this matter. This was because the beginner competition carried an extremely huge risk. People would die in the most unexpected ways. Zhao Hai had ascended three months ago and was still adapting to the density of spiritual qi. Allowing him to join the competition was simply sending him to his death.

Although Desbarres knew that Zhao Hai had plenty of powerful Undead, allowing him to compete against level 4 Mages, he still didn’t think of having Zhao Hai join the competition. This was because Zhao Hai was the Bone Symbol Camp’s hope. Also, the Bone Symbol Camp wasn’t lacking in money nor resources. So he didn’t want Zhao Hai to take risks.

But even if Zhao Hai didn’t know, this didn’t mean that other people wouldn’t , especially Laura and the others. They surf the net every day in order to understand the Machine Field better. And how could the internet not include information about the competition? Not only was information available, the propaganda about the competition was overwhelming. There were even sites that wrote about the competition’s origins, its process, and its past results. Everything about it was expertly detailed. Therefore, Laura and the others were aware about this matter.

Needless to say, the Machine Field was at the bottom of all participants. After all, the strength of the other realms was focused on the individual while the Machine Field relied on mechs and battleships. Because of this, the Machine Field had no chance in winning the competition.

But this didn’t mean that they wouldn’t send participants. Conversely, the Machine Field would always send ascenders to participate. Although they would struggle against the other five realms, these participants were also fighting for their groups in the Machine Field.

The Machine Field was also using the Beginner Competition as the basis for the internal distribution of resources. Just like how the 100 final participants were handsomely rewarded, their groups would also gain a corresponding benefit. And if a participant did well, gaining good achievements, then their group would receive good advantages. Because of this, the Machine Field placed great importance on the competition. During this period of time, as long as one was online, they would definitely read about this event. And it was in this manner that Laura and the other learned about the entirety of the competition.

Chapter 1120: I Must Participate!

Zhao Hai was currently inside the villa. In front of him was a computer with an article about the Six Realm Beginner Competition.

After reading the article, Zhao Hai turned to Laura and said, “What? You want me to join this competition?”

Laura nodded and said, “Right. We have been in the Machine Field for three months now. And in the past three months, we have basically adapted our lifestyle to it. You should also know how sincere Desbarres has been. So isn’t this beginner competition an opportunity to make the Bone Symbol Cmap rise again?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “You sound like a member of the Bone Symbol Camp.”

Laura chuckled, “Although I’m not a member of the camp, I was able to see how the camp works in the past few days. To be honest, I’ve taken a liking to this group. Everyone is united, Desbarres certainly poured great effort into this camp.”

Zhao Hai nodded, he couldn’t help but agree to Laura’s words. He also liked the atmosphere of the camp. And to be honest, he had already learned a lot in the Machine Field. It was time to go outside and look at different sceneries in the World of Cultivation.

With this thought in mind, Zhao Hai gave a nod and said, “Alright, I’ll join the competition. I also want to see the strength of the other realms.”

Laura and the others happily nodded. Zhao Hai saw their reaction and smiled. To be honest, Zhao Hai’s stay inside the Space was to accompany them. He knew that Laura and the others were bored of staying inside the Space. Therefore, he took the time to be with them.

Looking at the time, Zhao Hai and the others had their meal before Zhao Hai went out of the Space. Then he told his robot to contact Desbarres and Tao Wang.

All robots have communication functions built inside them. However, when people leave their homes, they usually don’t bring their robots with them. When they were out, they would use their computers to contact other people.

Although they didn’t know why Zhao Hai contacted them, Desbarres and Tao Wang still used the quickest time to head towards the villa.

Seeing that Zhao Hai was already waiting for them, Tao Wang looked at Zhao Hai and asked, “Little Hai, what’s the problem? You want to drink?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Camp Lord, Brother Tao. Take a seat first. I have something to tell you.”

Desbarres and Tao Wang looked at Zhao Hai’s conduct and couldn’t help but feel that something was happening. They had been in contact with Zhao Hai for two months, so they already have an idea about his temper. Zhao Hai, who wasn’t really too formal, acting formally made them feel somewhat strange.

The two sat down with Zhao Hai opposite them. Zhao Hai looked at the two and said, “Camp Lord, I called you over to tell you that I have already adapted to the Machine Field’s spiritual qi. Moreover, I’ve decided to enter the Six Realms Beginner Competition!”

Desbarres and Tao Wang heard what Zhao Hai said and couldn’t help but stare. Desbarres immediately stood up and said, “No, Little Hai, you can’t!  The beginner competition is very dangerous. You can’t participate.”

Tao Wang added, “Little Hai, you shouldn’t join, it’s too dangerous. It’s common for people to die in the competition. Even those powerful experts lose their lives.”

Zhao Hai saw their reactions and could understand what they were thinking. He smiled faintly and said, “Camp Lord, Brother Tao Wang. Rest assured, I fully understand the danger of the competition. However, I need to participate. This is the turning point for the Bone Symbol Camp!”

Desbarres and Tao Wang found themselves silent upon hearing Zhao Hai. They worked hard so that the Bone Symbol Camp would rise. However, they still didn’t think it’s time for Zhao Hai to help them.

Naturally, not allowing Zhao Hai participate in the competition didn’t mean that Zhao Hai wouldn’t participate in future battles. They knew that practice couldn’t make an expert. And they already made plans about Zhao Hai’s future development.

This plan was quite comprehensive. It started after Zhao Hai adapts to the density of spiritual qi. He would first be assigned small tasks. These tasks would be done in groups so there wouldn’t be any danger. This would exercise Zhao Hai’s mindset as he was given more and more responsibility. Then several years later, he would represent the camp in the Family’s internal competition. This would be the beginning of his rise in the Machine Field.

There were no risks in this plan as it involved training Zhao Hai. All of these were made because Desbarres and Tao Wang placed too much of their hopes on Zhao Hai. They didn’t want Zhao Hai to go out this early.

Because of this, when they heard Zhao Hai saying that he wants to join the beginner competition, they couldn’t help but show a huge response. In their minds, sending Zhao Hai to join the beginner competition was akin to sending him to his destruction.

Zhao Hai looked at their reactions and smiled, “Camp Lord, Big Brother Tao, don’t reject so easily. Let’s sit down and slowly talk this over. To be honest, my decision isn’t done in the heat of the moment. Let me be true to you, my strength has reached level 4. I have confidence to defeat the enemy. Therefore, I decided to join the competition.”

Desbarres frowned and said, “I know that you have strong Undead and is both a Mage and a Warrior, so it isn’t surprising to know that you can defeat level 4 Mages. However, you are competing in the Six Realms Beginner Competition. No matter which realm, each one would treat this matter with importance. Therefore, the participants of this competition are all elites from all kinds of origin. The losers would either be dead or severely injured. It is a competition with a high rate of mortality. It isn’t the reputation boost that I want, and I don’t want to extinguish our hopes in it. And to be honest, there is a huge disparity between the Mages and Warriors of our Machine Field compared to the other 5 realms. And that disparity is weapons.”

Desbarres stopped here, but Tao Wang followed up, “Right, our biggest gap is in weapons. The strongest weapons of the other realms are those magic talismans. These talismans are single use weapons. So in this competition, the other realms would surely use these talismans. The might of these talismans is quite terrifying. Even if we have Mages more powerful than them, we still couldn’t underestimate them because of these talismans. This is the reason why me and the Camp Lord doesn’t want you to participate in the competition.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “I found out about those when I was researching the other 5 realms. But Camp Lord, this makes me want to join the competition even more. Don’t forget, all spoils from the battle will belong to the winner. I want to get those items. Moreover, I have the confidence to deal with them.”

Desbarres frowned, “Little Hai, I still think that it is too risky. Our Machine Field had never achieved success in the beginner competition. Our top three members have already surpassed five years. Also, every time we send participants for the competition, they were at least ascenders for three years. From this point, you should see how powerful the opponents are. I really don’t want you to enter the competition.”

Zhao Hai didn’t say anything and just smiled faintly as he waved his hand. Then a layered formation set appeared in front of him.

When Desbarres and Tao Wang saw the formation set that Zhao Hai released, they couldn’t help but be shocked. One must know that layered formation sets weren’t easy to use. Every layer added to a formation demanded a high amount of spiritual force. Moreover, experiments would be needed for a Mage to use a formation set. They need to know which formation was compatible with another formation, and also find out if the formation was beneficial to the set. Because of this, beginner Mages would find it difficult to use layered formations. Only after gaining enough experience could they push on and become stronger. The more they know which formations were compatible for them, the quicker they would be able to layer them. This was also why level 1 Mages have 5 formations as their peak, level 2 Mages have ten, level three Mages have 50. And more than that for level 4.

And for most Mages, finding a 50-layer formation would need about five to ten years of research. Even if one studied Magic Theory all their life, they would still need three to five years. Not to say achieving 50-layered formation sets, there were Mages who got stuck at level 3.

Now that Zhao Hai revealed this formation, Desbarres and Tao Wang were shaken. They didn’t know how Zhao Hai managed to accomplish this in such a short time.

Zhao Hai waved his hand again, withdrawing his spiritual force. In turn, the formation dissipated. When the magic formation disappeared, only then did Desbarres and Tao Wang recover. They looked at each other and saw the surprise and joy in each of their eyes.

Zhao Hai looked at the two and smiled, “I’m already a level 4 Mage. Moreover, my battle qi is quickly catching up. At the very least, I have the means to survive if I join the competition. Camp Lord, Big Brother Tao, this is an opportunity for the Bone Symbol Camp to rise!”

Chapter 1121: Test, A Group of Ten!

On the Bone Symbol Camp’s mountainous region was a training ground. It was the most elaborate training ground of the eight. People were currently present in this place. There was a competition between members of the Bone Symbol Camp.

One side was Zhao Hai while the other side were people elected by Desbarres. These were the representatives of the latest generation, totalling ten. The context of the test was very simple. As long as Zhao Hai can win against these ten people, then he would be allowed to participate in the Six Realm Beginner Competition!

After Zhao Hai revealed his hundred-layer formation, Desbarres finally relented. He agreed to Zhao Hai joining the beginner competition, but on the condition that Zhao Hai pass a test.

The mountainous training ground was chosen out of all the training grounds because Desbarres knew that the battles of the Six Realm Beginner Competition weren’t only in arenas. Participants would also fight under various environments.

The Bone Symbol Camp spent a high price constructing this training ground. The entire place took more than 2000 mu. There were nearly a hundred thousand cameras installed inside the area. There were also 100 aerial cameras circling the place. These cameras could monitor the training ground for five straight days, completely recording the entire event.

At this time, Desbarres and Tao Wang were sitting inside the training ground’s spectator’s room. In front of them was a large screen showing Zhao Hai and his ten opponents. The former entering a different entrance than the latter.

It wasn’t just Desbarres and Tao Wang who were inside the spectator room. Elders of the Bone Symbol Camp were also present. When these people learned from Tao Wang that the unseen Zhao Hai was currently being tested, they couldn’t stop their curiosity from surfacing, so they joined in to spectate.

The ten people elected by Desbarres had already surpassed the five-year mark of ascending. Moreover, their strengths were pretty good. There were six Warriors and four Mages. Three of the Warriors were level 4 while the other three were level 3. As for the Mages, two were level 4 while the other two were level 3.

With Desbarres’s signal, Zhao Hai and the other ten people entered the mountainous grounds. The grounds were densely forested and had varied terrain. There were stones, trees, water, pits, and holes inside. The terrain was very complex. Only those with enough fighting experience could find the enemy and make a surprise attack.

When Zhao Hai entered the grounds, everyone’s eyes were immediately aimed at him. They wanted to see how Zhao Hai planned to proceed. Zhao Hai looked around and then waved his hand, releasing about a hundred Undead. The undead went on to scatter themselves out into the surrounding area. Meanwhile, Zhao Hai looked for a cave where he sat down and closed his eyes.

Upon seeing Zhao Hai’s action, Desbarres and the others were stunned. But in the end, they nodded. They understood what Zhao Hai wanted to do. He hadn’t been to this training ground before, so he was quite unfamiliar with its terrain. In this situation, it was better to have the Undead scout while he looked for a place to wait in. He would only attack once he found the enemy. This was the most correct approach for him.

Desbarres spared a lot of thoughts in constructing this training ground. There were large numbers of spirit-suppressing stones installed all around the training ground. This way, people wouldn’t be able to use their spiritual force to scout the area. Otherwise, Mages could just sweep the entire area with their spiritual force. If this happens, then what’s the point of the varied terrain?

Spirit-suppressing stones were relatively common in the World of Cultivation. This stone doesn’t have any other effect other than suppressing a person’s spiritual force. Also, the more stones there were, the more powerful the suppression would be. If your original spiritual force could be released up to 10 thousand meters and there are 100 cubic meters of spirit-suppressing stones, then your spiritual force would be limited to 100 meters.

Although spirit-suppressing stones weren’t rare in the World of Cultivation, this didn’t mean that they were cheap. In this mountainous training ground, Desbarres installed 2000 cubic meters of stone. One could see that its construction was definitely a huge deal.

Even if the people in the spectator room thought that Zhao Hai’s method was very good, there were actually only a few who could really do it.

If one wanted their Undead to scout like Zhao Hai, they needed to accomplish a few points. First, if one was a Dark Mage, then they would need to know summoning magic. Second, they need high-level Undead. If they only had low-level undead, then they wouldn’t be able to gain any information at all, completely removing the possibility of reconnaissance.

The third point was that they should have formidable spiritual force. It was well known that summoners couldn’t be too far from their summoned creatures. If a summoned creature goes beyond the summoner’s range, then their control would go weaker up to the point where the summoner could no longer control the creature.

Out of everyone present, only a handful of them could achieve this. And to those who were able to do it, they were able to gauge of Zhao Hai’s strength.

Before long, Zhao Hai’s undead discovered an enemy, it was a Mage. Zhao Hai began to move. He walked out of the cave and went towards the Mage. The Undead that discovered the Mage was already unsummoned by Zhao Hai. Because of this, the Mage had yet to know that he has been discovered.

Just like everyone else, the Mage was using spiritual force in order to explore the surroundings. He carefully moved forward while also having a protective shield around him. Although this might possibly cause him to be discovered, the shield would protect him from any surprise attack.

Zhao Hai slowly trekked through the dense forest. From the Undead, he knew about the terrain in front of him. Therefore, he wasn’t worried about falling into pits.

Before long, Zhao Hai felt the Mage’s presence. He didn’t only feel the Mage’s spiritual force, he could also feel the energy coming off of the shield.

Zhao Hai began to tread carefully. Not only did he withdraw his spiritual force, he also hid his form using the shadow of the trees.

The people in the spectator room looked breathlessly at Zhao Hai’s actions. They found that Zhao Hai was like an assassin as he proceeded carefully. The Mage didn’t discover Zhao Hai at all. The distance between the two was getting smaller and smaller.

When the distance between the two became a hundred meters, Zhao Hai suddenly sped up. He appeared behind the Mage and then a 50-layer formation set appeared in his hand. Then Zhao Hai said, “Sharp Metal, Spear!” As his voice fell, a huge metal spear flew out of the magic formation, stabbing through the Mage’s shield. And like a bubble, the shield broke.

Just as the Mage was about to counterattack, Zhao Hai already got another 50-layer formation ready. When the formation appeared, Zhao Hai said, “Breeze lock!” Along with Zhao Hai words, a wind element chain appeared around the Mage and then entangled him. When the Mage was captured, the Mage was already out of the test. This was because Zhao Hai could kill him in that state.

The Mage understood this point and his expression couldn’t help but drop. Then he nodded towards Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai waved his hand and the wind chains vanished. The Mage bowed towards Zhao Hai before leaving the battlefield.

Zhao Hai moved once more and disappeared into the forest. If the people from the spectator room didn’t look through the cameras, then they wouldn’t have known where he was.

Zhao Hai’s fight with the Mage was very short. Zhao Hai only sent two magic formations to defeat the other party. However, as long as magic was used, a disturbance would appear. The others already noticed the magical waves coming from the battle.

At this time, Zhao Hai was flying towards a Warrior. This Warrior was level 4. Although his strength was among the top, he was still quite careful. He had his weapon ready and he moved slowly.

Then suddenly, the Warrior felt magical ripples in front of him. He wasn’t familiar with this ripple, so he readied his sword so that he could immediately send his sword qi.

After carefully advancing for two minutes, the Warrior suddenly felt some movement not far away from him. He hid behind a tree and looked ahead. What he saw stunned him. This was because not too far from him was an Undead holding a mage staff. When he saw this, he was startled, he knew that this was a trap!

But even if the Warrior found out about this, it was already too late. He suddenly heard a voice saying, “Green vine, entangle!” Upon hearing this voice, the Warrior found that the tree he was hiding behind suddenly sprouted vines. It didn’t take long before the vines wrapped around the Warrior.

However, the vines didn’t wrap him for a long time and loosened slowly after. When the Warrior saw Zhao Hai, he didn’t say anything and just nodded before leaving the area.

The man sighed as he took his sword and left the training grounds.

At this moment, the other people arrived at the place of Zhao Hai’s first battle. Naturally, there was nobody there. Although traces of magic were still present, nobody could make any use of it.

The eight people looked at each other. Then they felt the magic that Zhao Hai released when fighting the Warrior. But just as they were about to go over, they suddenly found out that they had been surrounded!

Chapter 1122: Resolution of Zhao Hai

There were ten thousand bone-armored Undead, each holding their own weapon, and were on battle formation. The undead surrounded the eight people. The eight knew that the test was over upon seeing all of these Undead. The undead were too high-level; each one of them were rank 9 Apprentices. Such strength with that number, they had no chance to resist.

Desbarres and the others also knew that the test was over when they saw this situation. Desbarres and Tao Wang looked at each other and saw a trace of excitement on the other’s eyes.

Zhao Hai’s strength and his use of magic formations were completely beyond their imagination. One shouldn’t just look at the layered formations that Zhao Hai used. For Desbarres, level 4 Mages could also use normal formations instead of layered ones. They were like cooks. If they only have a handful of recipes on hand, then it might not be appropriate to use those all the time. Sometimes, the chef needed to use ordinary dishes to serve his customers.

Level 4 Mages might be known for their multiple-layer formations. But during battles, they only use layered formations about ten to twenty times. It was impossible to use layered formations all the time. Although layered formations held great power, the speed of casting them wasn’t quick. And in battle, the faster you can release your magic, the better your chances of winning would be.

On the other hand, the magic that Zhao Hai used were all 50-layered formations. Moreover, he casted them in almost an instant. Not even level 5 or level 6 Mages could do this. Therefore, Desbarres and Tao Wang were very happy.

The other people in the room were also very happy. Zhao Hai’s performance far exceeded what they expected. They really didn’t expect a three-month ascender to have this strength. In their minds, Zhao Hai was the hope of the Bone Symbol Camp.

Now that the test was done, Desbarres and Tao Wang led the other people in the Bone Symbol Camp towards the training ground’s exit. When Zhao Hai came out, Desbarres laughed and patted his shoulders, then he said, “Little Hai, good, good. Everyone, let’s go to the restaurant. We’ll have a good drink together!” Everyone cheered. But some of them curiously looked at Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai didn’t appear in the camp in the past two months; he just stayed inside his room. However, details about him were spread towards the camp. He only ascended for a month; then after taking an exam, he entered the Bone Symbol Camp.

To be honest, the people from the Bone Symbol Camp found this timeframe hard to believe. But at the same time, they also felt happy. They were somewhat looking forward to seeing this talent that Desbarres brought. They were anticipating what miracles he would do after closing up for two months.

And sure enough, Zhao Hai didn’t disappoint them. After closing up for two months, he really did bring forth a miracle. He actually ended a battle against ten people in such a short time. Although his undead practically ended the test, these Undead were part of his strength. Because of this, nobody thought that it was unfair.

Desbarres brought everyone to a large restaurant. This large restaurant spanned the first to third floor of the building. The entire place could accommodate ten thousand people at the same time.

At the end of each year, members of the Bone Symbol camp would come here for a meal. Everyone would participate. They would review what happened that year while also giving away bonuses.

After bringing the group to the restaurant, Desbarres also rung everyone currently in the camp. It didn’t take long before 5000 people came in at once.

Desbarres didn’t stop anyone. When he saw that almost everyone was here, Desbarres stood up from his seat and walked to the middle. He looked at everyone and said, “I reckon everyone already knows about today’s gathering. I’m officially introducing Zhao Hai. He joined the Bone Symbol Camp two months ago. And after closing up for two months, he is now officially joining the camp.”

Zhao Hai stood up as well. Tao Wang then pushed him towards the Camp Lord’s side. He bowed to everyone in the camp and was met with applause.

Desbarres waved his hand down and the crowd stopped. He looked around and said, “Besides introducing Little Hai to you, I also called you over for an announcement. I’ve decided to have Little Hai represent the Bone Symbol Camp in this generation’s Six Realm Beginner Competition!”

Upon hearing the Camp Lord, the entire room went abuzz. Theoretically, the Six Realm Beginner Competition can be attended by any ascender that had ascended for less than five years. However, most groups would have an internal test before deciding on who to send.

As for the Ashley Family, the eight camps of the External Hall would conduct a test among themselves. Then they would select the strongest to participate in the Machine Field’s own test. This time, there was no limit to how many joined. This matter will be decided by the Camp Lords; the family wouldn’t interfere.

Although there were quite a few newcomers who wanted to participate in the competition, they still have to pass Desbarres’s test. And according to the Camp Lord’s previous actions, he wouldn’t send the truly strong individuals. He was afraid that they would lose their lives in the competition.

Desbarres properly cared for these new members. Although those people might blame him, Desbarres didn’t want to make any risks. This was because Desbarres knew that their strength was still quite bad. Not to say about the Machine Field’s qualifiers, they might not even pass the test inside the family.

The Ashley Family adopted a very strict stance on competition. The relationship between the eight camps wasn’t good; and the competition between them was very serious. If these newcomers from the Bone Symbol Camp join the competition, then some of them might die. Because of this, Desbarres didn’t allow them to join.

If Zhao Hai didn’t pass the test, then Desbarres wouldn’t let him participate. Even if Zhao Hai wanted to, then it was useless. The test didn’t only test Zhao Hai’s strength, it also tested his combat experience. Seeing Zhao Hai’s performance, Desbarres knew that Zhao Hai had been in wars. So he was at ease.

Desbarres looked at everyone’s reaction. These people didn’t know Zhao Hai’s ability, so their reaction was normal.

Desbarres didn’t say anything and just stood quietly for a while. At the same time, when those present saw that Desbarres didn’t speak for some time, they also began to quiet down.

When the hall turned quiet, Desbarres said, “There’s no need to doubt Little Hai’s strength. Although he just ascended for three months, he had already passed the test I’ve prepared for him. He definitely has the strength to participate in the beginner competition’s qualifiers. If you aren’t convinced, then you can talk to his opponents.”

The people that Desbarres talked about weren’t embarrassed to be defeated by Zhao Hai in the test. On the contrary, they stood up and gave everyone a salute.

Desbarres continued, “The first competition is in one month. So nobody disturb Zhao Hai during this period of time, understand?” Everyone loudly complied. Then Desbarres led Zhao Hai to return to their table.

Desbarres’s table only had a few people in it. There was Desbarres himself, Tao Wang, Zhao Hai, and then a man dressed in Warrior clothing. This person was very tall and had muscles akin to forged copper. He had a bald head and radiant eyes. His pair of hands were particularly thick.

This person was called Tie Sheng. He was a level 5 Warrior whose weapons were a pair of hammers. He was also an Expert who knew how the camp worked and was Desbarres’s most efficient assistant.

Tie Sheng was on duty before and had just come back. He also saw Zhao Hai’s exam and understood his strength. Because of this, he was very polite towards Zhao Hai.

After Desbarres sat down, he looked at the three and said, “Now that Little Hai’s test is finished, A’Wang, take Little Hai to the treasury tomorrow. Let him choose a few weapons and armor. Those things have gathered dust for several years, its time for them to come out.”

Tao Wang gave a small nod before turning to Zhao Hai and saying, “Little Hai, although our Bone Symbol Camp is worse than before, when it comes to riches, no other camp compares to us. All these years, the camp has been collecting a lot of good treasures. I will go take you to see them tomorrow.”

Although he knew that these wouldn’t be useful for this strength, Zhao Hai still gave a nod. He doesn’t want people to know about this magic staff yet. Even if his staff was his exclusive item, people would still attempt to grab it once they know about its abilities. In their eyes, even if they couldn’t use it, they’d still prefer it if it was in their hands.

Because of this, Zhao Hai decided to follow Tao Wang and take a few weapons for himself. After all, when in battle, it was always better to have more weapons in hand.

Everyone happily ate their meal. Naturally, everyone was talking about Zhao Hai. Desbarres and Tao Wang seems to be very happy as they drank a lot of wine and talked nonstop.

When the feast was over, Zhao Hai returned to his room and entered the Space. Laura and the others were already waiting for him to come back. After they saw Zhao Hai, they immediately provided him with spatial water.

After Zhao Hai had settled down, Laura looked at him and said, “Brother Hai, how’s the test?”

Zhao Hai’s face was a bit heavy when he replied, “It went very well. Instantaneous casting of 50-layer formations are on a completely different level compared to lower realm spells. Although they look ordinary, I’m quite sure that even Addison wouldn’t be able to block them.”

As soon as they heard this, Laura and the others nodded. But then, Laura asked, “That’s fantastic. But why aren’t you glad?”

Zhao Hai let out a long sigh and said, “Although this power is already good in the Machine Field, we still fall short compared to the people in the other realms. Don’t forget, the Machine Field is the weakest one among the six realms of the World of Cultivation. Battleships are the king here. Experts defeated by battleships couldn’t be defeated by normal Mages. On the other hand, powerful experts from the Cultivation Realm could contend against a fleet just on their own. If we are recognized by Lu Wei this time, then we’ll be out of luck.”

When they heard this, Laura and the others turned silent. After a while, Laura said, “Brother Hai, what do you mean?”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “It’s nothing, I was just thinking. We’ve already arrived here in the World of Cultivation. Additionally, with our current strength, we don’t necessarily need to be afraid of Lu Wei. Even if Lu Wei is a member of a sect, he still wouldn’t be able to do anything in the Machine Field. If we keep being afraid because of Lu Wei, then we wouldn’t be able to advance in this place.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Laura and the others stared. Then they looked at Zhao Hai in confusion. In the past, because he was afraid of being chased by Lu Wei, Zhao Hai ascended in the Atlanta Plane. But now, he’s no longer afraid?”

Zhao Hai saw their expressions and couldn’t help but smile faintly as he said, “Are you wondering why I’m afraid of Lu Wei in the lower realms but now I’m not? We’re already here, so why the need to be afraid? Why should we continue being afraid of Lu Wei? Since I decided to show my abilities, then we need to prepare for a fight. This time, I’ll make an impact so big that the other realms would understand that Mages in the Machine Field couldn’t be underestimated. And as long as we give benefits to the Machine Field, then the Machine Field will certainly guarantee our safety.”

Laura and the others were clever people, so they immediately understood what Zhao Hai meant. Laura nodded and said, “Alright. Since Brother Hai can now use thousand-layer formations, you will certainly get a high ranking in the beginner competition. As long as you have a good accomplishment, then the Machine Field will certainly ensure your safety. Even if Lu Wei chases you down, the Machine Field would still block him. If they don’t save you, then nobody might want to work for them in the future. Therefore, it doesn’t matter if it was Lu Wei, Yin Wind Ghost Emperor, or the Myriad Treasures Pavillion, we don’t have to worry about them.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Not only that, but I also want to use this competition to contact a huge sect in the Cultivation Realm. As long as I can enter one of them, I would truly be assured.”

The others nodded. Laura said, “Brother Hai will surely get to join one.”

Chapter 1123: Treasury

Zhao Hai was currently inside an elevator with Tao Wang. Not everyone can go inside this particular elevator. Without Desbarres’s permission, nobody besides Tao Wang can enter this place. If those with no permission force their way in, then the defense system will immediately attack them.

There were only two buttons that can be pressed in this elevator. Moreover, this elevator was headed towards an underground area. Only a few people were aware of it.

While he stood inside the elevator, Tao Wang turned to Zhao Hai and said, “This elevator’s sole destination is the camp’s treasury. Inside are things that the Bone Symbol Camp had accumulated for many years. The Camp Lord was always reluctant in using what’s inside. He always said that we could only use them during major situations. Besides me, the Camp Lord, and Tie Sheng, nobody else is allowed to enter this place.”

Zhao Hao nodded. He couldn’t help but feel warm inside. Desbarres and the others had taken very good care of him, making it difficult for him to pay them back. Zhao Hai’s principle was returning a drop of graciousness with a river of gratitude. Therefore, he will definitely pay Desbarres’s favor back.

Tao Wang continued, “The treasury is a kilometer underground. Above it are multiple defensive measures. One floor is built out of spirit-suppressing stone. There are also early warning systems, magical defense system, and even a self-destruct system. Anyone who dared to go to the treasury without authorization will be ruthlessly dealt with. And even if an extremely powerful expert comes, the treasury could blow itself up. The might of this explosion is equivalent to a hundred thousand nuclear bombs. I’m afraid that if the treasury truly explodes, then it would take the entire Dark Demon Planet along with it.”

Zhao Hai was startled, he didn’t expect a treasury defense system to be this formidable. It even has a self destruct mechanism that can destroy the entire planet.

Tao Wang turned to look at Zhao Hai and said, “The reason why the Bone Symbol Camp is rich was because the Camp Lord and our various brothers had desperately worked hard for it. The Camp Lord said that these things are shared by all of the brothers in the camp. Even if one of us is left, then they could still revive the camp. And if the Bone Symbol Camp cannot keep these things anymore, then the treasury might as well be buried along with our brothers. It can’t fall into the hands of outsiders.”

Zhao Hai nodded. He didn’t expect the ferocious looking but friendly Desbarres would actually be this ruthless!

The elevator descended for more than ten minutes before it stopped. Then Tao Wang left the elevator first with Zhao Hai closely following behind. Outside the elevator was a small room with three doors in it. Marked on the doors were the numbers one, two, and three.

Tao Wang led Zhao Hai to door number 1. Then he took a key no more than 30 centimeters long. Zhao Hai observed the key and saw that it looked very ordinary. However, it was made out of a material that was neither wood nor metal. It looked quite magical.

After walking to the door, Tao Wang softly knocked on it. After knocking more than 20 times, he stopped. Shortly after that, a magic formation began to appear on the door. When the formation disappeared, a keyhole was left in its place.

Tao Wang proceeded to insert the key and proceeded to unlock the door. The unlocking process wasn’t a one-directional action like rotating. It involved moving the key left to right as well as twisting it at certain angles, it looked very troublesome.

Tao Want used more than ten minutes to unlock the door. Seeing the door open with no problems, Tao Wang let out a long breath before he turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Let’s go. The treasury is divided into four small storehouses. And in order to be safe, doors 2 and 3are false storehouses. If people went through those doors, then they would immediately be reported. And if the door is forcefully opened, then the self-destruct mechanism would start.”

As they were talking, Tao Wang and Zhao Hai entered door number 1. Upon passing through the door, Zhao Hai’s eyes shone brightly. This storehouse was 30 meters high, about ten thousand meters long and also ten thousand meters wide. There were a lot of shelves inside. These shelves were covered with glass containers. There were a lot of weapons on these shelves, both used by Mages and Warriors. There were even formation plates.

Tao Wang looked at Zhao Hai and smiled, “This is only the outside of storehouse 1. We won’t be staying here for long. Let’s go and see the other three storehouses. The good things are there.”

Tao Wang led Zhao Hai further into the storehouse. There were three other doors in this place, each about ten meters high and four meters wide. This time, Tao Wang didn’t use a key and just knocked a few times before the door automatically opened.

When the door opened, Tao Wang led Zhao Hai to go in. Then as they were walking, Tao Wang said, “This is one of the three internal treasuries of the Bone Symbol Camp. The three treasures are respectively named, Armor Treasury, Weapon Treasury, and Magic Treasury. We’re currently in the Armor Treasury. Deposited here are things used for protection. Armors present here not only included those for Warriors. There are also armors that Mages can use. You can look through each item to see their function. It’s much better than me introducing them.”

Zhao Hai nodded. Then he used his spiritual sense to scan the entire treasury. To be honest, he wasn’t expecting to obtain something useful here. With his staff, almost all of his problems were solved. If he wasn’t afraid of other people getting suspicious, then he would’ve already rejected choosing a weapon.

As he swept the area with his spiritual force, Zhao Hai discovered that not only was his spiritual force not suppressed, it was even amplified. This enabled him to see the armors more clearly.

After he swept the place, Zhao Hai saw that the armors here were divided into two types. The first type were those that were made in the Machine Field. A majority of these armors were made of metals with engravings on them. Some looked like iron cans. There were also a few that were inner armors, they were mostly made out of metal arranged in a chainmail configuration.

The other type of armors were armor that had been snatched or bought from the other realms. The styles of these armors greatly varied. Some looked like ancient armors while some looked like cotton garments that doesn’t seem like protective armor at all.

Zhao Hai wasn’t interested on those full body armors. Even if he received those armor by chance, he still wouldn’t use them.

Armors from the Cultivation Realm were further divided into two types. There were protection-type and garment-type. Protection types could recognize their owners by spiritual force. Afterwards, they could be nourished by their users. The longer they were nourished, the more powerful their protection would be.

As for garment-type armors, they were armor that can be worn outside. They could provide pure defense and also passive body cleaning. There were also those that can allow their user to turn invisible. But because of its nature, garment-type armors had much worse defense compared to protection-types.

At the same time, armors from the Machine Field were also divided into two types. First type were exoskeleton armors. These armors were those iron cans that Zhao Hai saw before. These armors were made with the combination of magic and science. When not in use, these armors would were like small devices. But once they were activated, they would surround the user’s body, including the eyes. There was also a computer program inside these armors. The armor itself had a magic formation that provided it with power. Not only could these armors provide protection, they could also aid its user during battle.

However, the downside of this armor was that it takes time for it to fully activate. Although it was only a fraction of time, this smidgen of time was enough for an Expert to take a life.

The second type of armors were these inner armors that looked like chain armor. These armors couldn’t cover the entire body and could only be worn as undergarments. Moreover, the manufacturing of these armors was very complex. Each chain in the armor had a magic formation engraved on it, making it good for defense. This chain armor could only play a defensive function and can’t be used for attack. It also needed a supply of spiritual force when defending. The more powerful your spiritual force is, the stronger its defensive ability.

To be honest, armors made in the Machine Field still couldn’t compare to those in the Cultivation Realm. Although the chain armor looked good, depending on it for defense at the very beginning was very dangerous. Armors from the cultivation realm provide for their own energy and can automatically protect their user. With the Cultivation Realm’s armors, regardless if the user noticed the attack or not, they would still be protected by their armor; which was almost a life-saving ability.

Zhao Hai scoured through the armors and analyzed them. He was favoring the cotton garments of the Cultivation Realms. Although their defense was quite poor, the functions were still very useful. It was also the most comfortable armor to wear in comparison to the others.

Just as he was about to pick a cotton armor for himself. Zhao Hai suddenly discovered something at the corner of the Machine Field section. It was a clump of mercury-looking substance. It didn’t look like an armor at all and instead it was a metal sphere.

Zhao Hai stared. This was because this metal sphere had no introduction, which was surprising.

Tao Wang had been paying attention to Zhao Hai all this time. When he saw Zhao Hai’s expression change, he couldn’t help but be curious. He didn’t know what Zhao Hai just discovered.

At this time, Zhao Hai suddenly said, “Big Brother Tao, I just saw a sphere of liquid metal. What is that?”

When he heard Zhao Hai, Tao Wang immediately knew what he found. Tao Wang smiled bitterly and said, “That sphere of liquid metal is actually very famous in the Machine Field. Nobody knows that it fell into our hands. But even if they did, there wouldn’t be too much of a reaction. After all, it is a failed product.”